The Dancing Dump Truck
Hey, cool moves!
Huh? Who's that?
Hey, you aren't invited here...
Come on, be a good sport and let me in on the fun!
Woohoo! Hahaha!
Huh? Where did you go!?
Ugh...
Save me, brave warrior!
Wahaha! There is no use crying now!
The world belongs to Vance, the evil overlord!
Not so soon, evil overlord Vance!
Are you Jun, the warrior?
Agh, how did he get past our ten million men?!
I will have to dish him a lesson myself!
Take them on, Blue Cop!
Aaugh!
Oh, Jun!
At your service, Princess Anna!
Thank you very much, Jun!
Ahh... Princess Anna... one little kiss on this cheek too, please...
Wake up!
Hey, mom... good morning...
Don't you "good morning" me!
You promised to help out at the restaurant, remember?
Right, I just remembered...
Jun, here's a cheeseburger.
Yes, Dad.
Table number two.
I got it, Dad.
Hey, here's your cheeseburger.
The coffee here is the best in town. I'm not kidding!
That won't get you a refill, officer.
Welcome!
Jun, I think they're here for you.
For me?
Come on in.
Good day, ma'am!
Vance and Lavi?
What are you guys doing here?
What do you mean? This is a restaurant, we're obviously here to eat!
That's not it!
Come here, we need to talk.
Huh? But I'm...
Uh... Welcome, we have a corner table for two right here.
What is it, then?
It's about the robot that took you away.
Uh... what robot?
Don't act coy now!
We know what we saw. On that bridge over the waterway...
Well, it's...
Jun. Please keep this a secret between us.
Secret?
If people of Earth find out about the Metal Cardbots, they will get frightened. I don't want to cause any trouble.
Don't worry, I promise!
Uhhh...
We're going to middle school next year! It's so crazy!
Anna would laugh at us if we were to go around talking about robots!
Vance did say that last time...
Oh, shut up! I'm leaving!
B-but Vance! Don't you want to eat first?!
Have a good day, lady...
Hey, don't you want a smoothie before you leave?
Yeah, can I have a strawberry-
Hurry up!
Ah, maybe next time... wait up, Vance!
Huh? What were they here for?
I have no idea...
A giant robot has been seen in a carpark under an overpass last night.
A giant robot?
This video has caused uproar on the Internet.
According to an eyewitness, a dump truck approached him and his friends...
That's...
Wow, that video looks so real. You can do a lot with CGI these days.
Yeah... it looks like a movie...
I heard the new Max Force movie is coming out soon. Let's say I take you to watch it?
Oh, oh, my dear!
Yes- oh, oh no no!
This is coming out of your pay this month!
No, not again!
No doubt about it. That's Mega Trucker.
Right?
I told him so many times to lay low and not be seen by the people on Earth.
What are you going to do? This already has a million views, it's gone viral!
He won't listen to me anyway.
We'll just have to put him under a seal.
A seal?
You can seal a Metal Cardbot in its Metal Card using the power of the Metal Breath.
In the meantime, I have to go talk to Mega Trucker once more.
Yeah, but to do that, we have to go find him first...
Right. Can you procure a large speaker?
A speaker?
I think I have an idea.
I guess I'm awake now. This will be over before school, right?
For this plan to work, we have to do it when no one's watching, and while it's quiet.
I'll make you coffee if you're sleepy.
I'm too young to drink coffee- wait, you know how to make coffee?
Mega Trucker loves music. His favorite is Musica Latina.
He can't help but dance when he hears that sound.
How about that?
That's perfect.
Let's turn up the volume.
Alright.
Don't you think this is too much?
Not loud enough.
Woohoo! This is just my kind of music!
He actually showed up?!
Let me in on the fun!
Hehehe!
This is great! Step on the gas and let's dance the night away!
Mega Trucker! I told you to lay low and not be seen by anyone!
Why can't you listen?!
You can be boring if you want! I'll live my life dancing and having fun!
Jun, careful!
Hey! Bring the music back!
I can't let you destroy Edo's repair shop!
Who's this kid, anyway?
We have lost our home planet and have no choice but to live here! We must learn to live with the natives, like this boy!
Shut up! Don't you tell me what to do ever again!
Blue Cop!
Blue Cop! Are you alright?
We have no choice. We'll have to fight him to put him under the seal.
Jun! The time has come for us to fight.
So it's come to this. Stay calm... what should I do?
Mega Power Tackle!
Look out, Blue Cop!
Jun, now!
Blue Cop, setup!
Huh? So you know how to hide!
Uhh... Thunderbolt Smash!
Thunderbolt Smaaaa-
Uhh..huhh... sorry...
Hahaha! You're pathetic!
After all that talk, you can't do anything, can you?
Blue Cop!
Jun, I'm okay! Just give me the next command!
Blue Cop, Burst Shot!
Burst Shot!
Great!
Burst Shot, Burst Shot, Burst Shot!
One last shot!
Megavolt Punch!
Megavolt...
Punch!!
Jun, seal it now!
Now? Alright...
Metal Cardbot... Change Up!
Mega Trucker... seal!
Well done, Jun. You did it.
Mega Trucker really turned into a card...
Yes. It's been sealed in the Metal Breath as Metal Card.
You can summon Mega Trucker any time you want with that card,
and give him commands too.
What's going on? What happened here?
Uhh...
Uh, Mister Edo...
This is bad...