The Black Ambulance
A black ambulance?
Yes. An ambulance blackened by fire.
Children taken as its prisoners will have their souls taken by the Grim Reaper,
never to be seen again.
Aah!! I'm so scared!
That's what you want to hear? Try a better story!
Y-yeah, we know it's all made up!
I've heard about it too.
A child was kidnapped by the black ambulance, and by the time he was found...
he had been turned into a mummy!
Aah!
Hey, come on! Stop it already, Anna!
Yeah! Come on, guys! Stop it already!
It's not even a good story!
You WERE listening!
I was just getting to the good part!
No way! You guys seriously need to grow out of those silly stories.
Jun...
Come on... give me a break, Jun!
He used to love stories about robots and ghosts... I wonder what's the matter?
Huh?
...a tire?
Waaugh! Where did it come from??
Hm? What?
T-Teo?
Could that be...?!
I'm back!
Hey Jun, what's up?
What's going on?
It's just like a health checkup.
I'm sorry... but I will have to go faster.
I don't think so!
That's it, you can stop! Stop!
Blue Cop is in tip-top shape.
I do feel as great as ever.
Mega Trucker, you have a worn out tamper in your knee.
Wait, what?
How can you tell?
Because... after ten years in this job, I can tell a lot just from the sound of things.
What do you mean? I need fixing? No way!
Edo's the best mechanic. You can trust him. Er, well he's not that bad...
Hey, I heard that, Jun.
Jun! Mr. Edo!
Quick, transform!
Aah, what a surprise! What brings you here, Anna?
It's an emergency! Theo has been kidnapped by the black ambulance!
What?
You're the new kid, right?
So... uh, what's your name?
Theo!
Oh, Theo! Hi!
My name's Jun. Come play with us!
But, no... I'm not good at sports...
Don't worry! No one starts out being good at something!
You're awake now?
Sorry about that.
My tire slipped off earlier.
A-are you a talking ambulance?
Oh, dear me. I'm sorry.
My name is Mega Ambler.
I'm a Metal Cardbot that looked after patients on Machina planet.
Ma-chi-na Me-tal Card-bot?
Huh?
I saw it with my very own eyes!
The police car turned into a robot!
Could this be...
A black ambulance?
It just sounds like a legend to me!
I saw it with my very own eyes!
Hey, it's Theo...
Huh?! Metal Cardbot!?
What is it? Let me see!
Hey hey! This is private!
You should respect his privacy, Anna!
Don't worry, he was just wondering what I was doing...
Why don't you tell me more about the ambulance over here...
Blue Cop!
I knew I could count on Theo. He even sent a map!
So, your friend is over there... right?
Hang in there, Theo...
Jun...
Now, let me have a look at you.
Look... at me...?
Just lie down and stay still.
Hm. The bone seems fine.
Alright, then.
Operation complete.
Now, wrapping it up...
What's going on right now?!
Help me, Jun!
I told you to stay still!
Theo! Are you okay?!
Jun! Get me out of here!
What?
Mega Ambler! Step away from that child!
The police car just t-talked?
Are you also a Metal Cardbot?
What should we do?
Don't you worry about Theo!
Alright.
Are there more robots?
Who are you, then?
Don't you know each other?
Mega Ambler is a notorious travelling doctor.
He goes around treating people without a license,
and charging them exorbitant fees.
But you can't deny I've got skill!
Blue Cop!
Looks like you need me again.
Mega Trucker?
Don't waste time, just give the command!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
You stay there!
A-another one?
Theo, you gotta run!
Oh, g-got it!
A new patient?
Mega Trucker,
Mega Power Tackle!
Haha, that's not going to work on me!
Now, how did you like that? Mega Trucker power!
That was some power for sure...
...however,
I found your weak spot!
Mega Trucker, watch out!
Huh?
What's going on here...?
You didn't fix yourself properly.
I think you should have listened to Edo...
Are you alright?
Yes. And I am ready to fight!
Got it. Mega Trucker, take back!
H-hold on!
Don't push yourself.
Blue Cop, setup!
Hm?
Broke out of your bandages, I see.
Stop trying to scan me.
I have no weak spots, unlike a certain someone.
Hey, I can hear you!
Looks like it.
But a weak spot can easily be made!
That's not what a doctor does!
Blue Cop, Burst Shot!
Burst... Shot!
Forceps Shock!
What's wrong? Should I have a look?
Nothing to see here.
Oh no...
This is bad...
Aah! Is your arm alright?
I'll take care of your other arm too!
Blue Cop, watch out!
Blue Cop, can you move your shoulder?
Yeah, I think it's okay.
Alright! I just had an idea.
They caught me off guard...
What's happening?
So I just do this?
Just trust me!
I'll make sure you can't move at all!
Now! Megavolt Punch!
Mega...volt...
Punch!!
That's it!
Metal Cardbot... Chain Shot!
Mega Ambler... seal!
Is your arm alright?
I think I'll need a little help from Edo.
Yes.
Theo! Are you okay?
Blue Cop... I can tell Theo, right? He's my best friend...
Of course. If he's your friend.
Theo! There's something you need to know.
How is it?
I couldn't be better!
And Blue Cop?
As good as new.
We have this one all cleaned up, too.
I think it's finally ready now.
Theo. I have a favor to ask.
Hey, don't worry! I won't tell anyone about the Metal Cardbots. I promise!
I'm sorry I startled you earlier.
Let's be friends from now on.
Sure, let's be friends, Mega Ambler!
Oy! That hurt!
Oops! I'm sorry!