Blue Cop's Special Training!
Blue Cop!
How about you abandon this pile of scrap metal,
and form a new team with me, Jun?
Alright! Heeheehee!
W-Wait!
Jun!
Please! Don't go without me!
Jun!!
What was that?
I'm not going anywhere.
You even had a nightmare...
the defeat must have come as a shock.
Come on, Blue Cop!
You just have to show what you've got next time!
With what I've got... you know I can't beat Wild Guardy.
Don't doubt yourself like that!
Just work harder to become stronger!
Become stronger?
So it's time for the special training?
Special training?
Yes. Just leave it all to me.
Yes, sir.
A special training for Blue Cop?
Yeah. Uncle Edo said that he's going to find a new place and that he's going to make new equipment for the special training.
Really? Wow! I want to see that.
I heard it will be ready today. Should I ask?
Blue Cop!
Jun.
Is the special training ready?
Yeah.
It's almost done. We'll start the training soon.
Alright! Keep it up! I'll be there soon.
What are you guys so excited about?
Waaah!!
U-Uh, it's nothing...
...hey guys...
Jun, did you forget Crest invited us to his house today?
Aha... I kinda did...
You don't mean to say you're not coming, are you?
Actually, I do have something, uh...
Thought you're all busy, huh?
If it's not urgent, why don't you just drop by?
You said you wanted to try out the latest VR game.
Uh... shall I...
Hm? Of course, come on.
Let's go.
Woah...
It's so huge!
Please come in, master.
You have a robot at home?!
His name is Sebastian.
Pleasure to meet you all.
He's an all-rounder robot. Does the chores, security... you name it.
And your parents?
They're often overseas for work.
So, Crest... you live here by yourself?
Well, yeah... but I'm not actually lonely.
I've made so many cool friends around here.
T-that's so great, then!
Ah!
This is the last one.
Alright, we're finally ready now!
Huh? What are you going to do with these sticks?
You'll find out soon.
Blue Cop! To the center, please!
Yes, sir!
Huh?
Shall I be here?
Yep.
Alright, then...
Woah...
This training is for dodging enemy attacks and striking back.
It applies a virtual hologram game.
It's synced to your neural network, so it will hurt if you get hit. Got it?
Alright, are you ready?
Of course.
Here we go!
That looks like it hurts.
The effects are stronger than expected.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let's go again!
Not a chance, mister!
Haha! Well done, Vance! Yeah!
Theo, you can do it!
Haha, you'll never beat me!
Jun, want to have a go?
Alright!
I will help Theo take revenge!
Not this... not this...
Aha! I'll choose you.
Will this training even work for us mechanical lifeforms?
I dunno. Looks like a waste of time.
It is not a waste of time! Hard work and perseverance always pays off!
Again!
Haha! No matter how many times you play, I'll still win!
That was just a practice game! I'll beat you, somehow!
Alright! I'll take you until you give up!
Ugh. What are they getting so worked up over?
At least they're having fun.
Be prepared!
Again!
Grr... Again!
No more. You take a rest.
I'll show you how it's done!
Alright.
Alright, let's go!
It didn't hurt!
Come on!
Doesn't seem like an accident!
Haha! He's running into the hits! That's got to be some kind of talent!
Calculate the course and speed of the attack.
And then, respond a little before it lands.
H-hey! Wait up! Augh...
Ugh. That didn't help at all.
No. I think I've got it.
Edo! Let's try one more time.
Attack pattern?
Mhm. Each robot character has its own attack pattern and timing.
Figure that out and you might be able to beat Vance.
Hmph. You couldn't beat me even if you tried it, loser!
I see. Thanks.
Again!
It's working!
I will never give up!
Well done! Just do as I showed you!
I think the trick is not to do as you did.
Seems like Blue Cop's response speed has picked up!
Seems like his seeing the projectiles and moving preemptively.
Hey! Why aren't the hits landing?!
Grr... so that's how you're playing it!
Maybe I should...
Huh? Hey...
Why are you getting bigger?!
This is the most advanced skill!
Never!
Never ever!
Give up!
Huh?
What...
Is this...
Jun!
Blue Cop!
Infinite...
Force...
Blade!!
Aw, come on!
What was that about?! It was just dumb luck!
Hey Jun. Could you give me that bracelet?
Augh?!
Of course I'm not asking just to take it.
I'll give you anything you want in this room.
Shall we do a trade?
For real?
I'd be taking this TV!
How about this robot?
W-what are you talking about?
Maybe it's something important to Jun.
It's up to Jun to decide if he wants to trade.
So... what would you like to have?
Uhh...
Sorry! I have to go now!
T-Thanks for the game!
So... he just ran away...
Blue Cop!
Jun!
I got it now! When our hearts join as one, we become stronger!
So it's true. The voice from before... it was you.
It seems like the Metal Breath still holds many secrets that we have to discover.
Hm.
So when you share your feelings, the power of the card grows...
and new skills are unleashed.
Then... we could also power up like Blue Cop!
Alright! Let's start training together!
It could be Wild Guardy or Heavy Iron... we could beat them all!
Let's do it, guys!
But... where's Uncle Edo?
My storage room...!
I really thought I had him where I wanted.
But I didn't manage to get the Metal Breath.
I'm sorry, Wild Guardy.
You don't have to apologize.
The Metal Breath will be mine after I win the next battle.