Buster Gallon, the Betrayer
That Buffalo Crush!
He told us to leave it to him, and look what happens!
He gets sealed and that's the end of it!
You were just watching him get sealed. Who are you to talk?
Shut up!
I guess... it's really sad to lose a man from our force.
Our plan was to rule the world with the Metal Breath in our hands.
Buster... Gallon... what are you doing?!
Oh, you mean this?
This is a device to momentarily pause the function of the Metal Cardbots.
But I think I'll just take the Metal Breath for myself.
How dare you! You betrayed me!
That's how a pirate really works.
Farewell... Captain.
Buster Gallon!!
Could you put that down here, please?
What are you guys making?
A shelter!
A shelter? You mean... for evacuating?
Captain Black Hook's rule is to never lose a target he sets his eye on!
We have to build up our defences to keep the treasure of planet Machina safe!
But... don't you think it's a misunderstanding?
A Metal Cardbot can't use the Metal Breath, you know.
Yes.
If we could use the Metal Breath... I would have sealed the Cardbots myself.
So... you mean, even if Black Hook takes the Metal Breath...
...he couldn't possibly make a Metal Cardbot army?
Wouldn't explaining all of this to Black Hook make him give up?
Listen. That's not a great idea.
Why?
The three of us have been trying to take the Metal Breath carefully.
If he learns that he cannot use it, he might try to destroy it with all his might.
That won't do!
What do you say we attack him first?
Yeah, that's a good idea! You might have heard the best defensive is an offensive!
Hey, Buffalo Crush!
Huh? What?
You know where Black Hook's hideout is!
Please tell us where we can find it!
Yeah, tell us now, Buffalo Crush!
I can't tell you that! I gotta go!
What are you doing?!
Blue Cop, after him!
Alright.
Jun!
Mom.
Hello, guys.
Uh... Hello...
The car that just left... wasn't that our Buffy?
Our Buffy? You mean Buffalo Crush?
Yes. I have something for him.
Will you pass it on?
For him? What is it?
It's just a gift I made for him myself.
What are you doing here, Buffalo Crush?
Jun...
This is... a doll that Mom made specially for you.
A doll she knitted herself!
Thank you... but I can't.
I'm sorry, what?
Black Hook is the first friend I found before I came to Earth.
I cannot betray him.
We aren't asking you to do anything.
My Mom made this doll out of love for you!
So I really hope you will accept it!
Love... for me?
Transform into a car! I'll put it on for you!
Does this look good?
Yeah! It looks great on you!
Huh? What was that?
There's been an explosion in a warehouse in the port area.
It's on the news right now.
What?
Is this it?
-but the warehouse hasn't been used in a while. And that hasn't been anyone seen in the vicinity. The police...
Huh?! That was our hideout!
Really? It is close from here!
Maybe something happened to the Captain!
Hey! Don't leave me behind!
Blue Cop! The exploded warehouse is Black Hook's hideout!
What?
I am on my way. See you there!
Let's go. All together!
Yes!
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Where are you, Captain?!
Hey, hey, look!
It must be that... robot!
I got it on film!
Jun. I will be arriving soon with Shadow X.
Yes. We have to drive out that helicopter!
Leave it to me!
Watch out!
I'm sorry!
Hey, what are you doing?!
This is not safe. Please keep your distance.
Jun! We did it!
Huh?!
Aah!
Come back, both of you!
Are you okay?
My engine has been hit.
...my propeller.
To think that you came to me holding the Metal Breath.
You've made things easier for me.
What's happened here?! Buster Gallon! Where's our captain?!
It seemed to me that it would take too long to get the Metal Breath in our hands with him in the way.
So... I took care of things.
What?!
Now, Buffalo Crush! It's your turn!
Buffalo Crush!
I... can't... move...
Jun! Are you alright?
Don't come here!
Buster Gallon!
I have more customers.
What happened here?!
Just stand aside and watch!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Shoulder Shield!
Twin Blaster! (FIX_THIS)
Mega Ambler! Please! See what happened to Blue Cop!
A powerful magnetic field is blocking the Metal Cardbot's movements.
Found it! The magnetic field is coming from there!
If you value your friends' lives, hand over the Metal Breath!
It's a bomb!
Everyone, please come back!
Huh?! What is this...
It's no use. All of your functions stop working when caught in the magnetic field.
How devious of him...
We did so much research...
Of course. Black Hook believed the Metal Breath was a treasure of Machina planet.
But I'm different!
That object is nothing more than a system constructed by Deus Machina, the mother computer.
Even if it's locked so that Metal Cardbots can't use it, there is a way if you put in the time.
Now. Hand over the Metal Breath!
I will gather the Metal Cardbots around the universe
to construct an empire across the galaxy!
...y-you're out of your mind, Buster Gallon...
I'll tell you three important things!
Who, me?
What do you want to tell me?
One!
In my experience, a talkative villain always lets down his guard and loses!
What do you mean, let down my guard?! Your fate is in my hands!
Two! I still have eight friends left in my team!
Eight? Huh. There were two taken back just now...
Huh?! One is missing!
I found the magnetic field emitting device!
Oh no!
When did you...
I'm free!
And three!
We are connected to Jun in spirit!
We don't need commands!
We know what we need to do.
Try to block me, then!
You can't do that!
Phoenix Fire, setup!
Strike!
Then how about this?!
Wild Guardy, setup!
What's this?!
Jun!
Hey! Guys!
This is a freeze grenade. My invention.
A genius like me always has a backup!
Now... what do you do with the Metal Breath?
Hold... on...!
Oh, dear... Buffalo Crush... you should learn when to give up.
Inside me is the warmth of a human that knows love!
As long as his love remains warm, my engine will never...
...freeze up!
Awesome! It's our turn!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Buffalo Crush, setup!
Buffalo Fission! (FIX_THIS)
Buffalo Fission!
Let's get him! Buffalo Moonsault!
Buffalo...
Moonsault!
Yaah!
Buster Blaster!
Metal Cardbot, change up!
Buster Gallon, seal up!
You are a friend of ours now!
Finally...
I'm so sick of being unable to move!
Looks like the freeze didn't last too long.
That's great!
You did it. Jun.
It was all thanks to Buffalo Crush!
Incredible job.
You saved us all.
Thank you.
We've won... but where's the Captain?
What's that?!
Is that an earthquake?!
You're alive...
Buster Gallon's puny little bomb can't do anything to me!
Captain!
Buffalo Crush. You're still calling me Captain?!
Yes...
You fool!
That's just too much.
And you, Earthling child!
I will take the Metal Breath from you one day!
You better mark my words!
A pirate always delivers!
You will never get it your way, you hear me?!
The Captain hit me...