Goodbye, Buffalo Crush!
What's the speed of a car that took 8 hours to travel 283 miles?
35 miles per hour.
Hehehe...
How far does a plane flying at 211 miles per second fly over seven seconds?
1,478 miles.
Hehehe...
Homework done!
Jun. It's no use knowing the answers if you don't know how to solve the problems.
But you know time is gold!
I'd really like to save time on doing homework so I can read more!
But... that's a comic book.
A comic book is a book!
You're right.
Tell me. Would you like to read some of my comics?
Aagh!
Dad! I always tell you to knock!
I did.
But... who are you talking to?
Uh, haha... I was just talking to myself.
Talking to yourself means that you are under a lot of stress.
You should know Milky Way will be closed tomorrow.
Would you like to go on a trip?
Yahoo! Awesome!
It feels like things are not working out!
Don't you have some brilliant plan to take the treasure of Machina planet?!
We already know where it is...
So why not a surprise attack?!
Surprise attack?!
Yes! Or we can take the child's family as hostage!
All we want is the treasure.
We shall not get other humans involved!
Hahaha! I see you have some loyalty in you!
If you have a better idea, why not say it, Buffalo Crush?
Leave it to me!
Where are you going now?!
Leave him!
A pirate always stays true to his word!
Yes. And... I must not cause her any harm.
Ugh... what is so fun about going on a trip?
Shh! Be quiet!
I could be there much faster than a car!
Shhh!
Talking to yourself again?
Ahahaha! It's nothing!
He's starting to take after you...
Me?
You always do that when you're driving, haven't you noticed?
Ha, do I really?
What's the hurry?! You gotta go to the bathroom?! Why didn't you go earlier?! You're a terrible driver! What if something had happened?! So irresponsible!
Uh... excuse me?
Ooh, what a strange car!
Do you need something from them?
Uh, yeah...
I know they're not home today.
They were all going on a trip to the Itar Plateau.
Itar... Plateau?
Thank you.
Itar Plateau, Itar Plateau...
Your call is not connecting. Try again later.
Ugh! I'm bored!
If I knew, I would've stayed at home!
Jun.
Yeah?
Don't you have... something to tell me?
Uh... something to tell you, like...
Maybe something like any worries or secrets you have.
I would really... like to hear from you, Jun.
Uhh... haha...
Dad! I don't have any secrets...
Jun. Do you think we've been discovered?
No, I hope not...
I'll use the restroom first. You guys go ahead.
Okay!
Woah! Haha!
How's this? Pretty impressive, right?
Yeah!
I used to have worries at your age, too.
When I couldn't work things out,
I would turn to nature to forget about them all.
Where is this conversation going?
You're 12 and there are things you don't want to tell us.
But it's not right to tell lies. That would make us sad.
Uh... I never lied to you! C'mon, Dad!
Wait a second.
Hello? Theo?
Jun! Bad news!
Buffalo Crush was at your place!
What?! Again?!
I think he's headed to where you are!
Huh? What's wrong?
Huh? Huh!
Hey, Jun!
Mom!
Jun!
Found them! Haa!
Huh?
Please return the treasure of Machina planet.
You are... what treasure?
Your son has the treasure. Please help us!
Lady Yuri, I owe my life to you.
I don't want you to get hurt over this!
Mom!
Darling, what's going on?!
Well done, Buffalo Crush!
Black Hook!
Now. Please take off the Metal Breath!
Jun. Summon me now!
No! I can't do it!
You guys will be discovered!
Kid. I'll give you to the count of three.
Hand over the treasure of Machina planet!
One.
What do I do? I can't summon them with my parents watching. They'll find out everything!
Two...
I don't have a choice!
Three!
No!
Buffalo Crush...
I told you to leave this to me!
Do promises truly mean nothing to pirates?
If only we can get the Metal Breath, such promises aren't worth it.
Jun!
Dad! Mom! I'm sorry! I'll explain later!
Jun! What are you doing?!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Shadow X, setup!
Haaa haa!
Please excuse us!
Oh my, he summoned a robot!
Did you see that?!
Shadow X, take him out with Heli-Tornado!
Okay!
Heli-Tornado!
Quickly! Lower the sails!
A sneak attack, I see!
You will pay for this!
Stop it!
I'll repeat once again.
You must leave it to me!
Try and see how that works out, then.
Hurry up and take the Metal Breath!
Let's go, Buster Gallon.
Huh?!
What is this?! Hold on, Black Hook!
Call me Captain! Captain Black Hook!
T-Thank you, Buffalo Crush...
The Metal Breath...
is a treasure from Machina Planet.
You have no right to be holding it!
That's not true.
Huh? Blue Cop!
Jun is qualified to have it.
So... I have given the Metal Breath from Deus Machina to Jun.
Qualified? What do you mean, huh?!
The fact that Jun has the Metal Breath... is the proof.
I don't know what it is... but it seems other people can't hear this.
...I don't believe this...
Then try to fight him!
What?
Try to fight him! And you'll find out how strong Jun is!
I don't like violence...
but I'm ready to prove my friendship with the Metal Cardbots!
Alright...
Let's go!
It's dangerous here. Please come with me.
We'll stay by Jun's side.
We won't, we're his parents!
Now, this way please!
Listen! I need you to be somewhere safe.
Mega Trucker, setup!
Mega Trucker, Mega Power Tackle!
Finally! It's my turn!
Amazing! This is a battle of brute force!
Who are you calling brute?!
Not so fast!
Beam Omission! (FIX_THIS)
A laser beam attack?! That's a foul play!
What is that green thing?
Isn't that...
Aah! Looks like his hole isn't better yet!
Alright, thank you Mom!
Mega Trucker, Mega Touchdown!
Mega Touchdown!
Let's finish this!
Dexter, setup!
Dexter, into the ground!
I'm so... hungry...
Dexter, attack the Milky Way!
Spiral Ray!
Metal Cardbot, Change Up!
Buffalo Crush... seal up!
So I guess I've proven myself.
Woohoo! A new subordinate!
Hey, we don't work that way, Shadow X!
Huh?
Are we really just leaving?!
He told us to leave it to him!
A pirate does not go back on his word!
Goodbye, Buffalo Crush!
Are you actually crying?
Shut up!
Mom, Dad...
I'm sorry I've been hiding it from you guys!
You don't have to be sorry.
Jun, we have known about the Metaca... I mean, the Metal Cardbots all along.
That's no surprise.
Duh???
You've been coming home late, your most treasured bike all smashed up...
It was all just too strange.
So we confronted Edo. And then asked him to tell us everything he knew!
So... he had to tell us everything that happened.
Uh, there is a robot from Machina planet called Blue Cop! (FIX_THIS)
We see through everything, your mom and dad.
Not just that... we also know what you're hiding.
Uh...
So... you mean... you mean that...
Don't you have something to tell me?
Maybe something like any worries or secrets you may have?
Was this what you were talking about in the car?!
Your scores are really bad.
But what's worse is hiding them from us.
That makes me really sad.
I-I'm really sorry, Mom and Dad!