The Hungry Metal Cardbot
Hm? Has there been an accident?
Hello?
Are you alright?
H-Hello?
I... I'm hungry!
Aah!
We have a report that a monster truck transformed into a robot
and ate a battery from an electric car that was passing by on Route 66 last night.
I-I mean, a garish looking car suddenly started saying it was hungry, and it transformed into...
Mmph? Could this be?
Yes. I'm sure it's a Metal Cardbot.
Jun!
You're gonna be late for school again!
Uh, yes!
I'll be off, then!
Do you know where it happened, Jun?
Yes! A country road outside Mowtown-
What are you saying?
Hahaha, what's got you all jumpy, huh?
Uh... Dad, what are you doing below the car?
Well, the car is acting a little strange.
I think it's broken somewhere. But I just can't figure out...
...well, I'll be going off to school then!
I had a great stay thanks to all of you.
Thank you so much!
Crest!!
I'll never forget the fun times we had!
We're friends for life-
Oh no, Crest!
I can't believe you're leaving us, Crest!
Oh, you mustn't forget me no matter what!
Haha, thank you...
He's a big star from start to end.
You said it!
Hope things will be fine until the farewell party tonight.
The news this morning didn't sound good...
Everybody's looking for the culprit now, so we'll find out soon enough- huh?
Did you find anything?
I found traces of oil spilled by a Metal Cardbot.
It might be from the culprit.
Do you mean the culprit was hurt?
I'm not sure.
But it looks like he went downtown.
Okay, I leave you to it then.
You can count on me.
What timing for the car to break on the day of the party...
I asked  for a replacement vehicle, so it should be alright.
Well, I'll be off then!
Take care, honey!
Ugh... time to prepare for the party...
Ugh... how odd... I just ate... but I'm hungry again...
I wonder... why that is...
Ah! Oh...
Wha? What's that?!
Uh... uh...
When did that arrive now?
Hello? Oh, Edo!
About the car. It seems like the tank is rusty.
It seems it's going to take about a week to fix.
What? I'm going to be driving around in that garish looking truck for a week?!
What garish looking truck? I haven't sent the replacement vehicle yet.
But there's... one right here- Huh?
What?
Uh, Edo... I'm sorry. Forget about what I just said. I must have made a mistake.
So... you said the repair would take a week? I'll wait for the replacement vehicle then.
Please send a normal car.
Please send a normal car...
I... I can't hold it any longer! Aagh!
Oh, in an hour? Don't worry, I'll be here. Alright...
I'm really hungry!!
Hello? Hello? Are you there, Yuri?
A garish looking car suddenly started saying it was hungry!
Then it transformed into a robot and attacked my car! I was so scared!
Huh... wait a minute!
I found the trail of oil! It goes to the residential area!
That is where Jun's house is...
Let's hurry!
H-Hey! Hang on!
Wait for us!
I'm so... hungry...
I... wanna eat... that...
You want to eat... this generator?
Gimme!
Then you need to ask nicely!
I said no!
And your hands are all dirty!
Hang on.
There you go.
Now. You have to say "thank you" before eating.
Say, "thanks for the food".
Sorry. Thanks for the food, lady.
Hmph.
So good...
Oh yeah. Good job.
See you in the evening, Anna.
Yeah, see you later!
Take care!
Jun.
Blue Cop! Did you find him?
We found that the trail of oil is heading to your neighborhood.
What?!
Jun! Jun!
Get in. Something has happened at your house!
Wha?! No way!
Uh... what's wrong...?
I'm still hungry.
Oh.
Is there a problem with the voltage?
Hm...
Hang on. Excuse me.
Oh dear. There's a hole in there from a nail.
This must be the problem.
Stick your bottom out.
Like this?
That's right.
Oh, you poor thing...
Hang in there.
There you go!
T-Thank you, lady!
Don't mention it.
But, who are you, anyway?
I am... Buffalo Crush.
I'm Yuri. Finish your meal.
Thanks.
He's in our yard?!
Hey, hot pink! What are you doing in my house?!
Mom?!
Let my mom go right now!
Huh?
That's the treasure from Deus Machina. The Metal Breath!
Hey! Give me that!
So this is why you're taking my mom hostage, huh?!
Hostage? What do you mean?
Stop it.
Say "I'm done, thank you" if you're done eating.
Huh?! I'm done, thank you lady.
Jun.
Wild Guardy and I will soon be at your place.
I'm in my house right now. Please hurry.
What? Okay.
Uh... I have something to discuss with you about the repairs.
What? But I have to prepare for the party...
That's Edo's car!
Jun! Are you alright?
Blue Cop! Wild Guardy!
Buffalo Crush? Why are you here?
Give me the Metal Breath!
What?!
Blue Cop, setup!
Wild Guardy!
He's way too strong!
Buffalo Crush has been fed!
That means I'm... unbeatable!
Mega Trucker! Where are you?!
Ugh.
Come on, move already!
We must not let him overpower us with brute force!
Let's confuse him with serial attacks!
Got it!
Wild Guardy, setup!
Bring it on!
That shield is nothing.
Tomahawk Crush!
Gotcha! Sorry, pal.
The time is now. Megavolt Punch!
Megavolt...
Buffalo...
Moonsault!
He's as hard to break as my shield...
Blue Cop! Let's finish with Infinity Force Break!
Got it!
Infinity...
Force...
Who's that?!
Where are you roaming about, Buffalo Crush?
That sounded like...
Buster Gallon.
W-Who's that?!
Black Hook's crewmate.
I am here for the Metal Breath like I promised, Earthling child.
I never invited you to my house!
And you're never getting the Metal Breath!
If you want to turn this place into a battlefield, I have nothing to lose!
Let's just go back.
I'm sorry, what are you saying?
Black Hook. You said this before.
A real Cardbot always repays a favor.
Our restaurant sticker?
I guess... if you have a good reason...
Fools. It was the chance of a lifetime.
We're heading west. Let's go!
I don't understand what's going on here...
I followed the trail of oil and found an escape pod in the forest.
Perhaps... it was damaged during the escape?
So... Jun's mom fixed the leak!
She must have been shocked!
So it's all thanks to your mom that we're having this great party.
But Crest...
Now that there are all these new enemies, I'm a little bit worried.
I truly believe you will defeat them all.
I think so too!
We'll be fine as long as we work together!
Promise you will be back, Crest!
Mhm. Of course!