Anna's Metal Breath
Looks like you're still coughing, I see.
Could it be a cold?
A cold?
Do Metal Cardbots catch colds too?
Could it be a gremlin?
A gremlin?!
It's a goblin that lived on Machina planet.
It could make the Cardbots' engines unable to stop, or make their brakes not work properly.
So that's what catching a cold means to you.
It's all a myth! I've never even seen a gremlin!
It's just we know you have a bad temper!
Want to see that temper in action?!
Achoo!
...it's getting cold... let's head back, guys...
You seem a little different today.
Who, m...me? I'm the same as ever...
Everyone... take back...!
Mr. Edo... please take care of Fleta Z's engine...
I'm sorry, but planes are not my specialty.
Oh, come on, Mr. Edo! I know you can do it!
We know you're the best mechanic ever!
We trust you!
Haha... I'll try to do my best...
...ugh.
What? A flu?
Is Jun alright?
Jun's parents called to say he's sick.
It's the first time he's skipped school for a flu, isn't it?
He seemed fine yesterday...
Could it be...
A gremlin's prank?!
Why did you eat ice pops before sleeping?
With your window opened and your tummy exposed to the cold?
Now look at you...
His throat is so sore, he can't talk...
Oh, dear me...
The doctor said it's just a common cold. He'll be better after a day of rest and sleep.
Jun... get well soon...
Huh.
This is a great opportunity!
The Metal Breath may well already be in our hands!
But... it's bad luck to get in the way of a gremlin's trick.
Wait... do you really believe in such a myth?
It is the fool who doesn't believe.
Want to lecture on who is the fool? Really?
No need. We can all see that you are!
Hey, hey! It doesn't matter if gremlins exist or not!
It would be a disgrace to lose the treasure in front of our eyes!
We shall set sail, Black Crew!
...not that way, though.
...looks like Captain's the fool.
Be quiet!
Uh... Theo...
Do you think this might actually be dangerous?
What is?
If Jun can't talk, that means... he can't use the Metal Breath to...
Right! He can't summon the Cardbots!
Let's go!
Hey, wait for me, Anna!
Jun has a flu?
Help us, Fleta Z! You're the only one that can protect Jun!
Of course I'll help.
Really?!
Fleta Z. But your engine is still choking out...
Still... I cannot turn down a beautiful lady like Anna, who needs my help.
What they're after is Jun's Metal Breath!
I have an idea.
What are you going to do?
We're about to arrive. Be prepared!
Who are you, little lady?!
Who are we?
The sonic speed hero, Fleta Z!
Guardian of peace, Anna!
Together we are...
Z and Anna!
Robbers with their eye on our treasure?
We will send you...
Back to space!!
Wohohoho...
We're not interested in you!
All we want is the Metal Breath!
Out of my way!
Really? the Metal Breath?
You mean this thing?
No way!
H-How do you have the treasure from Deus Machina?!
If you thought Jun was the only one that could use the Metal Breath,
you're totally wrong!
How weird. I don't smell anything of Deus Machina in that child.
Impossible!
Uh... yeah! Is your nose blocked or something?
What?! You have a cold?!
Me?! Get a cold?! Never!
Anna! We need to get them away from Jun's house!
Right, of course!
Fleta Z, fly!
Let's go!
Stop them!
Just fire, Buster Gallon!
I know!
Are you okay?
Y-yeah, don't worry-
Hang on tight!
Are you alright, Anna?!
I-I told you n-not to worry!
Yeah, but you're not saying you're okay...
Fleta Z? What's going on?
Don't worry. It's nothing.
J- Aaah!
Fleta Z! Where are you?!
You little rat!
You won't get away.
Fire...
Chest Cannon!
Is that a homing cannon?
Anna. Hang on!
Aaaah!
Huh? Look at that, the child is falling!
He abandoned his master!
Now's our chance, Black Hook!
I said call me captain!
Oh no...
I don't think I can stay in the sky. I'll get back to land.
Waaah!
It sounds like they are in battle.
It must be Black Hook's gang!
So... he's fighting the three of them by himself?
What can we do? We can't help in our current state!
Woah!
Jun. Are you awake?
Uh huh...
We're safe now.
I... Fleta Z... thank you...
S-sorry... are you alright now?
Over there!
How did I get hit by my own Chest Cannon...
Not too bad! I underestimated you!
You won't get away this time!
Now. Hand over the Metal Breath immediately.
This is bad.
Don't dilly dally about! Just send it over!
Aah! Fleta Z, sit down!
That was close!
I'm sorry...
Buster Blaster!
Uhh... roll away!
Oh no...
Z and Anna Punch!
Z and Anna... Punch!!
Jun! I came home early today! Are you feeling better?
Huh? Jun?
Yes! We did it!
What a disgrace...
How odd... why doesn't he use his bow?
How do you like the power of Z and Anna-
Oh...!
Uhh...
The Metal Breath...
Huh?!
It's a fake!
You brat tricked us!
Insolent little lady! You will not be forgiven!
Oh no! Anna! Watch out!
Captain's Cannon! Fire!
Anna... are you alright?
I... can't anymore...
You will pay for playing foolish games with the Black Crew!
Yeah! You will!
And with interest!
Get ready!
Spinning Cutter!
What?
Haha! Sorry I'm late!
Jun!
That little brat!
So is that the real Metal Breath?!
But he can't even talk with the flu! How was he summoned?!
Jun and I are connected in spirit. We don't need to talk.
That's ridiculous.
Whatever it is!
They are here and we have one thing to do!
Take the Metal Breath now!
Aah, whatever!
P-Phoenix Fire... setup...
B...Burning... Hammer...
Burning... Hammer!!
Buffalo Moonsault!
Forceps Shock...
Forceps Shock!
How is that... possible?!
I know! That's also a trick!
Fleta Z!
I'm okay now. Please try to hear Jun's voice too!
Jun's voice...?
Ah! Yeah!
Jun! We're also ready!
Fleta Z!
The two of us will end the battle with Vulture Wings!
Yes!
Black Hook!
Vulture Wings!
Vulture... Wings!
Captain's Cannon!!
You will pay for this!
The Black Crew will never give up!
Just give up already!
Jun! Are you okay?!
Oh, Jun...
T-Thanks, Anna... Fleta Z...
It's my duty to protect you, Jun.
No, thank you for saving us!
You're burning up! Let's get you home!
I... can't anymore!
Jun! Please wake up!!