Showdown Between Blue Cop and Wild Guardy!
You ready for this?
Just go ahead and shoot!
Woah!
Here it comes!
Wow!
Thank you, thank you.
Those are amazing skills.
Never misses a shot.
He's a hunter in the wild who never ever misses a mark!
Fleta Z, welcome to the team!
Once again, thank you for joining us!
Thank you for having me, Jun.
Huh?
What's with Mega Trucker's head?
Aah!
I am terribly sorry about this.
It's fine. It's nothing, really.
Crest?
Just as I thought. You're all here.
What brings you guys here?
Hm. I see it's been sealed.
I have kept my promise!
It's your turn to tell me what I want to know.
What is it?
Tell me everything about you and Wild Guardy! I wanna know everything!
I would like to know too.
Alright. Where should we begin?
How about when you used to be a Star Guardian of Machina planet?
Star Guardian...?
What is that?
An elite force was selected to guard Deus Machina, the modern computer of Machina planet.
Blue Cop... was the best Metal Cardbot of them all.
I vowed to become a great Star Guardian just like Blue Cop.
However,
My dream was crushed when Machina planet was destroyed.
I just managed to escape and was lost in the vastness of outer space.
After a long period of wandering, Wild Guardy crashed onto Earth.
Crashed?
Did your escape pod malfunction?
We don't know.
He was in a terrible state when I found him.
Master! This looks like...
Sebastian. Turn the car around. Let's take him to the villa.
Uh- yes, Master!
Fortunately, the villa was equipped with everything we needed for repairs,
because my dad is the CEO of a car company, and my mom a doctor of robot engineering.
We didn't even share a language then.
But we shared a genuine connection.
So this... is planet Earth?
Yeah. It is where I was born and raised.
So... what's your name?
It's Wild Guardy... in your language.
I'm Crest.
Let's be friends.
So... Crest is the one who saved you, Wild Guardy?
Yes. He is also a precious friend that I found on this planet.
A friend?
Then we saw on the news that mysterious robots have been showing up in Mowtown.
We knew right away.
They had to be Metal Cardbots from Machina planet, just like Wild Guardy.
So, Crest... the reason you transferred here was...
That's right. It was to find out who you guys were.
Although Machina planet is gone, I can still prove
that I am better than a Star Guardian if I can beat Blue Cop!
That is beyond obsessed, bro.
You are basically stalking Blue Cop here!
It might be better for you to spread your wings and fly on your own.
You simpletons have no clue about the loneliness and thoughts
of someone with the dream of becoming the best!
What?!
I will rise above the Star Guardian and become king of the Metal Cardbots!
What is this guy even going on about?!
If that's what you want...
I will give you a chance.
What?!
Huh?
Yeah! In return, you have to promise to join our team if you lose.
Sounds fun.
Take them on, Wild Guardy.
I'm sorry, what?
Crest, not you too...
But... if you lose, you have to hand over the Metal Breath. Do you accept?
Yes!
No! You mustn't, Jun.
Are you afraid, Blue Cop?
No, I just think that-
You are definitely not having this battle in my car repair shop, got it?!
I think we better move, Crest...
Yeah, actually... I know the perfect place. Follow me, please.
Alright!
Shall we begin?
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Wait, what?
That's not Blue Cop!
I said we'll take you on!
But I never said it would be a one on one battle!
If you want the Metal Breath, you will have to get past all of us first!
What?!
Don't worry about it. I'm sure you can handle them all.
No doubt about it!
Alright then! Let's begin!
Yes!
Mega Trucker, Mega Power Tackle!
No one can stop the unstoppable! Mega Trucker! Raah!
There's no need to stop you. You can't even touch me.
Next!
Mega Trucker, come back!
That didn't even take ten seconds...
Unbelievable...
Phoenix Fire, your turn!
Yes!
Speed attack! Water Splash!
Water Splash!
Stop right there!
Watch your back!
Wild Slash!
Phoenix Fire, are you alright?
He's too strong...
Jun, you need to stay strong!
I know, Edo.
Your turn, Mega Ambler!
Don't think changing players will change the outcome.
Be a little more polite, kiddo.
Crest is right. I don't want to waste my time.
Just show me what you've got.
He's sure isn't here to make friends!
Pride comes before a fall.
Jun. We are ready whenever you are.
Alright! Well it's time to get him!
Mega Ambler, Forceps Crush!
Forceps Crush!
Shadow X, Spinning Cutter!
Spinning Cutter!
Haha! Watch your head, buddy!
Dexter!
Spear Thrust!
Spear... Thrust!
Wild Slash!
Jun! Send me out there!
I always win no matter who you send!
Fleta Z, setup-
Hold on, Jun.
Blue Cop?
Send me out this time.
...are you sure?
Yes.
Don't worry, Blue Cop. I can handle it.
That's not the problem. Please. Let me, Fleta Z.
...I understand. Please go ahead.
At last you are here, Blue Cop.
Thought you'd be the finale, but I guess you'd want to fight now.
When Machina planet was destroyed, I was on my own too.
I spent ages wandering through space alone.
When I finally got to this planet, I found my kind again. I don't want them to get hurt.
Save the sob story for someone else.
Just let me defeat them!
I have pulled myself up from the jaws of death!
Working to make myself stronger!
I am the rightful Star Guardian!
Don't you see it?
What?
Blue Cop said he doesn't want his fellow Cardbots to get hurt!
And that includes you, stubborn robot!
Stop acting all high and mighty!
No way... my sword!
Blue Cop!
Let's end this, Jun!
Infinity...
Force...
Break!!
Wild Guardy!
...why...
...why can't I beat him...?
Does this mean I'm not qualified to be a Star Guardian?
That's not true, Wild Guardy.
I don't need your empty words now...!
I mean it.
Deus Machina told me, right before Machina planet collapsed,
to use the Metal Breath, to find a friend.
A friend...?
May I do it? Crest?
I made a promise.
Metal Cardbot, Change Up!
Sealing Wild Guardy!