Black Hook Strikes Back
What is this?
All of these are my inventions.
Buster Gallon, the self proclaimed genius inventor of Machina planet.
"Self proclaimed" was unnecessary...
Is this a pen?
That is a cheat pen which automatically writes the correct answers for you.
With this I could be the top of the cl-
Auckpth!
It's actually a pen that punishes those who want to use it to cheat like that.
And... what's this?
It's a brush that makes your hair beautiful with just one stroke.
Wow, really?
Look, beautiful, isn't it?
These inventions are quite useless...
But aren't they fun?
What do you mean?
What's fun about them!
To me, it's the most fun to see the looks on people's faces after they've been tricked!
Really? That's what you find "fun"?
Should we accept this trickster as our teammate?
I say no! We cannot trust him!
Have to agree.
I don't like him either.
No... he will... oh...
I'll trust him!
What?!
Jun?!
Why? He's so fun!
Also, I like to play pranks too, you know?
You're too optimistic.
I think it's too hard to trust after you've been betrayed.
However... if you keep suspecting someone like that, you can never build trust!
I trust you. Jun.
Cool!
That means you trust me that we can trust Buster Gallon, right?
What does that mean?
Anyway! Thank you once again for joining our team, Buster Gallon!
Huh?
What is this?
What's wrong?
[unintelligible]
What's going on?
What's happening?
This doesn't seem like a simple blackout.
The current dropped, but it hasn't stopped completely.
Do you think there could be a problem at the power plant?
Huh? Daddy?! Is that true?!
What is it, Anna?
A strange ship has appeared at Mowtown's electrical facility!
What?! Is it...
It's Black Hook!
Hahahaha! Give me everything!
Aah! If we let them, the entire city will come to a standstill!
Let's go! Right now!
Got it!
Black Hook...
Everyone, come back!
I'm worried... what is he planning with an attack on the electrical facilities?
Black Hook is trying to absorb all the electricity to power up!
Trying to take in all of that energy in one go is typical Black Hook!
I see he's one greedy fella...
He was already powerful before! We'll never beat him if he gets stronger!
Theo! Anna! I have an idea!
Yahaha!
I still need more! More! MORE!
Anyone who gets between me and my food will get crushed!
Huh?
What?!
Water Splash!
Let's go! Mega Ambler!
Mega Ambler, Forceps Shock!
Forceps Shock!
Stop!
We did it!
Water conducts electricity, just as Jun planned!
Augh, my car...
Not so fast, kiddo!
Guys, come back!
Ha! That little plan of yours never had a chance!
Then what about this, huh?
Fleta Z!
Fleta Z, setup!
Fleta Z, Beak Arrow!
Beak Arrow!
Not a chance!
Now, Fleta Z!
Yes!
Why isn't it coming out?!
I'm losing energy!
Have you heard of a grounding rod?!
It's a safety device that sends electricity from washing machines and fridges into the ground!
Now all your energy will be absorbed by the ground!
We did it!
That's our Jun!
All thanks to you guys!
Why, you little...
I'll share something with you!
Fleta Z, come back!
You brats are getting on my nerves!
You will be punished!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Shoulder Shield!
How long do you think you can last with that?!
He's too strong for Mega Trucker!
Yes. We all have to get together!
We're here to help!
Oh! It's been a while!
Buffalo Crush! Buster Gallon!
You're helping too, right?
I guess there's no choice.
Buffalo Crush is helping too!
After turning against me, cretins!
You sold your soul to that Earthling kiddo, and now you will strike me?!
I, Buffalo Crush, never sold my soul to anyone!
What?!
Machina planet is now gone.
We have to live on planet Earth.
You. Me. Everyone!
Shut up!
Oh no!
After spending all that energy, he can still use his lethal weapon?!
Everyone, concentrate on the shield!
Now! Hurry!
No! We don't have time!
Captain's Cannon!
Oh dear. I've never been one to lose my cool,
but I almost ended up destroying the Metal Breath!
Oh no! Everyone, are you alright?!
Now! You are the only ones who remain.
Run away, Jun!
I can't do that!
I will never leave my friends behind like that! Never!
You hear me?!
What's that light...?
Could it be? The light of the forbidden power?!
The forbidden power...?
A legendary force in Machina planet!
Too huge that it had to be sealed away!
So deep, it had been held within the Metal Breath!
Hey, kiddo!
Give it to me right now! Hand me over!
I actually don't know what that is!
But I will never give it to you-
What is he doing?!
Let me go! Drop me!
Buster Gallon... huh?!
Here it is.
It's all yours now. Captain.
He's kidding, right?!
Did he just betray us?!
Oh no...
Well done, Buster Gallon!
You know I always trusted you with my heart.
With this, the universe will be ours! Hahaha!
What did I tell you?! I said we shouldn't have taken him in!
I believe I told you.
It is my greatest joy to see your faces...
...after you've been tricked.
Yes!
This is our last chance!
Ack! What's this?!
I can't see anything!
The time is now, Buster Gallon!
Alright!
My energy!! After all this!!
Buster Gallon, setup!
Thank you for believing in me. Captain.
Buster Gallon! Twin Vulcan! (FIX_THIS)
Twin Vulcan!
Buster Blaster!
I never thought you would fool me twice!
Looks like I don't deserve to be Captain...!
Jun!
Blue Cop!
Infinity...
Force...
Break!!
That's it!
Metal Cardbot, Change Up!
Black Hook, seal up!
We did it...
We did it, Jun!
I thought we lost for a moment there...
Hey you, Buster Gallon. Who's side are you on?
What do you mean, "who's side"?
Don't you act so coy...
Were you thinking of betraying us?
I don't really know. However...
However?
Jun believed in me.
So I started thinking about believing in him too.
Buster Gallon!
Now we are officially a team!
Thank you.
No!! My arm!!
Jun! Are you alright?!
Ehehehe! I got you! Haha!
Oh, dear me... you got me this time...
Ugh... really, Jun?
You still have the energy for pranks?
Oh... what do I tell the insurance company about this?
Maybe that you made a supreme sacrifice to protect the peace of Mowtown!
That's not gonna work!
It's my dad...
Hello, Daddy!
Why are you calling me?
Anna, tell me. Where are you right now? Are you okay?
Something strange is happening at the landfill.
Look! A huge dome-shaped ore is rising from Landfill 30!
It seems large enough to cover the entire landfill!
Could this mysterious phenomenon be a simple act of nature?!
What is that...