Red Blitz's Sincerity
Gate course settings all clear.
Uhhh, engine internal pressure, all clear!
W-We're good to go, Captain.
From this moment forward, we're taking off in search of a new world.
Speranza! Full speed ahead!
Full speed ahead!
Speranza, departing!
Now, speak out loud! Speak out the words that come to your mind! (FX-mukara voice)
Blue Cop! Superior Docking!
Blue Cop Trinity! Set up! (FX-trinity)
Blue Cop! Show them your power!
Is this... The ultimate power that's been hidden inside Mukara's Metal Breath?!
H-How...
Captain?
Guys! Let's get outta here!
Give me back my Metal Breath!
Captain!
Get away from Jun!
Captain!!
Tch, stop being so cocky! All you did was grow a little taller!
Stay back, Red Blitz. This fight is mine!
Blue Cop! Show them your newfound strength!
Roger!
Star Rising Cannon!
Fire!
C-Captain!
REX! (FX-phoenixFire bold xl)
That must be-!
-That flame again!
Not a problem! Nothing can stop Blue Cop now!
INFERNO!! (FX-phoenixFire bold xxl)
Blue Cop!
Supernova Shield! (FX-xl bold blueShine)
How can this be...!
Blue Cop! Time to finish this!
Now!
Galaxies Punisher! (FX-xxl bold blueShine)
You've lost, Gigantrex.
Now surrender and be sealed!
Stop it!
Get out of the way, Red Blitz!
No! I will not stand by and watch him be sealed away!
Captain Gigantrex means too much to me...
'Cause he's my dad!
D-
Dad?!
Dad!?!
We were all crew members of the Speranza. We thought our mission was to pioneer a new planet and create a second home.
Until that day...
What just happened? How?!
Something must be wrong!
What's all the commotion?
Captain! Planet Machina just... exploded!
What?! What are you trying to say?!
I'm not making this up. I checked again and again and it's all the same. It's even disappeared from the radars!
That doesn't make sense! Check again!
I see... So the time has come.
What do you mean, Captain?
Don't tell me... you knew about this? You knew that planet Machina would explode all along?
Deus Machina informed me.
I was told that planet Machina would soon reach the end of its lifespan.
You're lying! Do you actually believe that, Captain?!
We've received an image from a survivor!
You mean...
This is all true?!
The whole pioneering thing was a lie. We came aboard the ship to escape Machina's collapse!
So what's your point?
Crest...
Of all the planets in this vast universe, why did you come to Earth? To make Earth into your new home?
No!
Red Blitz, that's enough.
No! I'll say it!
The one who crash-landed the Speranza on Earth...
was me!
Boy! What are you doing!?
I'm going back to planet Machina!
What kind of nonsense are you going on about, Red Blitz?!
Our planet is long gone!
I'll go back in time! And stop planet Machina...
...from exploding!
Stop this foolishness!
The Speranza then came crashing down to Earth, all because I was being reckless.
You mean the giants from the sea of stars went back in time to Earth as it was 4,000 years ago?
That's impossible! Einstein's Theory of Special Relativity says that the speed of light can't be surpassed!
But with the technology of planet Machina, it's not so far-fetched.
I don't really know what you're talking about, but... come live on Earth with us!
What?
You said that your spaceship sank into the ocean. Then we just have to salvage and fix it, right?
Not this again...
You're being too optimistic...
It's not a problem. In those 4,000 years you've been asleep, humans on Earth have come a really long way.
We've been faithful to the dreams you entrusted to us.
Yes. We might be able to bring that spaceship up to the surface if we can find where it is.
Really?!
Of course! Crest is super duper rich and super duper handsome!
It has nothing to do with my looks, though...
I agree with Jun's plan. Our friends must be waiting for us in the Speranza, after all.
Isn't that right, Red Blitz?
See? You can put your faith in us.
Gotcha! I finally got a scoop!
Captain!
How can we trust you...
You HUMANS! (FX-youHumans)
Captain! No!!
Come back, Musclehyde!
Figured as much. The Captain's condition is too severe.
Blue Cop! Slash his tires!
Roger!
Don't you dare lay a finger on my Captain!!
Then we'll deal with you first!
Dad...
You have some nerve in that engine of yours, picking a fight with my Captain.
Shut up! I'm gonna crush you all for sure!
This little guy has a first-rate mill. What's your name?
I am known as the crimson flash, Red Blitz!
Cringe.
I like this boy.
Until the flame in my heart is extinguished, I will defend my Dad!
Crimson Shoot!
Jun! Your Metal Breath!
It must mean we're almost at our limit! Let's finish this quickly!
Roger!
If you don't mind, would you like to come aboard my ship?
Your ship?
Yes. It is a giant ship that sails through the vast ocean of space.
Mega Crimson...
Kick!!
Blue Cop! Star Rising Cannon!
Final attack!
DAAAAAD!!
I see. So that means... Gigantrex is like your dad.
What's a dad?
A child is born by the love of their mom and dad. And a dad is someone who watches over their child as they grow up.
I made a huge mistake. It's all my fault the Speranza was shipwrecked...
Metal Cardbot! Change up!
It's all my fault the Speranza was shipwrecked...
But because of that, we were able to meet like this.
Do you think Gigantrex will look back on this as a mistake?
No, he won't.
Red Blitz, sealed!
Who were those two that lent me their strength?
I don't know. Could it be the power that was hidden in the Metal Breath, just like Ultimate Blue Cop was?
Jun! He's gone!
Gigantrex is gone!
Wh- What?!