That's the Speranza? It's terrifyingly huge.
[Battle of the Red Ark]
I-Incredible!
Could that be an entrance?
Yes. But there's no way Flame Nova would have just left the gate open.
You might be able to force it open by manually overriding the control panel.
Alright! That's our cue to step up.
I've also been researching the escape pod technology for Metal Cardbots. I'm sure it can be of some help.
Rest assured, I have all the relevant data.
Very good.
All units! The Speranza must be retrieved, no matter the cost!
Roger!
I'm not dreaming, am I?
L-L-L-L-L-Look!!
We need to land quickly!
Affirmative! Now arriving at Speranza. Speranza Station!
Where's your old friends and your Metal Breath, again?
Red Blitz told me to look for the red door, but...
Easy peasy. We'll find it on the way.
Yeah. Let's hurry.
This stage is too small for you. A bot who cries out for freedom...
A bird trapped in a cage, if I must say.
Sky Gallop!!
This place is too unfavorable for a bot whose specialty is flying!
Worry not, I am not going down with a wound this ill.
Now, let the duel continue!
With pleasure.
As expected. The deck defense system was alive and well!
Heh! I can easily dodge all of these bullets-
- Boy! Don't underestimate the firepower of our defense system!
- Ow! Daaad!!
But we have to get in there somehow...
Ah! Everyone, follow me!
What are you going to do?
Now's our chance!
All units, charge!
Hey! You've got a lot of guts!
This is nothing!
Sky Gallop!!!
Now, hand over the Metal Breath, or else...
Stop!!
As long as thou art safe, milady, I care not what happens to me.
What are you talking about?!
I have been wandering in this strange new land all alone, yet thou have brought back the joy of flying to me.
So worry for me not and run!
No!
Metal Cardbot! Change Up!
Sky Gallop...!
Sealed!
Glober!
Floor it!
Sky Gallop. What a fool...
Heh! Let's go after them!
I will take care of that child. You deal with the guests upstairs.
Blue Cop? Alright! Time for revenge!
Wait. You're not making sense. You want the two of us to fight all of them!?
Heh. You scared, bro?
That's not the point!
Do not worry. I will give you power.
Is that...?
Next!
Hey! That one was mine!
Sorry.
Great work. Let's go inside. Huh?
What's this? Are they welcoming us in or what?
No. Wait!
Flash Vector and Spark Bit brothers?
Great! Time for some revenge!
Don't they look a little off to you?
Yes. Something feels strange about them.
But... All we have to do is strike them down!!
Alright!
Was that pineapple-head's fist always this strong?!
I got blown away by a little guy like him?
The Cosmic Stone, a sacred stone that Deus Machina hid away in their sanctuary.
With it, we, the Metal Cardbots, can unleash power beyond all limits!
Power beyond...
All limits?
Everyone stay back!
You're at a disadvantage without your Weapon Cards!
I'll join you!
Where do you think you're going?
What the heck is that?
It's one of Flame Nova's limbs!
What?!
Behave and hand over the Metal Breath.
Oh no!
There's no point in running.
Capture Whip!!
I told you... it's futile!
Dad!!
What the heck did they eat to make them so strong?!
We're running out of time...
We'll go!
Are you sure?
We're small, so it's harder for them to notice us!
That's some great journalistic spirit.
Guys!
Alrighty!
Let's keep them busy!
Should I keep running around?
I'll cover you!
Glober!!
Big guys are always mean to me for some reason...
I'll be fine.
Keep the Metal Breath safe no matter what, for the sake of my people who sleep on this ship.
I will, so get some rest for now.
Now, then. End of the line, Lady Peruru.
Here it is. The panel Musclehyde told us about.
Sebastian! The data!
Here!
Uncle, are you sure it'll work?
Even if it's an alien spaceship, the basic circuitry is probably similar to ours. We'll just have to wing it.
(Jun, Peruru. Please be safe.) (FX-italic)
(Everyone... Jun...!) (FX-italic)
Deep Bite! There!
This must be it.
REX! INFERNO!!
Children! Get back!
DAD!!! (FX-bold)
Caught you. It seems those brothers are on quite the rampage.
Ow... What was that?
Woah, that scared me! (FX-megaTrucker)
I know, right?
What?
I said, that scared me too.
Wow. That was a really big kaboom! (FX-shadowX)
No more sleep for us I guess, thanks to that racket. (FX-megaAmbler)
Isn't it a little dark in here? (FX-phoenixFire)
I guess this is our punishment for causing trouble. (FX-fletaZ)
I'm supposed to be feeding the cats. (FX-dexter)
Me need food too! (FX-buffaloCrush)
It's the big guys who we're causing trouble, not us. (FX-busterGallon)
It's because that jerk stuck his big butt in my- (FX-blackHook)
Stop being so petty. (FX-heavyIron)
You want a piece of me?! (FX-blackHook)
Quiet. Someone's coming. (FX-heavyIron)
JUN!!! (FX-ua)
The Metal Breath is now mine!
Never...
What did you say?
I'll never let you have it. For the sake of my friends!
Friends? Are you talking about...
...them, perhaps?
Peruru!!
Flame... Nova!!
Look at them.
Do you really think that two species, so different in size and appearance, could ever be friends?
We arrived on this planet without a place to live. It is inevitable that one of us will be doomed to extinction.
Either the humans... or the Metal Cardbots!
Now, let us try this again.
Don't tell me... You broke the seal on the Metal Cards?!
Yes. The two billion comrades who have been sleeping on this ship shall finally awaken!
What the...?!
Honey!
A card?
Peruru! Take off the Metal Breath! Or your arm will be-!!
Yes! Take it off already!
It's absurd that a lowly human like you should have it.
Coexistence? Don't make me laugh!
To you humans, we are nothing but monsters to be exterminated!
There is only one way for us to survive!
And that is to turn this planet into a second Machina!
Take it off now, Peruru!
No...! I'll never take it off!
I'll save... Mukara's will...
And the friendship between... Humans and Metal Cardbots...!!
I'll keep them safe, no matter what!!
Very well. Let's see how much you can handle.
(Help me... Mukara... Jun...!) (FX-italic)
Mega Trucker!
Set Up!
Mega Power Tackle! (FX-megaTrucker)
Mega Ambler!
Forceps Shock! (FX-megaAmbler)
Hehehe! (FX-shadowX)
Who are these bots?!
Spinning Cutter!
Phoenix Fire!
Burning...
Hammer!! (FX-phoenixFire)
You okay, Peruru?
Jun!
Behind you!
Rock Crush!!
Dexter!
That was close. (FX-fletaZ)
Th-thank you...
Wild... Slash! (FX-wildGuardy)
I will never forgive you... (FX-wildGuardy)
for threatening my friend! (FX-wildGuardy)
Wild Guardy!!
Did they wake up from the Speranza?
Unfortunately, that's where you're wrong! (FX-blackHook)
You're... Black Hook!
Boys! Open fire! (FX-blackHook)
Aye Aye, Captain!! (FX-buffaloCrush)
I haven't felt this much excitement in a long time! (FX-busterGallon)
Then...
What on Earth are you?!?
What are they, you ask?
Greetings, hero of the Star Guardians. (FX-heavyIron)
It can't be-?!
Since you don't seem to know much about them, I'll give you a special lesson!
Jun... You guys..!
All the bots here...
are my friends!
Flame Nova! It's time to settle the score with you!