Exclusive! Steel Interview
Nice to meet you, my new partner.
I bought you on a 48-month installment plan, so let's work together to finally get a scoop!
Wait, is that...?
If my instincts are correct, then that must be...!
Hey you, glasses guy. Fine looking camera you got there. Are you a news reporter or something?
Go grab your boss, and I'll get you a scoop!
A sc... scoop?!
Teacher!
I'm sorry as always. We've been disturbing your work too often.
What do you mean, disturbing? I like the company.
Whenever you're having a hard time, just let me know. I'll be there for you!
Since when did you two become so close?
J-Jun! How long have you been there?
Hello!
We've been at the car center all day...
Did you forget your promise? We need to keep the existence of Metal Cardbots a secret!
Don't worry! We can trust Ms. Mona.
- Teacher! This is a big train!!
- You need to keep this a secret from others, okay?
- I know that!
Mr. Train, transform into a robot please!
I'm sorry, but I shouldn't.
Pretty please? We won't say anything to the grown-ups!
If it can't be helped. But just this once.
Guys!
Cool!
Uncle Edo!!
Ms. Mona, what's going on?
Kids, how did you all know about this robot?
Got that? The thing about Metal Cardbots is a secret, so don't tell anybody.
I can't tell my mom about them?
Of course not!
It was him all along!
At this rate, it may only be a matter of time before the Metal Cardbots are discovered.
It's already too late.
Crest!
Look at this.
The editor-in-chief of Mowtown Times interviews a Metal Cardbot, a mechanical lifeform from outer space...
And they're holding a special press conference?!
Aw, yeah. This is what I'm talking about!
Today's main character is none other than ME! Spark Bit!
Good work, Jim! With this, the sales of Mowtown Times newspapers will skyrocket!
Th-Thank you...
Daddy, it's about time to start.
Oh, right, right!
Hahaha! I feel amazing!
Acting a bit flashy for a press conference.
My reporter's spirit is burning up! Jun! Let me interview him too!
What are you talking about? We need to stop this!
What are you guys doing here?
W-where did you-?!
You didn't come here to interrupt my dad's interview, right?
Vera, long time no see. How have you been?
Crest! It's been so long! I'm doing great, thanks!
I came here because I found the article in your newspaper interesting. If you wouldn't mind, could I get a seat?
Of course you can! I've got the best spot. Let's watch it together!
Now's our chance. Let's go!
Alright, then... Greetings, everyone. This is Warren Williams, the editor-in-chief of the Mowtown Times. We've got a great crowd here.
We're going to have an exclusive interview with a special guest. First, could you tell us your name?
Listen up! My name is Spark Bit, I'm a Metal Cardbot- a mechanical lifeform from the planet Machina.
There are many more Metal Cardbots other than me hiding out on Earth.
And one of them is a Star Guardian!
One who would pose as a defender of justice on my home planet of Machina, and now he's here on Earth!
Star Guardian, show yourself! I'll crush you!
Spark Bit deserves to lead the Metal Cardbots on Earth!
Are the Hidden Cardbots starting a rebellion?
We have to do something.
Jun, let me handle this.
Deep Bite...
Okay. The stage is yours!
Deep Bite! Set Up!
Trident... Submarine!
- If what you're saying is true, then this is a historical moment!
- Hmm? What's that?
A shark!
Run for your lives!!
Hey, hey! Wait!
Deep Bite! Take Back!
Alright. And now...
Jun. He wants to fight me. I'll go.
Nuh-uh! You sit this one out! Let me at him!
Okay, Red Blitz! First, let's lure him out of town!
We'll take care of things here.
What the heck just happened? Who was that Metal Cardbot?
Hey, you cocky punk!
Some nerve, trying to pick a fight with a Star Guardian!
Heh! I don't know who you are, but I guess I'll have to teach you some manners...
Little boy!
Little boy?!
Just try me, if you think you can keep up!
You wanna play tag, huh?!
He'll catch up at this rate!
Then let's blow him away!
What, did he run away?
Spark Bit! It's a head-to-head match!
A head-to-head match? Heh! That's my favorite kind of match!
Just don't cry when I beat you! Jun!
Red Blitz! Set Up!
Oh, you fight with your feet! Interesting.
My fists versus your legs.
Let me teach you... which pair is stronger!
This guy must be a power type. Dragging him into a speed fight will give you an advantage!
Alright!
You're too slow! You won't leave a scratch on me at this rate!
You little-!
What, so you're all bark and no bite?
Watch your mouth!
Calm down, Red Blitz! You're faster than him. You've got the whole ring.
Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee!
Alright then. Let's float!
I already told you, you're too slow!
Eh?
Giving up already?
Wh-What are you doing?
Now!
Heh! Why don't you tell me again who's too slow?
Don't act so tough when your kicks don't even have a hint of weight to 'em!
Let me show you a real attack!
Oho, you want some more, huh? Jun!
Red Blitz! Mega Crimson Kick!
Mega Crimson...!
Sparking Force...
Knuckle!
-Kick!! H-huh?! I can't move!
What's that..?
Red Blitz! Behind you!
What?
(What was that? Something doesn't feel right...)
No way he got me with those weak fists...
Come back, Red Blitz!
W-What?
Rock Crush! Use your ultrasonic sensor to scan above that container!
O-okay!
Who's that bot over there?
I knew it!
You've seen through my stealth mode.
He's got company.
What? Flash Vector? How long have you been here, big bro?
Big bro??
I've been watching you from the start. You're reckless, after all.
I know I can be! But you shouldn't come off as cooler than I am- Uh, wait a minute. Does that mean...
The reason why that red guy was immobilized is 'cause-
Silence.
Do not forget our goal, Spark Bit. Our target is the Star Guardian.
Boy. I know you're with him.
Wait, really?
You've already been told this before!
So that's how he pulled those Metal Cardbots in and out.
Hey, Bluey! Summon the Star Guardian now!
Jun! I'm their target. Let me fight!
But... It's two against one. I know you're strong, Blue Cop, but-
What's the hold up? Backing out because you're afraid?
Jun. Let me and Cielo handle this.
Yeah. We can't just sit still when Red Blitz got beaten up.
Alright.
Who are you guys? Didn't you understand me when I said to summon the Star Guardian?
We don't have to listen to you when we don't even know who you are.
I'm Musclehyde, a former journalist of Cardian's Post.
I'd like to interview the two of you. How does that sound?
I'll let you meet the Star Guardian if you accept.
Huh? Interview?
Ah, Musclehyde is stalling, expecting him to make another fuss for attention.
I refuse! I'm under exclusive contract to the Mowtown Times!
At least he's honest...
Declining my interview?
Jun!
Then I'll force you to do an interview!
I knew this would happen.
Oh, you want a piece of me too, huh?!
They're a pain in the neck...
We'll finish you off quick then!
Huh? L-look!
That is quite enough, Vector and Bit brothers.
Sky Gallop!
Why are you here?!
'Tis only but a matter of alignment with them.
Hey! The fun was just getting started!
Thou pretend thou art not, yet thy wounds from the broil with Sir Crimson Flash left thee impaired.
Wha-?!
The first step to dueling is to be in perfect physical condition. Dost thou agree, Flash Vector?
Mhm. I think so too.
What the- Bro!
Tch... aargh!!
Alright. Fine! But I'll fight you for real next time!
Hey you! Bluey! Tell the Star Guardian that it's his turn next!
He better be prepared for it.
Farewell, master of the Star Guardian.
Send my regards to lady Peruru for me.
Tch. What a let down.
So they were working with Sky Gallop all along...
Hidden Cardbots... We shouldn't let our guard down against them.