The Return of Steel
What was that?
You're... You're Jun's...
Yep! We're all friends of Jun!
All of thou are his...?
Sky Gallop?!
Everyone we've met from Planet Machina so far has become another one of Jun's friends.
And you'll be one of them soon enough, Sky Gallop.
I'm sure of it!
Hm. We shall see.
So Jun and those guys are the best of friends, just like Mukara was to us...
Are you saying we aren't, Red Blitz?
Heh! Of course you're our friend too, Jun!
Alright, everyone! It's time to gather all of our strength!
Mega Ambler!
Right.
Our stamina is coming back!
It's a temporary fix. It's to prepare for the pain to come later.
And don't forget to pay for your treatment.
Oh, we have to pay for that...?
I'll fix you all up when we're done, don't worry!
Increasing your numbers won't change anything!
Not a chance!
The brothers are not acting like themselves.
It looks like those foreign objects in their bodies are the reason why.
I'm detecting some abnormal energy readings from them!
That false power will confound those two brothers.
He took away their freedom of choice... I shall not forgive him!
Then we'll save them!
Hm? I see that Flame Nova has the same object!
Could that be another hidden treasure of Deus Machina?
If that's the case, that power will be mine!
You think I'll just let you have it?!
W-wait!
You want it? Then come and take it from me!
Let them handle Flame Nova for now. Peruru! Let's fight together!
You got it, Jun!
Metal Breath! Pick Up! (FX-both)
Cielo! (FX-mukara right)
Fleta Z! (FX-jun left)
Set Up! (FX-both xl bold)
- Nice to meet you. I'm-
- Later!
Vulture Wings! (FX-jun)
Cielo! Homing Magnum! (FX-mukara)
Where are you looking?
Dexter! (FX-jun)
Rock Crush! (FX-mukara)
Set Up!! (FX-both xl bold)
Spiral Iceberg!! (FX-mukara)
Spear Thrust!! (FX-jun)
Shadow X! (FX-jun)
Deep Bite! (FX-mukara)
Trident Submarine!! (FX-busterGallon)
Heli-Tornado!! (FX-shadowX)
Now!
Buffalo Crush! (FX-jun)
Musclehyde! (FX-mukara)
Are you ready?
Bronto!! (FX-mukara)
Strike!! (FX-bold musclehyde)
Buffalo!! (FX-jun)
Moonsault!! (FX-bold buffaloCrush)
Blue Cop! (FX-jun left)
Red Blitz! (FX-mukara right)
Set Up!! (FX-both xl bold)
Mega Crimson...! (FX-mukara)
Meteor Bolt...! (FX-jun)
KICK!!! PUNCH!!! (FX-split bold)
Milady. Grant me the honor of finishing them.
Okay!
Sky Gallop! Set Up!
We shall reunite soon.
S...Sorry...
Thank... you...
Metal Cardbot! Change Up! (FX-both bold)
Spark Bit! (FX-mukara right)
Flash Vector! (FX-jun left)
Sealed!! (FX-both bold xl)
As expected, they're not capable of handling this power!
You're the only one left!
Just give up already!
Speak for yourselves!!
This is getting annoying.
Now that's more like it.
My people... Must survive!
Jun! Looks like it's my turn, ain't it?
Everyone, give your energy to Mega Trucker!
Roger!!
You coming or what?!
Giga Flame Impact!!! (FX-phoenixFire bold xl)
Mega Power Shield!!! (FX-megaTrucker bold xl)
How about that, huh?
Great job, everyone. We'll handle the rest.
Jun. I'll stay here.
The Speranza's increasing speed!
Flame Nova! What are you planning?!
Ah, the Speranza is...!
It's coming this way!
- Huh?
- Wha?!
Stop the Speranza right now!
Why don't you defeat me and do it yourself?
Give us some time!
We'll get the door to the bridge open sure enough!
Trust us and fight to your heart's content, guys!
Jun! This card is it, right?
Yeah!
Blue Cop!
Roger!
Superior Docking!! (FX-blueShine bold)
Blue Cop Trinity! Set Up!! (FX-trinity)
Blue Cop, now you're big enough to stand up to me!
Flame Nova, you were once hailed as a hero. What happened to you?
You know nothing.
Do you realize the true reason why Deus Machina entrusted you with that Metal Breath?
I can't know everything...
but I can tell you that it's not what you think it is!
You foolish subordinate!!
Prominence Cannon!! (FX-phoenixFire bold)
You traitors who side with the humans will not stop me!
Blastrain!
Gigantrex!
Rex!! Inferno!!! (FX-gigantrex bold)
Not... A chance!
That guy is tough as all heck! Jun!
Okay! Black Hook! Set Up!
Captain's... (FX-jun)
CANNON!!! (FX-blackHook bold)
Peruru's mother! We need to get away from here!
That cable must be it!
Come on, come on!! Work!!
Just how strong is that son of a gun?!
Let me handle this, twerp.
I said to call me Jun!
Heavy Iron! Set Up! (FX-jun)
Heavy... (FX-jun)
BUSTER... (FX-heavyIron xl bold)
CANNON!!! (FX-heavyIron xxl bold italic)
Blue Cop!
Looks like the so-called hero of the Star Guardians is not capable of handling that power, either.
Blue Cop! Wild Guardy!
Let's end this!
Roger! (FX-left blueCop)
Got it! (FX-right wildGuardy)
Wild Guardy! Set Up!
Everyone! Let our powers combine!!
I'll let you finish him.
Let's go!
This time for sure...!!
Uncle!!
Master Crest!
Captain!
Right. Red Blitz! Head to the bridge right this instant!
Uh, m-me?
I'm speaking to you and no one else!
Just do as we taught you.
Now go!
O-okay!
Don't have too much fun without me.
I shall aid thee as well. Vector and Bit Brothers, join us!
But we're...
Bro! Let's give it a try!
...Very well.
Come here. You need to learn how to control the rudder in case something happens, don't you think? (FX-italic)
Let's start with the basics. First you need to- (FX-italic)
Galaxies... (FX-blueCop bold)
Wild... (FX-wildGuardy bold)
PUNISHER!!! (FX-punisher)
Flame Nova...
Earth... is a world where humans and Metal Cardbots can live together!
Blue Cop... I saw it...
At the lowest level of planet Machina.... There lies Metal Cardbot's very... First...
Jun!
Hey, guys!
Mom!
Peruru!
You had me worried sick!
I can't breathe, Mom!
The train to Mowtown, Mowtown, will be departing soon!
If you need any repairs, come stop by my car center whenever you'd like.
We'll be sure to, once we're finished here.
I'll stay and search for the Organizer that fell into the ocean.
I owe uncle Rex, after all.
We'll be waiting for you.
See ya later, pal.
Take care of yourself.
We have decided to help settle the situation as well.
Hmph.
Yeah, it's only fair.
Thank you, everyone!
But it's too bad. You didn't get to see the temple.
Our parents will be worried if we're gone too long.
We'll visit you again!
Don't you forget!
Jun!
You're just the greatest.
You're a wonder itself.
We're lucky to have met you.
Ahahaha! You guys are embarrassing me!
Jun!
I had a lot of fun!
Me too! Everyone, see you again!
Blue Cop! Your friend there is one of the best!
He sure is!
Jun!
Thank you for everything!!
So long!!
Someday, we will have to leave as well.
Do you really have to go?
This planet was not our original destination.
But... We'll need more time before we can continue our journey.
Now, it's only natural you seal me as well, yes?
Use the token of our friendship... Peruru.
Okay!
Metal Cardbot! Change Up!
Jun. Jun! Look at this.
This is the group photo we took earlier. It looks great, right?
What do you think of my skills?
Woah!
Jun! Let me see it! (FX-blueCop)
Me too! Me too! (FX-shadowX)
It's nice to have a bunch of new bots around! (FX-megaTrucker)
Those heavenly wings... They were so beautiful. (FX-fletaZ)
Me miss Yuri. (FX-buffaloCrush)
Yarr! Let's party when we get back home! (FX-blackHook)
Before we do that, I have something I need to say to you all...