Search for the Speranza
Why is she not responding?
- The train will soon be arriving at Porcaca, Porcaca station.
- Jun. Jun! Wake up! We're here.
- Please gather your belongings and ensure nothing is left behind when leaving the train.
- This is... Porcaca?
Now arriving at Porcaca village. Porcaca village.
I'm dizzy...
You alright?
Is this really Porcaca?
It looks a lot different from before.
It's only natural. It's been 4,000 years, after all.
That cliff... This must be it.
This is the place where we lived alongside Mukara.
Is it really okay to be out in the open like this?
After Vera's livestream, there's no need to hide them anymore.
Hello! Excuse me, are you Jun?
Wait, are you...
Peruru's mother?
You are Jun! Thank you for taking care of my daughter.
You're crushing my ribs...
Oh, sorry.
Anyway, where is Peruru? She didn't say anything about coming home.
Well, actually...
Looks like my daughter's friends brought Mukara's friends back home.
We're in big trouble now.
We lost the Metal Breath, and we're running away in this who-knows-how-big ship.
H-hey, at least we have my Metal Card, so don't blame yourself too much.
I've been in this kind of situation many times before and-
O-oi, Peruru. Can you get out for a sec?
'Tis of no use.
The power is on, but the engine is not running.
As expected. I will head to the bridge.
This should take me upstairs.
Ow ow ow, my back...
Did... that sound a bit ominous to you, too?
Yeah...
Dang it!
Hang on tight, Peruru! Capture Whip!!
You two will stay here and find a way to get the engine running.
Sky Gallop, you come with me.
I shall remain here too.
All the main circuitry of the engine sits overhead.
I shall rejoin thee as soon as we are done.
Very well. I'll leave it to you.
That almost turned me into a pancake! You okay, Peruru?
Yeah, just peachy...
Oh! That light...!
What is this room?
What do you mean Peruru got kidnapped?!
Peruru's mother, please do not worry.
We came here to save her.
Peruru is in the Speranza right now.
Speranza?
It's the spaceship we came here in.
Now it's sunken under the ocean, thanks to a certain someone.
Do you seriously have to bring that up right now?!
If you're talking about a ship that crossed through the sea of stars...
it fell to where the four stars lay.
So says the legend written in the ruins.
It is one of the records Mukara left behind.
Jun!
Mukara must've seen where the Speranza crashed!
According to the surviving records,
the Speranza fell on the night of June 21, 4,000 years ago, on the night of the summer solstice.
The four stars Mukara saw that night are...
The constellation of hospitális. The Umoa Trench is right beneath them.
It's go time.
You sure you'll be alright on your own?
Only two people can fit inside Deep Bite.
I should go alone to bring Peruru back.
If only we had the Metal Breath, you wouldn't have to go alone.
We have no choice but to rely on you.
Haha! L-Looks like it!
Jun!
I drew it roughly 'cause my memory's a bit hazy...
But when we crashed, a gaping hole was made in part of the ship.
I'm sure you can find your way in through that gap.
Sweet! Thank you, Red Blitz.
We'll be waiting for you, Jun.
Please take care of Peruru.
We believe in you.
But don't push yourself too hard.
When you see Glober, tell him I'm waiting for him.
You can do this.
Jun, make sure to bring our friends back.
I will!
Guys, we finally made it here. (FX-italic)
I'll be there soon. So please hang in there a little longer! (FX-italic)
Now then, let's go down to the coast and from there-
Brace yourself and let's get going!
Why can't you just do things normally?!
I knew it.
The core is warped and the flywheel is rusty. No wonder the engine's battery won't turn on.
What does that mean?
You wouldn't get it if I told you.
What are you gonna do, bro?
Just sit back and watch!
Glober, don't tell me these are all...
Metal Cards.
Everything on display in this room...
are all Metal Cardbots!
Peruru?
Hey hey hey, Peruru! Where are you going?!
We need to go back to the engine room!
Why the engine room?
Flame Nova's goal is to conquer the Earth by waking up the Metal Cardbots sleeping on this ship!
We need to destroy the Speranza's engine before they all wake up!
But if we do that, we won't be able to get back to land, either.
It's still better than a war breaking out between humans and Metal Cardbots!
At least ask me to come with you. This uncle is feeling left out.
Jun. Over there.
That must be it. The Speranza!
Ah, the entrance should be on the note Red Blitz gave me...
What the...?
Deep Bite, there must be a gap in the hull somewhere. Let's find it!
Aye-aye.
Woohoo! Cool moves, bro!
We're nearly there!
There's only two.
What are they doing?
I dunno... It looks like they're trying to force the engine to start by pushing the flywheel.
WHAT?!
Wuh?! Who's there?!
Is that you, redhead kid? So you've come back! Stop hiding and come on out!
Heh! Are you seriously challenging the- Huh?
-the best boxer on planet Machina, Spark Bit, just by throwing some trash??
Thunder Whip!
Hold him down! I'll go stop the ship's engine!
Are you serious?
It's not too late. I just need to stop him!
A little bit... more!
I did it!
Huh?
You did what, exactly?
Peruru! Argh-
Spark Bit. Smash the core with all of your might!
What's the core?
That big purple thing!
Heh! With all of my might?!
Oh, boy.
No!!
That's what I do best!!
Finally... It is time!
Speranza...
Rise up!
The Speranza is starting to move!
Jun. There's the gap Red Blitz was talking about!
Alright, let's go in through there!
What is it, Cielo?
Th-that's-
What, what?
A spaceship! It's a spaceship! A red one!
What?!
It's the Speranza!
Deus Machina knew.
That our mother planet, Machina, was doomed to be destroyed.
That's why they sent the seeds of life out into space.
Now, my two billion compatriots sleeping aboard this ship.
It is finally your time to wake up!
Let us make this planet... The second Machina!
What? Why isn't anyone waking up?!
I shall remain here too. All the main circuitry of the engine sits overhead. (FX-italic)
What are you planning, Sky Gallop...?!
Hm?
Give us back our Speranza!
The air defense system is still up and running.
We're not going to be able to make a frontal assault!
That's the Speranza, alright. In that case...
Yahahaha!
This is why machines need to be beaten to make them do what you want!
Watch what you say!
What are we gonna do with these two, bro?
We might as well dispose of them, just to be safe.
Sky Gallop...!
Dang. So you were up there all along.
Bro!
Sky Gallop, you dare betray us?!
Do not say such deplorable things.
I was never one of Flame Nova's allies to begin with.
Now, milady, I am yours to command.
Thank you, Sky Gallop.
That's what we call betraying!
I'm disappointed in you. I thought we were on the same side!
Thy choice is equally disappointing.
Flame Nova's ideas are the furthest thing from the freedom I so desire.
You're right, Sky Gallop.
Freedom is the least necessary component in the reconstruction of Planet Machina.
You stole the treasure of Deus Machina from me. I will make you pay for your transgressions!
This Metal Breath was given to Mukara by Gigantrex as a token of friendship!
It was never yours to begin with!
Jun. Jun! Wake up!
Ow... Are we inside the Speranza?
Looks like it's above the ocean now.
Over there! Let's hurry, Deep Bite!
What's all this?
Shooting at your ally? You're making me real sad, Speranza!
Looks like the decoy tactics are working, captain.
Good. I knew we could count on Cielo.
Alrighty! Full speed ahead!
I'm on my way, Glober!
The next stop is Speranza. Speranza station.
Please hold on, and be prepared to disembark.
Blastrain is getting close to the Speranza.
Please be safe, everyone...
Peruru...
Will Jun be alright?
Don't worry.
I don't need the Metal Breath to know that he's safe...
because Jun and I are connected by our hearts.