Menace Up in the Sky!
The village of Porcaca kept watch over 4 treasures.
The crimson flash, Red Blitz.
The champion of the sky, Cielo.
The arms of steel, Musclehyde.
And their leader, Gigantrex.
There is also a tale that's been passed down for generations that says,
"The giants must not be awakened until the time comes."
The time?
If I were them, my eyes would open right up to the smell of breakfast!
Two have already woken up among the 4 stolen tablets. We need to find the remaining two quickly.
Do you know where the other two are?
I'm afraid we don't have any clues yet.
I'm also worried about where the other two, Red Blitz and Cielo, went off to.
One of them had a device that could teleport through space.
Through space?
Not anymore. It started to become a problem, so I broke it!
I bet they're wandering around aimlessly somewhere right now!
What the-? It's so dark, I can't see anything!
You're buried upside down.
Huh? Where the heck are we now?!
I'll look for the two remaining tablets.
Crest...
It's my fault we're in this situation. I'll get them back no matter the cost.
Okay. I'll be counting on you, Crest!
My, leaving so soon?
Ah... Yes! I-I'll make sure to stay to eat next time.
Then I'll be leaving too-
You can't. My burger joint has a rule that any new friend Jun brings in has to eat all 10 burgers before they leave.
T-Ten burgers?!
Go ahead, have some.
You guys had to do this too?!
Yeah... I didn't eat another hamburger for two months after I did that.
Three months here...
Thank you for the meal!
Delicious!
I'm glad you like them. By the way, where are you staying the night?
I'll have to look for someplace now.
What? Now?
It's okay, Ma'am! I can sleep well anywhere.
That won't do!
Here, you can stay in this room.
Is it really okay?
Of course it's not okay! That's my room!
You'll just have to sleep with Bluey for the time being.
Bluey...? WHAT?!
Brrr... it's cold. Why does my neighborhood have to be so much colder at night?
Should I turn on the heater?
Nah, it's fine.
Come to think of it... it's too quiet.
Turn on the radio, then.
Until yesterday it was so noisy here. Every day was so loud that I wanted to cover my ears...
...and that is how I became the greatest pirate in the universe!
Is that true?
No.
He is indeed the greatest charlatan in the universe.
What?! Does this weird-eyed guy have something to say about me?
Will they ever get tired of fighting?
That's proof of their friendship.
Why don't you compete with dancing? I'll be the judge!
Stop it! You promised that you'd cause no trouble when Jun is at school-!
I've never seen Blue bro's bare head before!
It's my first time seeing it too.
...But now, I'm all alone again.
I'm here with you, Blue Cop.
Jun!
I'll make sure to get our Metal Breath back from Red Blitz, and everyone along with it. They're all my dearest friends, after all!
Yes. Let's try our best!
What? 4,000 years?! You mean we've been sleeping that long?!
Well we needed to wait until the time came, but we've been asleep for too long.
Useless! It's completely busted!
Then what about the Speranza?
We can't go back there, I guess. The worst part is that we can't even find where Musclehyde and Captain Gigantrex went!
It's all because of that Jun kid, who was with the Star Guardian!
Jun? That boy who had the Metal Breath?
Yeah. That Metal Breath of his probably belongs to Mukara.
Wh- what?!
Huh?
Okay, now it's official!
Official? What do you mean?
Cielo! Hey!!
What do you mean?!
That kid must've taken Mukara's Metal Breath while we were sleeping.
There'll be no mercy for him!
Jun? Jun! Jun! Wake up! Someone is here!
Ehh... Five more minutes...
Wake up already, sleepy head!
Uwaaagh!! Vera!
Why are you freaking out like that? And what's with the police car?
Someone my dad knows left it here for a while. Why are you here so early in the morning anyway?
We're here to collect news material.
Hello! Nice to meet you. I'm Jim Hawkins from the Mowtown Times.
Mowtown Times?
Mr. Jim is a photojournalist who works for my dad's newspaper.
A photojournalist?!
I saw you out on the street yesterday. You know this robot, right?
W-well, it's uh...
Relax. It's not like you're being interrogated by the police or anything. All you need to do is be honest about this robot.
Ehh... W-well, uhh...
- Peruru!
- It... looks like a robot, but at the same time it doesn't! Heheh...
- According to the tales in my village, it is said that the pottery was shattered when the giants sang. Can you do that?
- But... I don't really know... uh...
- Yes. I will try.
Well? Speak up.
W-well... Ow!!
My- My camera!
There's no way!
All the data is gone!
What is that?
It's Cielo!
It's headed to the main street in Mowtown!
What is that airplane? Mr. Jim, come quick!
Huh? W-wait up!
Let's go too!
Alright!
Hold on a minute. You're not going out like that, are you?
Here. Your mom prepared it for you.
Let's go!
What's that?
Cool!
Show yourself, boy! The Metal Breath you're wearing belongs to Mukara! Give it back, or else!
Oh man. They're making quite a scene.
We'll be in bigger trouble if we don't seal them now.
Seal?
That means putting Metal Cardbots back into cards.
Do you know how to do it?
I think so.
Jun has sealed 12 Cardbots so far, myself included.
Then let me help!
Huh? How?
I'm a caretaker of the ruins in my village. It is my duty as a descendant of Mukara to protect the souls of the giants that once slept there.
That spear...
Okay. I'll be counting on you.
But our opponent can fly freely through the sky. It won't be easy to land a hit with that spear.
Don't worry. I have a great idea.
- I don't know how you obtained that Metal Breath, but it's not yours!
- Dang it, you're so impatient. There's no way that kid will just show up even if you go on a full on rampage like that!
How long are you going to hide? Show yourself, blue-haired boy!
I'm over here!
If you want this, then-
What's wrong with you?!
Firing from up there is cowardly!
Surrender now, or the next one won't miss!
Blue Cop, let's do as we planned!
Skyjet Shot!
Not a chance!
They know our position!
Let's go with plan B, then!
Roger that!
The parking building!
Quick! Take pictures! The pictures!
Now's not the time for that-!
Where are you?
Got you!
You think you can run away from me?
Well then, how about this?
Oh no!
You've got some nerve!
Always make sure to watch where you're going.
Hmph! You think I can't keep up through these shallow passages?
What the?
Homing Magnum!
Missiles are following us, Blue Cop!
Hang on tight, Jun!
That nimble rat!
They're here.
Peruru! Now!
This can't be happening!
Let's finish this! Blue Cop!
Yes!
Blue Cop! Meteor Bolt Punch!
Meteor Bolt Punch!
Skyjet Shot!
Mukara... Where are you...?!
It worked!
Metal Cardbot, Change up!
Cielo, Sealed!
You did it, Jun.
Of course we did! Thanks to Blue Cop and you.
So this is how they turn into cards.
Dang you, Cielo. You're so impatient.
I have to find Musclehyde and Captain Gigantrex as soon as possible!