Cielo is Upset!
Wow, a fighter jet!
Oh, is this our new companion?
This is Cielo.
Cielo, I'm Theo.
And I'm Anna. Nice to meet you!
This one hasn't answered anything we've been trying to ask all day.
Your colleague, Red Blitz. Do you know where we could find him?
I don't know.
Red Blitz knew where to find you.
So I'm sure you know where we could find Musclehyde and Gigantrex as well.
You're stubborn. I said I don't know.
Red Blitz stole my Metal Breath. Please tell me what you know!
I really don't know! You think I know the answer to that when I don't even know where I am?!
You kiiiids!!
I said my garage is only for automobiles! Stop bringing airplanes in here!
Please calm down!
Well, we kind of have a reason...
What reason?!
Here!
There's a hole where they were stabbed with her spear. I thought you could fix it.
Huh? Why me?
'Cause uncle Edo is a master of repair!
And you'll fix this in a blink of an eye!
Now come on, chop chop!
Hmm. Maybe I can fix this with something like polycarbonate...
Oh, what a relief!
I'm counting on you, uncle Edo!
Please take good care of them!
Huh? Wha- guys! Wait!
Geez... Just what do those kids think of me?
It's raining like crazy. Even my socks are soaked through.
It seems the weather will be gloomy until tomorrow. There's a heavy storm warning too.
At least Cielo won't be the only gloomy one around here. Let's come up with a plan, Peruru. How can we find a way to get Cielo to open up-
Wha- What the- heck is this!?
Oh, you're finally here!
H-hello.
Mom! What is all this...?
Here. My gift for Peruru!
Uh, thank you.
Mom! What have you done?! What did you do to my room?!
It's not your room anymore.
What?!
It's Peruru's room from now on.
I was only going to change the bedsheets, but for some reason I just couldn't stop making changes here and there.
I've always wanted a daughter, to be honest!
I-I'm happy too.
Really? I'm glad!
That's why I'd like to repay the favor!
Repay me?
It's done!
Oh my! Peruru has such lovely craftsmanship!
It's a symbol that's been passed down in my village.
Oh, I love it! Now we have matching friendship handkerchiefs! Aren't you just the cutest thing?
Mom, please don't forget about your son...
She's gonna' pay for this...
Jun, are you okay?
There's nothing I can do about my room, but how long am I expected to sleep out here?
What about sleeping in the living room?
No way! It can't be helped, I guess...
Do you think Cielo will be okay? Won't they be scared being alone in the garage during a storm like this?
Eh, Cielo being scared? There's no way.
I was scared. Until I met you.
Bluecop...
I think Cielo needs a friend.
Alright. I'll do whatever it takes. I want to be their friend, after all!
Thank you, Jun.
What are you doing?
What does it look like? Don't you feel your body moving to the beat of this music?
Huh?
My fried Mega Trucker really loved dancing.
Clear the area!
So? Won't you join us?
You two! What do you think you're doing?
I- I'm sorry!!
Hey, Cielo. Let's play soccer!
What's that?
It's a game where you kick the ball into your opponent's goal.
Shadow X was the best at soccer.
Way to go! Alright!
It's on!
Then how about a game of chess? Our genius inventor Buster Gallon was great at it.
Yes, there. Checkmate!
Waaagh! That's the 19th loss!
Maybe I should go easy on you.
... Of course, I always won.
I doubt it.
Then how about a sword fight? Wild Guardy trained me, so I'm really strong!
I'm a gunslinger.
Feeling Hungry? Buffalo Crush liked eating from my garden generator.
I lost my appetite.
Wanna play the flute, then? Flute playing was Fleta Z's specialty. Listen to this!
That sounds terrible. Just leave me alone!
Just give it a chance! How about this? No? Then how about this?
It's hopeless.
It's come down to this... Time for my last resort!
There. All done!
Now what?
Just once, I've always wanted to fly. I dare say, it's like a dangerous challenge to the sky.
What do you say, Cielo?
Just don't throw up.
Feel like your stomache's upside down yet?
I can take it!
That so? Then how about this?!
What's the matter? Giving up already?
No! I won't give up until-
Until I make friends with you!
Shut it!
Jun! A-Are you okay?!
Look at you, defeated so easily. Don't ever say you want to fly again.
Yes, I will...
Still haven't come to your senses yet? You just don't get it!
Cielo! Let go of Jun!
I'm okay.
But...
I trust Cielo.
Huh? Wait a minute, you..
What now?
Can I see that mark on your head?
This symbol...
It looks like the same symbol that's been passed down in my village!
But yours has become faded.
What?!
No way! My symbol of friendship with Mukara!
Symbol of friendship?
The friendship between us humans and the giants from the sea of stars, will be forevermore. Now, I shall inscribe that oath here.
It's only been 4,000 years since that day. And yet our symbol of friendship was erased in vain like this, in such little time.
It's not like that. That friendship remains in your heart, even if the symbol is gone.
But...
This is bad!
-Firefighters are still struggling to contain the wildfires in the northeast of Mowtown.
-While the danger of wildfires spreading to residential areas is raising public concern,
-It's worse than I thought.
-If only Phoenix Fire was here...
-Fire authorities are mobilizing all personnel to...
Cielo! I have a favor to ask!
A favor?
Fly with me one more time!
Cielo, let's fly right over that flame.
I don't know what that will accomplish, but alright.
Thanks!
I think that just barely worked.
Was that the best you can do?
What?
Fly through it as fast as you can!
Your body won't be able to handle my speed.
We got some practice in earlier, I'll be fine!
Alright then. Hang on tight!
Surpassing the speed of sound created a vacuum that cut off oxygen to the flames! Not a bad plan.
Yea, exactly. Hehehe...
Good thinking, Jun.
Oh, you started calling me by my name.
You- You Misheard me!
I heard right!
Forget it. Let's just put this fire out!
Aaagh!! Not so fast!
-Thankfully, the wildfire was quickly brought under control.
-The miraculous speed at which authorities were able to work in such bad weather conditions...
It's done.
Look there.
It's perfect.
There.
Now you and I are friends, right?
Yeah, friends.
Cielo, I'd like to ask about the Metal Breath Red Blitz took from us.
Don't worry. I'll ask him to bring it back next time I see him.
But don't get your hopes up. He's hotheaded.
Thank you, Cielo.
Wow! the sky is clear now!
Hang in there a little longer, my friends. I'll definitely save you.