Can't Stop!
At this hour?
"Good morning Peruru."
Do you even know what time it is over here-
Huh?!
"Have you eaten your breakfast?" It's night here!
"Have you brushed your teeth?"
"You should exercise regularly."
"How about your homework?"... Homework?!
Who cares about homework?! I'm trying to carry on Mukara's will!
But the stone tablets and the Metal Breath are all...!
"Don't push yourself too hard."
Mom... I don't know what to do anymore...
What?! Your memory card is missing?! How many times will you repeat these same mistakes over and over again?!
But I really got it this time! A robot turned into a semi truck and-
Forget it! Get out of my sight!
So you're saying... You accidentally picked up a memory card lying in the park?
Yeah! Accidentally.
Just because you found an abandoned item, doesn't mean you own it.
I'll return it as soon as I find out who the owner is.
Oops...
You seem troubled today. Is something wrong?
Huh? N-no. It's nothing...
In that case! Shall we take a look at what's on this memory card?
Has he been like that this whole time?
Yep. Looks like he still needs some time alone.
I'll check the files now.
We can't let these pictures reach the public...
Looks like the card can't be returned to the owner.
Wait, stop. Where did that wound come from?
I kept wondering about that too.
Did he get hit by something? Or... bitten by someone?
Bitten? No way.
Think you can fix that, Uncle Edo?
Hmm, I can't do much for this kind of wound.
The only options are to replace it with a new part entirely, or remove the damaged part and have it processed with an alloy.
NO!!
That scared me!
When did he get here?!
Where are you going?
Isn't it obvious?! I'm gonna go find my dad!
We don't have any clues on where to find him!
So you want me to sit still and do nothing?!
Dad kept saying that his head hurts! I gotta' hurry and give him some first aid!
Hey! Why did you have to break that door?!
I'm gonna find my dad!!
What is this stench?!
That's one nasty fart!
I'm coming to save you! Daaaaaad!!
Daaaaaad!
Dad!
Man, it's just a bunch of cars that look like my dad...
Huh?
DAD! Red Blitz is here!
...oh, it wasn't him.
Hey! You're the thief who stole my kite!
Kite?
You're...
Hey there, kid! Nice kite you got there!
Wait, you're that kid from the park.
Give me back my kite!
You little runt. You have some nerve in your engine, picking a fight with me!
Shut up!
You have some nerve in your engine, picking a fight with my captain.
Shut up! I'm gonna crush you all for sure!
That's right. You won't back down just because you heard something like that. Heh...
Your kite is broken so I can't give it back to ya. Sorry.
Instead, how 'bout driving with me? Does that sound good to you?
Really?!
Woah!
Whaddya' think?
Super cool!
By the way, what's your name?
Kent!
Why aren't you playing with the other kids?
'Cause they're boring. They always cry for no reason!
You don't cry?
I don't cry!
You wanna bet on that?
What?
Well? Scared yet?
T-this isn't scary at all!
Then how about this?!
You can cry if you're scared!
I said I don't cry!
You're such a stubborn little kid!
He sure kicked the door off clean.
That should be enough, right?
That smelled horrible.
My arms hurt...
We're done with ventilation!
Great work.
Thanks.
What kind of fuel has he been eating these days?
I'm dizzy...
Could it be an engine problem?
Engine problem?
I'll have to take a look at his engine to find out what the problem is.
But if it's severe, his engine compartment could catch fire,
or it could run wild, causing the brakes to become unresponsive.
That would be a big problem!
Looks like we have to go find Red Blitz before Gigantrex.
Huh? Bad timing, mom! Sorry, keep talking.
It's okay. Go check on it.
It's nothing. Just another pointless, daily life photo-
Photos?
I wanna see your mom, Peruru!
Let us see her too!
T-There's really nothing to look at!
"Good night." It's daytime here!
That's your mom? She looks amazing!
Pahahaha! You look nothing like her!
It's rude to laugh, Jun.
Looks like you haven't replied to her messages.
My parents only know how to nag me.
"Did you do your homework?" "Are you brushing your teeth twice every day?"
I understand...
It's natural for parents to worry about their children.
Eh? But you're not married!
And you don't even have a girlfriend!
So how would you know?
Is that the only reason?
What?
Are there other reasons why you might be avoiding your parents?
I need to return to my village with all four stone tablets.
But all of them got unsealed and became Metal Cardbots, and the Metal Breath now belongs to Jun.
I don't know what to say to my parents. I don't even know what I should do anymore.
It must be rough...
I'm fine.
Mom's calling again...
What is it, Mom? The temple...
What?! The mural is suddenly glowing?!
I drove that fast and you're still not crying? You got some guts!
Let's do it again!
Heh, you got it!
W-what's happening?!
What's wrong?
My engine is out of control!
My brakes... aren't working!!
Now, let's cross the road two by two. 2, 4, 6, 8...
Huh? One of you are missing.
Ms. Mona!
Help meeeee!
Kent!
Wow! Kent is so fast!
What's going on?
I don't know! Nothing like this has ever happened before.
Could Mukara be telling us to clean the spear until it's sparkly clean?
Your innocence is definitely your charm, Rock Crush.
Really?
Ms. Mona? Hello! What seems to be the problem?
- He just can't hide his excitement.
- Yes, ah, what?
G-guys? She said that a red sports car kidnapped a boy.
RED BLITZ!
Hold on! I'll find a way to-
Red Blitz! I knew it was you!
You! What took you so long?!
What? We heard that you kidnapped a boy-
You think I'd do something like that?! I wouldn't, right?!
R-right!
Anyway, my engine is running wild and I can't stop it!
Help us PLEAAASE!!
Blue Cop, follow them closely for now!
Roger!
Cielo! Can you grab them from up there?
It won't be easy to approach because of these wires.
So we have no choice but to go with plan B, then?
We should save the kid first! Blue Cop, get as close to Red Blitz as you can!
You sure you want to do this?
Of course! Don't you trust my athletic ability?
Alright. Then I'll leave this to you! Blue Cop!
Hang on tight!
You can do that?
Wh-what?!
Okay! I'm ready!
Roger!
Carefully, carefully...!
Watch out!
NOT AGAIN!
Peruru! We're approaching a fork in the road! This is your only chance!
Okay! Blue Cop, keep up with Red Blitz's speed as much as you can!
Got it!
Red Blitz! I know it'll be hard, but you need to keep parallel with Blue Cop!
O-okay!
Here we go!
Hi!
We came to rescue you! Take my hand!
What's wrong? You said you don't cry! Be brave!
That's it!
Closer...
Good! I've got you!
Blue Cop!
Roger!
It's done!
Musclehyde! Rock Crush! You're up!
Ready!
Somebody stop meeeeee!!
Nice catch!
Th-thank you...
You're welcome...
Good job.
We did it!
Yahoo!
Yay!
W-what? Hey, your spear!
Th-this is...!
That looks like...
Mukara?
Mukara!!
Friends of the Speranza.
By the time you wake up, I will no longer be in this world.
But I hope my descendants will still be with you.
Please heed my advice and get along with not only my descendants,
but with everyone on this planet.
Just as you did with me.
It's been fun, Mukara...!
Well then Ms. Mona, I'll be going now.
Bye!
See ya around, Kent!
Yep! See ya!
Wait, did that car just talk? Is that the car the one who kidnapped you, Kent?!
Nope! He's my friend!
Your friend?
Yeah! My new friend!
Now you can drive just like before.
Thanks.
Cheer up. We'll find Gigantrex together.
And Jun's Metal Breath too!
Huh?
I'll help you! I'll stay here until you reunite with your friends.
Thank you! You've been a great help.
By the way, Peruru. I think you really resemble Mukara!
Yeah! You have the same eyes as him.
Really?
I think I'll tell my mom about this.
Hey, Mom. Sorry I haven't called you often.
I... actually have so many things I want to tell you...