The Greatest Power Awakens!
That's him! I'm sure of it!
I found the Captain!
Oh! Sorry, sorry. Go back to sleep!
This town has far too many cars and pedestrians. It won't be easy to find our Captain.
Is this what they call an era of change?
No signs in Landfill No. 30 either. I'll return to the car center for now.
Okay.
Where could Gigantrex be hiding?
He looked like he had bad fuel efficiency. He'll show up when he gets hungry.
Aren't you being a little too optimistic?
If that guy starts running around town, it'll be chaos.
I know it looks a little shabby, but nobody's gonna find you here. So you can relax, Captain.
Ungh!
Ah, sorry...! It's too small for you, isn't it?
That's not it. I've been in pain, even before I came here.
Gigantrex looked distressed when he saw that light coming from the Metal Breath.
What was that light anyway?
Well, they say the Metal Breath was a hidden treasure of Deus Machina.
Deus Machina?
It's the name of the mother computer from our home planet.
When my spirit and those of the Metal Cardbots became one, a power hidden within the Metal Breath was unleashed that transformed Blue Cop into Ultimate Blue Cop.
I'd like to hear that story too.
Crest!
Thank you for coming all this way.
Peruru, about that Metal Breath you gave to Jun... You said it was passed down from generation to generation, right?
Do you know anything about it? Like, a hidden legend of this bracelet or something?
Sorry, I got nothing... besides that Mukara received it from Gigantrex 4,000 years ago as a token of friendship.
It's only natural that she doesn't know. I also never knew that the Metal Breath hid such power.
Can I ask you something? Why did you all go to sleep 4,000 years ago?
'Cause we had nothing to eat.
For you, food means...
It means energy sources to keep our engines running.
4,000 years ago, the village of Porcaca had neither natural gas nor gasoline.
We had wind power, but no technology to generate electricity from it.
That's why we decided to go to sleep.
Believing that one day, as human civilization advanced, energy would become readily available.
You humans monopolized the fruits of your budding civilization! (FX-italic)
Gigantrex... Is that why he was so angry?
Huh? Ah, hello Ms. Motors, It's Edo Mona! Ahh, I mean Ms. Mona. It's Edo Motors.
Who is it?
It's Ms. Mona. She's a local kindergarten teacher.
Ah...
He has a huge crush on her, as you can see.
Does he seem a bit too smitten?
Hey, be quiet! Ms. Mona, can you please speak up a little bi-
Wh-what?
A robot?
Huh?!
Now, now, let's stay calm and evacuate!
Yes, a red robot and a giant semi truck have appeared here, at the Seaside Par-
Ah!
Kent!
Hey, kid! Nice kite you got there!
Are you okay, Ms. Mona?
I'm alright. Let's get out of here, quickly!
Ms. Mona? Ms. Mona! She said it's a red robot and a semi truck! Ms. Mona!
Red Blitz found Gigantrex!
Cielo!
I'll head there first. Everyone, follow me!
Okay.
Ms. Mona, are you okay?!
What? A red robot is flying what? A kite?
A kite?
Kite?
Jun, give me the weather report!
The weather? Why?
When we could no longer endure our hunger, what do you think was our last resort?
Gosh, Metal Cardbots can get so reckless.
I'm sure that's how desperate they were.
The barometric pressure is about to drop dramatically. There's an 80 percent chance of lightning clouds forming!
Once Gigantrex recharges his energy, we won't be able to stop him anymore.
Hang on a minute, Captain. It'll start any minute now!
Are you sure you're okay?
Of course. I just sprained my ankle a little bit.
Eh?
Oi! What are you doing here?!
Next time, please transform after letting me down... eugh.
Red Blitz! I know what you're thinking! Cielo!
No! My kite! Waaait!
Why do you have to stand in our way?
Look at these people!
It was you who told us to get along with the humans! What happened to you?!
I told you...
That the situation has changed!
Cielo!
Musclehyde! Set up!
Captain, I don't want to fight you!
Say that to someone weaker than you, Musclehyde!
Crimson Shoot!
Look out!
Don't you dare interrupt our Captain's dinner time!
What problem are you going to cause this time, Red Blitz?
Do you know how much we've suffered because of you?
Red Blitz did nothing wrong!
He is just being true to his feelings!
Aaaah! It's here, it's here! It's gonna start, Captain!
Come back, Musclehyde!
No. Wait, Jun. I can still fight!
There!
Everyone, this place is dangerous!
Why aren't you running away?!
Over there! Kent and Ms. Mona are still out there!
Jun!
Are you okay, Ms. Mona?
Mr. Edo... What are those robots?
Ah- I don't know. Anyway, let's get you to safety! Excuse me!
You're Kent, right? Are you hurt anywhere?
Nope!
Come with me.
We have to hurry! The lightning will strike soon!
Looks like we're facing the worst case scenario.
Yup. But we have to push through it anyway!
Metal Breath! Pick up!
Rock Crush! Set up!
I'm going first?!
Yeah. You charge in first,
followed by Musclehyde and Blue Cop, who will attack in quick succession.
We believe in you.
Pierce them with your drill!
I really don't like this idea, but...!
Here I go!
Huh? Hey! I told you to stay out of our way!
Rock Crush! Spiral Iceberg!
I won't run away anymore!
Sit this one out!
Brachio Slash!
Way to go!
There you go.
It's alright, everyone. I'm here...
The Captain is really back now!
Now now, don't cry...
It's okay...
Well, Ms. Mona. See you soon.
What about you?
There's more children out there that need to evacuate. You go on ahead first.
Sebastian, depart!
This is it! I can feel the surge of energy coming back to me, like all those years ago!
This is bad... The Captain is going to blow this whole area away!
Quickly! To Jun!
Rock Crush! Protect Edo and the others!
Oh, okay!
Behold! The flames of hell!
REX! (FX-shakexl phoenixFire bold)
INFERNO! (FX-shakexxl phoenixFire bold)
Jun! Blue Cop! Get up! (FX-flipped)
Jun! Everyone! Are you okay?!
Let's get you out of there.
Can you walk?
Yes. Only a little...
See that? This is the power of my Captain! You've lost! So hurry up and give us Mukara's Metal Breath!
W-We're not done yet!
Blue Cop!
I... no, we... cannot lose here. Until we regain our companions, the friends we made here on this Earth!
Jun! Please seal Gigantrex. I'm counting on you!
I entrust the future of humans and the giants from the sea of stars, to you. (FX-mukara voice)
Is that...?!
How? How can this be?
Why does this child wield the power of Deus Machina?!
Now, speak out loud! Speak out the words that come to your mind! (FX-mukara voice)
Blue Cop! Superior Docking!
Blue Cop Trinity! Set up! (FX-trinity)
Blue Cop! Show them your power!