It's Okay, Rock Crush
Just when I thought I'd found a place that's nice and quiet... Why can't they just leave me alone?
Huh?
Oi Oi! Relax! I'm a friend!
L-Liar! I don't have any friends!
Just listen to what I have to say!!
Let's be friends, one loner to another!
Soooo, this is, uh... this goes here, and...
Whatcha doing?
Homework. We have to solve 10 pages of fractional number problems-
AARGH! I can't take this anymore!!
Cheer up. You can't give up now.
Yeah. Build up your patience.
Gimme that.
Done!
She's fast!
No kidding!
You solved all of that already?
I'm even considered to be among the slowest students in my village.
Delete.
Hey! Why did you do that?!
You need to do your homework for yourself.
Hello, Dad.
I'm doing homework with my friends.
Breaking news: We have an update on the recent sinkhole occurrences in the center of Mowtown.
Fortunately, there are no casualties yet, but Mayor Jacques-
Sinkhole occurrences... Reminds me of Dexter.
Okay. I'll be careful.
Did he say anything about all the sinkholes?
Yeah. We don't know how or why it's happening yet, so he wants me to come home as soon as possible.
Wait, that geyser...
Argh! Yeah, my head is about to explode like a geyser!
I'm not talking about your head! The place on the news where the water main broke... is the same tunnel we went through the other day.
Then that must mean...
Rock Crush?!
Did I miss something while I was away?
Ah, well...
Here we have a map of central Mowtown. These X marks are the places where the sinkholes occurred. Let me display these in chronological order...
So he's traveling underground.
If we trace its path, his destination in the next hour will be... here.
Th... this is... OUR RESTAURANT!
I hoped it wasn't...
(If that happens...)
AAAAH!! What should I do?!?
Stay calm, Jun.
Let's head towards the scene first.
Don't you worry. We'll solve this problem together.
We're ready, Blue Cop!
Alright!
Jun! Your homework--
Excuse me!
Ah, yes sir. Coming right up!
Where are we?
A thoroughfare road that's under construction. Rock Crush will have to pass through here to get to the Milky Way.
Is that...?
Over there!
Huh? I'm out in the open.
That's Rock Crush?
I knew it was you!
It's strange. He never wanted to come outside before, but now...
Uh, uh... it's dangerous! I'm going--
Shut up! Keep it moving!
That voice!
Red Blitz!
Eh? Oh ho! You came right to me!
Why are you here?!
Isn't it obvious? To bury you into the ground!
Don't say scary things like that!
So all those sinkholes happened because of you!
You're going to destroy the Milky Way by using your friend like a tool?! You coward!
Co-Coward?
I'm not his friend, though...
Enough talk! Just give me your Metal Breath if you want your precious burger joint to stay safe!
Not gonna happen!
I see what's going on. Rock Crush is most likely being fooled by Red Blitz.
Maybe Red convinced him that he can go back to his quiet life if they have the Metal Breath or something.
He's the worst.
Rock Crush! Everything he told you is a lie!
What do you mean?
Don't ask questions! All you have to do is follow my orders!
OW! My foot!!
Sorry...
Don't just sit there and apologize! Go take 'em down first!
O-okay!
Blizzard...
That's...! Blue Cop!
Roger!
Star Rising Shot!
He's getting away!
Wait, no he isn't!
Don't get too cocky!
Blue Cop!
Rock Crush! Now- Eh?
HEY!! What are you doing?! Get out of there!!
Their teamwork is terrible.
Good thing for us.
Get him to fight outside of this tunnel. It's getting stuffy in here.
We can't come out and fight because this place is too small.
I know, but...
You said you wanted to live a quiet life! So fight for it!!
I don't wanna!
Jun!
Is that...
Glober?!
Ha Ha! The Metal Breath now belongs to Glober! (FX-sarcasm)
WHAT?!
Ciao~! (FX-sarcasm)
Jun!
After him!
They're gone?
Stop right there!
Say hello to Jones.
Since when have you been after the Metal Breath? The world is full of untrustworthy people.
You're one quick-tempered fella. That's why your perception is all blurry.
What?!
Wha... Aha! So that's what's up!
That's what's up.
What's up?!
Don't tell me... It was bait?
I snatched the Metal Breath so that red guy will come after us with his eyes lit up like headlights, yeah?
We will lure away Red Blitz, and you, Blue Cop, will go stop Rock Crush.
We?
He has a talent for making friends with everyone.
That's Jun's specialty.
I think so too.
Alrighty! Let's roll!
This is Mowtown police! This location is at risk of a sinkhole occurrence! Please evacuate immediately!
He's here!
Gimme that boy and his Metal Breath!
Aaaahhh~ Let me go already! (FX-sarcasm)
Let me gooo! (FX-sarcasm)
O-of course not! (FX-sarcasm)
That twerp...! Stop right there!
He took the bait!
Wow.
You guys get off here.
Wait for me!
Rock Crush, stop! You shouldn't believe everything Red Blitz says!
It's none of your business!
No, Rock Crush!
You can do it, Blue Cop!
Be careful!
We need to lead him far away from the Milky Way... I mean, away from a crowded place full of people!
I got it.
You think you can get away from me?!
My speed and horsepower are second to none!
But, I bet you've never seen anything like this!
Dang it!
Is it here? No, here? Waaahh! Don't leave me alone out here!
Rock Crush, stop!
I can't see anything!
Rock Crush! Look ahead! Ahead!
We lost him, right?
Yup. And looks like that park over there is nice and empty.
Wait! That's my burger joint!!
Oh? This was your place?
Quick, we have to get out of here!
But we gotta follow the traffic lights.
Heh! Found ya!
That noise... That way!
I found you!
You're late!
Huh? Glober?
Final warning! Give me your Metal Breath, or I'll tear this place down!
I'm not gonna let you do whatever you want! I won't hand over this Metal Breath, and I'll protect my burger joint too!
And! I'll be taking Rock Crush with me!
Huh?
What?!
You can do that?
Of course! So lend me your strength. Please!
Good grief. Very well!
So that's how it's gonna be, huh?!
Cielo! Set up!
I was getting sick of waiting!
Enough messing around. Come with us, Red Blitz!
I don't wanna' hear it! Rock Crush! If you're that scared, just keep your eyes shut and follow me!
Bu-but...
Hurry!
Okay!
Stop!
You're up, Glober!
Sure thing!
Thunder Whip!
Rock Crush! It's okay now! you don’t have to listen to what Red Blitz says anymore!
You're lying! You'll just bully me too!
Musclehyde! Set up!
Leave me alone!
Musclehyde! Dreadnought Storm!
Dreadnought Storm!
Running away from your fears won't solve anything! Let us help you!
Don't listen to him! He'll just take advantage of you!
What should I do?!
Believe in me! Cielo!
'Scuse me!
Jun is not the person you think he is! I promise you that!
Nooo!
Glober!
It's okay, Rock Crush.
Musclehyde! Now!
It'll be over in a moment, Rock Crush!
Metal Cardbot, change up!
Rock Crush, sealed!
I should've found him sooner than I did... Take good care of Rock Crush, for my sake.
Of course. Thanks for the help, Glober!
By the way, where's Red Blitz?
Ah...
You'll pay triple for that!!
Uh... I'll see you again... somewhere!
Hey!
Blue Cop! Guys!
You did well.
What happened?
Now, now. Let's get back to work.
Ahahaha...
Thank you again.
Drill!
Cool!
I'm supposed to be the coolest one here!
Cielo...
Hey, quiet down.
They don't know "cool".
They're children.
Big bro! I wanna ride it!
I'm sorry, you can't.
Woaaah! So cool!!
Getting along with others isn't as bad as you thought, right?
Yeah, I suppose it's not.
Again!
You got it! This time in reverse!