With all the endless conflict and division / gyesokdoeneun galdeunggwa bunyeol
It feels like we'll lose all the light inside / bicheul modu ileul geot gata
But as long as we never give up / geuraedo jeoldae pogihaji ma
Always trusting in each other / seororeul mideo bwa
Together, let's drive away / uri hamkke eoduumeul
darkness with the light! / bicheuro moranaeja
Our hearts / tteuge-
shine passionately / -pge pureuge
hot and azure / bunnaneun maeum
May they forever blaze bright / ujuui byeolcheoreom
like the stars across the universe / yeongwonhi taoreugil
Even when darkness and trials come our way / eodumi siryeoni
I'll be there to protect you / dakchyeodo jikyeonaelge
Shout out! Metal Cardbot / oechyeo! Metal Cardbot
Wild!