Musclehyde's Choice!
Welcome... How much you want...?
Fill me up.
Monster!!
Wow, so much for customer service.
Hey, Red Blitz.
What do you want, Musclehyde?!
This isn't right. The humans will only fear us more if we steal what belongs to them.
You can't live on an empty stomach. That's what the Captain always used to say.
Just where did the Captain go?
I don't know! That's why we're looking for him, by any means necessary!
By any means, huh?
Ugh, you idiot!
You went out to collect news, yet you came back without a single photo? Is this a joke to you?!
I got ambushed by a robot!
Then why didn't you come back with a picture of the robot?!
Dad! Look!
Huh?
This is footage taken by a security camera at an electric vehicle charging station last night. What are these robots-
Why can't we have a journalist skilled enough to get an exclusive story like this?
I know, right?
I guess I have no choice. I'll put a bounty out for a scoop. Monster or robot, anything will do!
Can I get the reward if I get a photo?
Of course, of course!
Mowtown Times put a bounty on photos, huh?
Lavi! Camera!
Right here!
Mister Vance is gonna get that bounty!
I'll get half the reward, right?
Shut up!
A bounty? This is crazy.
We should seal Red Blitz before things get any worse.
But we don't even know where he is.
Why don't we look for him while we circle around Mowtown?
Easier said than done. Do you have any idea how many cars there are in this city?
Is there anything we can do?
There is a way, but...
What is it?
What do you have in mind, Jun?
Hey, Mr. Jim. Do you really think you can get a photo in the middle of town?
Of course I can! I'm a pro. I don't miss any good moments!
You're too unyielding. Monsters usually avoid people's eyes, don't you know?
I guess... the one I saw was in the mountains.
See? There's no way a monster would come to such a crowded pla-
I- I found one! There!
Huh?
What in the world is this?!
You! I knew you had a connection with those robots! Let's go somewhere else so we can talk-
Welcome. One and all.
Welcome. To. Milky Way.
Welcome. One and all. Welcome. to. Milky Way-
Cool, right? It's a robot for promoting this burger joint.
Yup. We spent good money on it. Well, come in, come in!
It's just an animatronic?
Tch. What a bummer. Let's go, Lavi.
I knew something wasn't right.
Guess I'll have to look for a scoop elsewhere...
Everyone will forget the news about Red Blitz if pictures of this robot are everywhere.
I call it, "Operation: Hide a leaf in the forest!"
How is this a good idea?
Is he always like this?
He's usually like that, yeah.
I feel sorry for Blue Cop...
It's my fault for asking what Jun thinks...
Guess there's no way I'll get that reward money.
Excellent!
Where did you get this?
A... burger joint called Milky Way...
You did it! This will be on the front page tomorrow!
Wait! It's just a robot for store promotion... Are you serious?
"Monster in Mowtown! Milky Way Mayhem!"
4,000 years... Earth has changed so much in that time. What would Captain Gigantrex say if he saw this?
Huh? That's the Star Guardian?
Huh?
Let me see that!
Milky Way? That's it. That's where I can find that boy!
Wha? Where are you going, Musclehyde?
I said where are you going!?! HEY!!
You worked hard, Blue Cop!
Never thought I'd be acting for 2 days straight to promote a burger joint.
But it's working so well! You're so popular on social media, too!
Today's sales were excellent thanks to you.
Can you do this again tomorrow?
T-tomorrow too?? Ah... I think that will have to wait.
Musclehyde!
I told you my plan would work!
Yeah, congrats.
Be careful!
What do you think you're doing?! You made an attraction out of a Metal Cardbot! Red Blitz was right. You really were trying to rule over us!
You misunderstand, Musclehyde.
Jun cares about us more than anyone. Although he's just a little baby compared to Mukara.
Who are you calling a little baby?
Musclehyde, the Arms of Steel! You were once friends with Mukara, so you should know! You must know what it means for him to be able to wield the Metal Breath!
Hey, Musclehyde! Don't you leave me behind like that!
Red Blitz!
Crimson Shoot!
Blue-haired boy! I'll take Mukara's Metal breath back today for sure!
Huh?
What the heck are you doing?!
We can't be dragging civilians into this!
Huh! Who was it that brought a civilian into this in the first place?
I told you, we must survive by any means!
No! There is another way!
What?
Be my companion and come join me!
You think I'd be your underling?!
Then... how about a game of tag?
A game of... tag?
You're it! If you catch me before that clocktower bell rings, I'll give you this Metal Breath!
What are you thinking? Do you think you actually stand a chance?!
Peruru. Let's believe in Jun.
Now! Are you ready?
Heh! You think you can beat the Crimson Flash?
One! Two! Three!
Begin!
What the-! Cielo! Seriously?!
Surely you didn't think we'd make this easy for ya?
Musclehyde! Go get him for my sake!
Out of my way! You think a little guy like you can handle my strength?
You're right, I can't!
Get off!
Blue Cop!
Darn.
Musclehyde. Compete with me! What do you say?
Mukara. I told you. Humans can't win against us.
You can't know unless you try.
Whoever gets to that dock first, wins!
Guess there's no talking you out of this.
Tres!
Dos!
Uno!
Hey Mukara! That's cheating!
You can take a shortcut too, you know!
That little...!
Why am I suddenly thinking about Mukara?
I won't let you get away!
Red Blitz is right. I'll use any means necessary!
I won't let you reach Jun!
Will you back off already?!
Three minutes left...
Admit that I won against-
Are you really a reporter? Those articles are all shams!
What? Do you have proof?!
I lied to cover up the charging station incident.
I don't understand. Why did you do that?
I wanted everyone to know that Metal Cardbots aren't a threat!
And you lied just for that?
For my friends, I'll use any means necessary.
Great job, Musclehyde!
This game of tag is now over! So gimme that Metal Breath!
The bell hasn't rung yet!
Then I'll put an end to this right now!
Musclehyde! Get out of my way! Scarlet Hurricane!!
What?! Hey! What's up with you?!
You're here.
I lost.
Humans are small, and our lives are much shorter compared to you guys. But our hearts are the same, for we are friends.
You're right.
I've decided. I'll live alongside humans on this planet!
Now you're saying things like that too?!
These are the means I choose to survive!
That so? Then you're my enemy too!!
Musclehyde!
Blue Cop!
Let's lend him a hand!
Supernova Smash!
Brachio...
Slash!
Waiwaiwaiwaiwait!! Calm down and let's taaaaAAAAAALK-!!
YOU'LL PAY FOR THIIIIIIS!!
T-Thanks...
I lost. Jun, seal me.
Then as of today, we're friends!
Alright. Nice to meet you.
Metal Cardbot, change up!
Musclehyde, sealed!
Good to have you, Musclehyde!