Operation Underground Battle
Wow!
It's a drone with a camera!
I got it yesterday.
With this thing, we can find the robot hiding in the forest from a safe distance.
Uh... about that robot...
You lost it, didn't you? I heard from Sebastian.
I... am just glad you're okay though, Crest!
Yeah, we were... so worried!
I think that forest is too dangerous. We better stay away for now...
Yeah, I agree with Anna...
That robot said it hated humans, though. We can't just ignore it.
I wonder just how much Crest knows about the Metal Cardbots.
Uncle Edo!
He wants the Metal Cardbots...
Let go of him!
Wait up, Crest!
He didn't seem surprised at all...
What's that?!
Mega Ambler? What's the matter?
Jun. It's an emergency.
The pipes burst and water is getting everywhere.
I have no idea how it happened.
There's been a sinkhole here too. I can't handle this by myself!
Somebody come help, please!
Alright. I'll be there right away.
Huh?! What's that?!
Dexter?!
Who is it?!
So you've been causing the sinkholes in Mowtown!
Shut up!
Yeah, got it. Out.
What's going on?!
I heard it's Dexter.
Wasn't he trying to protect the animals?
Why did it come all the way to Mowtown?!
I think it might be trying to destroy the roads to protect the animals.
People aren't stopping the road construction despite all the warnings,
so it's trying to destroy all the roads to protect the animals.
Why don't we get a look at the map?
These are the places that sinkholes appeared.
Let's connect them and see if we can figure something out.
Looks like there's no pattern...
Dexter got his face injured when Wild Guardy attacked...
He probably doesn't even know where he is...
Isn't that all... the more reason to destroy the robot?
So we can prevent it from causing more damage?
It's not a robot! It's a mechanical lifeform from planet Machina!
We should try our best to talk to him!
You think... he will listen?
Dexter is right in wanting to protect the animals.
He just chose the wrong way to do it.
What if it won't listen?
Then we'll have to fight to stop him.
Whether you want to talk or fight, you have to find it first.
How will you find it when it's burrowed deep underground.
That's why I have a plan.
Operation Underground Battle!
Operation Underground Battle?
For this operation to succeed...
Crest. We need your help.
What is that on top of the drone?
It's an ultrasound generator to repel moles.
I got it because Jun said he needed it.
We will put this baby in the sinkhole!
Dexter is relying on the sound to get around.
This will bring him out of the ground right away!
The map of the sewers! I got it from my dad.
Question: will the drone be able to communicate underground?
Don't worry. I will control it.
Sebastian!
I memorized the whole thing.
Thank you so much.
I'll be off then!
Let's get going, guys!
We have a signal on the radar...
Is it Dexter?
It's big...
It's coming!
No, that's a rat...
How is it going?
Shall I try again?
Is that...
Now he's here!
Wow...! A, uh, robot!
It looks dangerous, let's run!
Wait up! W-what's the matter?!
Huh? Is that the little human?
Yaah!
Stop! Stop that horrible racket!
Dexter! We don't want to hurt you either!
We'll find a way to protect the animals!
Please stop attacking innocent people!
What? Humans protecting the animals?
Don't make me laugh!
Dexter! Listen to me!
Metal Cardbots have to learn to coexist with humans!
To live peacefully on this planet!
No! Humans can't be trusted!
Owner of the Metal Breath! You're lying to trap me in your seal!
You leave me no choice.
Now I have to do this! Shadow X!
Stealth mode, off!
Stop right there!
How did you...
We were prepared in case you wouldn't listen to us!
Haha!
He was waiting there before we began this operation!
Will there be a fight?
Jun... please take care of things...
Wait... what?
Don't be a troublemaker! Enter the seal!
I will never!
How can he do that...
Huh?
Huh. Where did he go?
Hiding is supposed to be my thing!
I can't use the main camera.
But my sound wave device can detect where you are!
There you are!
Hey! Let go!
Come back, Shadow X!
Your turn, Phoenix Fire!
You don't scare me!
Hey! It went back inside!
Dexter is tracking our location through sound...
In that case...
Phoenix Fire! Hammer Quake!
Hammer...
Quake!
Augh!
Phoenix Fire! Proceed to attack!
Hammer Quake!
Augh! Stop it!
Behind you!
Water Splash!
Augh!
Well done!
Your turn, Mega Ambler!
Mega Ambler! Stop him from going back underground!
Got it! Leave it to me!
Forceps Crush!
Let go of me!
Oh no...!
Great job, guys!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Blue Cop, setup!
Dexter! It's time for a faceoff!
You!
Blue Cop!
Infinity...
Force...
Break!!
Metal Cardbot...
Change Up!
Sealing...
Dexter!
Now, what do you see?
What?
A gorilla waving?
Looks like he's been fixed!
What do you mean?
Thank you guys.
I really owe you an apology.
Hey, what's wrong?
Is there something on your mind? Come on, you can tell us.
Don't worry about me.
But the animals in the forest...
what will happen when the road is finished?
I have something to show you. Come with me!
Here we are.
What?
This road has been designed to allow wild animals to cross safely.
Humans have come up with a way to protect the animals too.
I see the people of this planet have shown a little consideration.
Do you feel better now?
Yes. I totally do.
I'll join you as a part of your team now.
Haha! Yeah, welcome!