A Metal Cardbot from the Sky!
It's real, I swear!
You may find it hard to believe, but trust me!
All of this is happening in real life!
What is she up to?
It seems Vera's video of Metal Cardbots is blowing up in views.
And overseas!
Overseas?!
Hrgh! I'm filming a report right now, be quiet!
Uh, I'm sorry!
What do you mean, "blowing up in views"?
It has already over 5 million views!
Whaat?!
But it seems the comments are divided...
"That's some good CG."
"Just like a Hollywood movie."
"Just a copy of a robot animation."
"Is anyone falling for this prank?"
I'm so mad!
How many times do I have to say this is not a fake video!
I have never used any kind of CGI!
Uh, hey, hang on! Hello?!
It seems she is getting prank calls and harassment from malicious commenters...
I kinda feel bad for her now...
Rrgh! Huh?
Who is this now?
Hello. I am Fleta from Belmeha Island.
I became a fan of yours after seeing your videos.
I believe that your videos are real.
I'll be visiting Mowtown tomorrow.
Hope to have a chat with you in person...!
Yes! I know there would be someone out there who believes me!
OMG, I look forward to meeting you, Fleta!
And... I take that back.
She just doesn't give up, does she?
I guess not.
Huh? A friend from overseas?
Said he was a fan of her Metal Cardbot videos.
That doesn't sound good.
I want to keep the Metal Cardbots as secret as possible.
But guys... everyone here already knows, anyway.
I think Crest is already on to us...
Why are you chasing people away?!
Ugh... they saw it with their own eyes!
I don't think we can make up any more excuses...
All of you have been too lax!
We need some special training!
Alright!
You're all here to train to transform into a vehicle mode
or hide before people see you!
We are ready!
Well... get into action as soon as I turn around, okay?
1... 2...
3-go!
Dexter... go in or come out. You have to pick one.
Mega Trucker, I see you!
None of you passed!
Where is Shadow X, though?
You need to be fast, just like m-
Waah!
You could have just used your stealth mode, Shadow X.
You flunk the test too.
First, we need to find who was it that sent Vera the email.
A strange kind of place to... meet a guest from overseas.
Yeah, it's not even a coffee shop. It's a little strange...
Crest is here?!
What are you guys doing here?
Well... we are...
We are... lost, you see?
The police officer told us to wait here while he calls our parents!
That is the worst lie ever...
Crest!
Fancy seeing you here!
Hello, Vera.
Wow, that's such a coincidence!
What are you doing here?
They told me you're lost.
What?! Our school is right around the corner!
Hehe... uh, anyway,
weren't you meeting the fan who sent you that email?
I guess word spreads fast, huh?
Yeah. We agreed to meet here.
Here?
Looks like he's here!
He arrived in that...?
Careful, Jun! That plane is...
...could it be?
A Metal Cardbot?
Alerting all pedestrians!
Please evacuate the area right now!
Hm.
What? A robot?
Nice to meet you, Vera.
E-excuse me... how do you know my name?!
My name is Fleta Z.
I'm a fan of yours.
Y-You mean...
Is this the guy who sent you the email, Vera?!
The views will be out of this world...
Fleta Z!
Stop doing things that alarm the people of this planet!
We've been living among them after losing our home!
B-Blue Cop!
Loitering is not permitted in this area. Please evacuate the area immediately. (FIX_THIS)
Heh, so you think this is hiding?
Blue Cop, what have you done...
Hey, you!
You mean me?
Why did you send the email to Vera?
What is it that you really want?
What do you mean?
Like I said earlier... I am her fan.
She is... my hope and light.
A flute?
But it doesn't even have a mouth...?
It's a long story.
He even talks while playing the flute...
I crash landed on an island called Belmeha
On the opposite end of the Earth.
Where I landed,
I couldn't sense any Metal Cardbots nearby.
So I was alone, in the depths of the jungle.
Then, one day... a huge turning point arrived.
Turning point?
I was able to find out more about this planet
thanks to the machine they left behind.
...what's this?
That was when I learned...
...that I wasn't alone.
That there were other Metal Cardbots that had landed on this planet.
So you thought that you would be able to find your fellow Metal Cardbots if you met Vera.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
You're very welcome in that case.
Right, Blue Cop?
Yes.
Let's work together to allow the Metal Cardbots and humans to coexist peacefully.
I refuse.
What do you mean?
I wondered by watching these videos...
Why do these Metal Cardbots have to live in hiding?
I told you.
For us Metal Cardbots to live peacefully on this planet-
We need to have some patience?
I'm not buying it.
Why are we the only ones who have to hide?
What exactly is your point here?
You said you wanted humans and Metal Cardbots to coexist.
So we should be able to show ourselves in public
and not have to hide.
I don't want to hide you either...
Jun.
We have no choice.
What if a giant robot just starts walking around town?
That would send people flying into panic!
So we should do it slowly, over time...
So it was you.
The evil boss trying to keep us imprisoned!
W-What do you mean...
Give me the Metal Breath!
If not... I'll take it by force.
H-hey... hang on!
Beak Arrow!
Blue Cop!
It's just a little scratch. It's nothing.
You shouldn't put yourself in danger like that! Come here!
Leave it to me, Jun!
Alright. Thank you, Mega Trucker!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Hey! Big guys like you don't have to cheat like that!
Hm. You have a point.
You can attack first this time.
What?
Mega Trucker, Mega Power Tackle!
Mega Power Tackle!
Are you running away?
I never said I would let it land!
That's nothing to me!
If you think that was all, you are mistaken!
There's no need to even block!
Mega Trucker, behind you!
Huh? What?
You got to stay focused!
Mega Trucker!
It's not safe here.
Let's take Vera somewhere safe!
Looks like the fun has just begun. I'm gonna stay here.
W-What do you mean?!
You know... I want to see what Jun is guarding.
Guarding... what?
Shadow X! Spinning Cutter!
Spinning... Cutter!
Shadow X, go after him!
An aerial battle! It's just my forte!
Looks like you haven't figured out.
I'm vastly superior in every way. Speed, and cruising distance!
What was that?
Waah!
As well as mobility.
Goodbye, then.
Shadow X!
Shadow X, are you alright?
I'm going to get you! Hang in there!
Because of the Metal Breath,
given to the chosen one by the great Deus Machina,
us Metal Cardbots will never have our freedom.
Now.
Please hand over the Metal Breath.
I'll take over this time!
No, I'll do it!
Hold on. You will only become targets if you don't have a strategy against those arrows of light.
Yes. We have to find out...
a way to break his bow!
Now, hurry!
I will never... give it up!
I'm sorry, what?
You heard me!
This is a token of the friendship between me and Blue Cop!
Jun...
I see...
How touching!
Hm.
So I see... that's what you want to guard.
Come! Wild Guardy!
Huh?!
Who are you?!
Wild Guardy?
What is g...
What is going on now?!