Defeating the Heli-Tornado
It was just a story you made up?!
Yeah! I just said whatever came to me at the time, you know?
But why, Jun?
Oh yeah?! Well, I have a secret weapon that can beat that!
Why did you have to say that!?
It was the only way to get out of that situation...
Don't worry... I'll think of something starting now...
What are you two talking about?
Vera?
It has nothing to do with you.
Oh, really?
Then what's this?
Aah!
Mhm.
Here's the thing.
We were filming a dance by the docks of Mowtown,
when we saw robots fighting. And we got it on video.
And we saw you two there.
What's going on?
Uhh... maybe they were guys that looks like us?
That's right! You know they say there are at least three people in this world that looks exactly like you!
Wearing the same clothes, the same hair, and the same shoes?!
You expect me to buy that story?! Really?!
We're busy!! We gotta go!
Hey, stop running!
What do we do? We can't keep running away from them!
We have to figure out how to take that video away from her!
Actually... she could have saved other copies...
If she uploads it on the Internet, there's no turning back!
Don't worry about a thing! I have a very good plan!
That just makes me feel worse...
Good day everyone.
I would like to talk about the rumors going around regarding a giant robot.
Giant robot?
Yeah!
There have been reported sightings of robots in
waterways, under highways, and flying above the city,
so we would like to... reveal the truth about all these robots!
I'm intrigued right now!
Tune in to our live broadcast this evening at 8!
Remember to subscribe to our channel!
What do you think he's going to say, huh?
I think it may be about that robot we saw last time!
Really?
Oh no, he got us!
I reveal at 8 pm today?! Huh?!
That fool is trying to sabotage the video that we took of the robots!
So tell me... what do we do next?
I'm not sure yet...
Oh no, not again...
Jun! It's all set up.
Woah...
That's awesome! Wow!
It's a jet engine from a plane.
It's been modified so that the wind will be strong enough to blow away a Metal Cardbot.
You're the best, Uncle Edo! That's great!
Uh, don't call me uncle! I'm not that old!
But what will you do with this?
A special training, for you to learn how to defeat Shadow X and its tornado!
Ha! Got it, Jun!
Let me have a go first!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Okay, let's begin!
Alright, setting power to 80%...
Mega Trucker will be harder to blow away since he's heavier than Blue Cop, right?
I'm fine with this little breeze...
Power 90%.
Mega Trucker... open your Shoulder Shield! You must hang on!
Shoulder Shield!
Output 100%!
Still doing good!
Alright, Mega Trucker!
This could work against Shadow X for sure!
It's Shadow X!
So you guys are training? Should've let me know! I would have helped you!
Augh, this is a rental!
You'll pay for the damages!
That's not my problem! Ha!
Shall we set the score once and for all?
Mega Trucker, show us your power!
That fool from yesterday, huh? Ha!
Spinning Cutter!
Hahaha! You thought I'd come from the front where you have your defenses?
Aren't you a real dumbo?
It's not over yet!
Huh? Quite persistent, aren't you?
Gotcha!
Let go of me!
My propeller! How dare you!
Come back, Mega Trucker!
Good job, Mega Trucker. Take a breath.
Jun.
Blue Cop!
Jun. Summon me, please.
But you have to-
I want you to.
Well... alright.
Metal Breath, pickup!
Blue Cop, setup!
Ha! You again?
As long as I need to fight for justice, I will rise up time and time again!
Oh... how heroic!
Shadow X can't fly anymore.
Now's your chance to shoot him!
Alright.
You thought that would stop me from flying? Ha!
No way...
How did he do that...?
Haha! Coming through!
Woah! Not too bad!
Let's make things more interesting!
Heli-Tornado!
Jun! Are you alright?
I'm okay, don't worry!
Just hang in there. Let's get out of here for now.
You can do it! Friends trust each other.
Friends...
You've got it, my friend!
Turn into a police car and run laps around him!
Alright!
What is happening now?!
Blue Cop's police car mode has less air resistance,
so it's less affected by the wind!
Stop that now!
Keep going! Faster!
Wha-! Why are you doing this?!
He must consume a lot of energy to create that kind of tornado!
He won't last for long!
His system is overloaded!
Get him now, Blue Cop!
Megavolt Punch!
Megavolt...
Punch!
Aaaaah!
No way... my Heli-Tornado...
You did it, Blue Cop!
A true friend is someone who doesn't give up when it gets tough.
Someone you can count on.
Friend? Huh... was that what I didn't have...?
Alright... you win.
I will become your underling now...
Not an underling. You're my friend too.
Sealing complete!
Great job!
But what are you going to do now?
About what?
You forgotten? We're going live in the evening!
Oh no!
Rawr!
Ka-boom!
Hohoho!
Woah!
Take that!
So you see? All the robot sightings were actually made up
using custom made miniatures and special effects!
Hey, hang on! We really saw it! It was a robot as big as a house, just flying at us!
Oh, that?
Well, take a look!
Ahem. This robot is a 1 to 1 scale model made to order by a film studio.
What?! A model?! Huh?!
Of course! It's made of styrofoam, so it's very light, you see? Hehehe...
It was in storage, but it flew away in the wind.
So sorry for the commotion...
So everyone, this was our live broadcast,
"I Saw Mysterious Robots Flying Around the Docks!"
Make sure to turn in to our next episode!
And please remember to subscribe!
Urgh... do you think you would get away with those lies?
I will find the evidence no matter what! You better watch out, Jun!