The Invisible Challenger
You can do it!
Not bad at all...
Let's go, Jun!
You can do it!
Goal!!
Haha! How was that?
But... Jun...!
What the...
Augh!
Jun, are you alright?
Okay, bye!
See you, Anna! Bye!
Jun?
Hey, watch where you're going...
What happened...
What was that...
I don't understand what's going on...
Augh!
Am I under some kind of spell?!
Haha! It looks like you're having a bad luck day.
No, it's not just some bad luck.
I'm sure someone must have put a curse on me or something!
Who could it be?
I wish I knew so I could get my hands on them!
What are you guys on about?
Haha!
What's that on your face?!
What happened to your face?
You're one to talk! Have you seen your reflection?
I would say it's an improvement.
What did you say?!
It was you, right?!
Guys, chill! Chill!
Stop! What are you doing?
Looks like we've all been pranked...
Who could have pulled such a prank...
I don't know...
I was just sunbathing in the area while you were in school...
We can get rusty if we just stay in our Metal Card forms...
When I woke up, this had happened...
Did kids in the neighborhood pull this as a prank?
It does seem like a childish prank...
Who are you calling childish?!
What's that?!
Did it go invisible?
Haha!
Show yourself!
You must be a Metal Cardbot like us!
So you figured out, huh?
Now... stealth mode off!
Is it a helicopter?
No, it's a VTOL aircraft. Vertical Take-Off and Landing.
It was camouflaged to blend into its surroundings!
I think there was something like that on Earth. Looks kinda like a lizard?
Chameleon.
Yeah, that's it.
Hey, chameleon helicopter!
Who are you?
You can call me Shadow X.
You drew on their faces, didn't you?!
Yeah, and that's not all!
I was also the one pranking you all day long!
So that was all you!
Why did you do that?
Isn't that obvious?
I. Just.
Don't.
Like.
You!
But what do you mean?
I mean, what have I done to you?
What did you do, Jun?
Try to think what it was.
I did nothing! Hrgh...
That's it! The Metal Breath!
You're using that to seal and summon all of us Metal Cardbots,
like you're the boss or something!
I did no such thing!
The Metal Breath is the sign of the chosen one,
the one who will lead us.
We need to have Jun to coexist peacefully on planet Earth.
Hmph!
I refuse to submit to this silly kiddo.
I want to fly high in the sky and be free!
Hey, don't call me kiddo, you... chameleon helicopter!
I said my name is Shadow X!
Yeah?? Well, that's a dumb name for a plane!
What, you little runt?!
Like apples and oranges...
They must both be five years old...
You want to have it your way?
Then try to seal me!
Then I'll become your underling!
Like the other Cardbots you have too!
Ugh, here we go again... more trouble...
Blue Cop! Let's get him!
Alright!
How do you plan to catch a plane that can fly and become invisible?!
Hey guys!
I'll show that helicopter what we've got!
Oh... I'm sorry!
Stop, stop, you guys!
Where's your energy?! I need you committed on this!
Sorry, Vera...
My dance videos haven't been getting views at all lately!
Please, can you put some passion in it?!
Yeah, sure...
It's the police!
We aren't allowed to be here! Let's get out before we get scolded!
Hang on. I feel like something's not right.
Hey! Vera!
It's gone up that building!
We need to get Shadow X to come down!
Ha! Took you a while to get here!
You're so slow! I was getting bored!
Hey, you...
Blue Cop! Prepare for battle!
Alright.
Metal Breath, pickup!
Blue Cop, setup!
I really hate it when you give commands like that to everyone!
Like, you call the shots here!
Hey, seriously, what did I do?
Quiet now, you blue haired child!
Ha...! Spinning Cutter!
It's a shuriken!
Blue Cop! Burst Shot!
Burst Shot!
Great job, Blue Cop!
One more shot!
Stealth mode, on!
Where did he go?
It's more like a spy than a chameleon...
Where did he go...
Haha! Yaah!
Oh, look out! Don't get distracted there! Haha!
That kid over there... is that Jun?
I think he is!
Is Theo there too?
Hey, what's that robot doing? A strange dance or what?
Quick, get that on video!
Alright!
That sure is going to get some views...
Hahaha! Why don't you look where you're going?
Blue Cop!
Megavolt...
Punch!!
Aah!
I don't get it... how did you find me?!
You only hide yourself by blending into your surroundings.
But hey, looks like you cannot hide your shadow!
Huh? So you think you have won already? Stealth mode, on!
Huh...? Aah!
Blue Cop! Thunderbolt Smash!
Thunderbolt...
Smash!!
What's that?!
What is this wind??
Oh, my phone!
Watch out!
Haha!
Blue Cop! Are you alright?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Hey hey! Don't push yourself too hard.
I think we better take over, Jun!
Not a chance! Heli-Tornado!!
Blue Cop!
Don't worry!
How long do you think you'll last?!
Blue Cop!
Haha! Looks like I have won, blue-haired kiddo!
What a pity I couldn't become your underling...
You keep saying underling...
but I have never made any Metal Cardbot my underling!
After acting so high and mighty, I don't need your excuses!
Well, you go first! Is this kiddo our boss or what?
Jun is to us Metal Cardbots...
A friend!
...A...friend?! I don't get it!
What is that? What in the world are you saying!?
If you don't know, I'll tell you!
But only if you can defeat us!
What?
Let's do a rematch, Shadow X!
I promise I will seal you for sure!
Next time we meet, you are the one that I hit with the Heli-Tornado!
I have a secret weapon that can beat that, alright?!
Huh? A secret weapon?!
I-I'll take you on!
Next time we meet, we will see if your secret weapon
can beat my Heli-Tornado!
I'm not leaving because I'm scared of some "secret weapon".
Don't get all cocky!
Jun!
You alright? What is this secret weapon...
I also want to know what that is.
It's actually...