Mystery of the Police Car Robot!
I was so close...
Hm?
Ah! I'm going to be late for school!
Huh, what's that?
A... robot?
This ends now, Mega Trucker!
You'll have to come with me.
That's what you'd like, Blue Cop.
Wouldn't you?!
Look here, it's not over yet!
You stubborn old truck!
My BMX!
A human boy...?
Ugh! This isn't over!
Stop right there!
What have you done to my bike!!
And where did my helmet go?
Hey, we'll be in middle school next year
and you're still saying,
"I saw a robot! I saw an alien!"
How old are you?
Oh my God, Vance, you're so funny!
I swear I saw it with my own eyes!
A police car transformed into a robot!
Oh really? Where's the evidence, huh?
Uhhh...
Look at my crushed BMX!
Uh... sorry, but it just looks like you fell and broke your own bike.
Ha! You made up a story about a robot for that?! Vance, you're sharp!
You should have made up a more believable story, Jun.
I don't think he's lying.
Huh?
But Anna, what do you mean by that?
You couldn't be thinking that Vance is wrong?!
I just know Jun wouldn't make up a silly story like that.
That's right, Anna! You know you can always trust me!
I think he's probably just mistaken.
Ugh... she didn't believe me either...
I believe you saw the robot, Jun.
Theo!
Security cameras?
If what you said did happen, something must have been caught on video!
Oh, right!
Huh?
Yeah, so when I got here this morning, I saw-
Huh? Jun!
Jun, you're safe and sound!
Stop it! I can't breathe!
I mean I was worried, you know? When I got here, everything was a mess!
I saw your bike and thought something happened to you too!
Hehe... I'm sorry, Edo...
Alright, I'm good now.
Seems like it's all good. We'll be off, then.
Thanks for coming!
Thanks.
Tell me, what brings you guys here?
We need the security footage!
Huh?
Look over here!
Rewind a little bit, please!
It's all covered up...
Yeah, didn't even get the license plate...
If we only had the license plate for the police car-
What would you do with that? Would you go to the police station and ask,
"Is there a car here that transforms into a robot?"
I knew it! You don't believe me either!
Who would believe that story...?
If only there was some other clue...
Hang on! I have this!
I picked it up when all of that happened.
Did the robots leave that behind?
I think it could be.
I think it could be something you could buy in any shop.
Stop fooling around, Edo...
Agh, no! I really can't lift it! It really won't come off at all!
I'll give it a go, then.
I can't move it at all, not an inch!
Nah, you're just kidding! See?
Agh! What's going on?!
That's what I should be asking...
Let's look for a place where a dump truck might be parked...
You guys never give up, do you?
You're trying to impress Anna, aren't you?
Nah, not at all, Theo!
I'll be back soon!
Please tell me you'll throw away that strange watch, will you?
Yeah, I will!
Ugh... guess it wouldn't be easy to find, right?
It might not even be in this town anymore...
Stop it!
Anna?!
Tell us, what's the matter, Anna?
Do you think you are better than us?!
That's not it! You're vandalizing our city without permission!
You just think you're always right!
Why do you care so much about this city? You want to get sprayed too?!
Stop it!
J-Jun?
So you want to play being a hero?
What about the robot?
I'll find it soon!
You sound quite confident!
Agh! I stepped on poop...
Want a taste?!
Get away, get away!
How dare you! Aah!
You fell for it! See you later, Anna!
Jun!
Ta-da!
Not too bad!
You cannot run anymore!
Let's not resort to any kind of violence, you guys!
Shut up!
Hey! You give that back!
This is for tricking me, you fool!
Hey!
Stop struggling!
I said, stop it!
What have you done now?
That's the robot I saw...
Wha...
A robot! Jun was telling the truth!
Come on, that's impossible!
I'm sure it was just a trick!
But I don't think so, Vance...
Listen up! You better not tell anyone about this,
unless you want to be called a liar just like Jun!
Alright...
Aah! What's going on?!
How is this happening?!
Let me introduce myself.
Huh?
I am Blue Cop, from planet Machina.
Blue Cop?
Agh! Does this mean I am actually inside a robot?! Seriously?!
Help, I've been eaten by a robot!!
Huh? Calm down!
Get me out before I am digested!
Digested?
Hang on, please don't push me down! Send me back up!
I am a mechanical lifeform. I don't digest anything.
Oh, really?
It's going to get a little bumpy.
Aah!
My home, Machina planet, was completely annihilated by a giant explosion.
Annihilated?
Since I came to this planet, I have been disguising myself as a car to avoid alarming the natives.
As you say, a tree is best hidden in a forest.
That actually makes sense...
I have to live on planet Earth now.
So I am trying to learn as much about this planet as quickly as I can.
I like this planet very much.
However, there are some of my kind who have not adjusted to life here.
You mean, like that dump truck from yesterday?
It's not the only one.
There are more Metal Cardbots hiding on planet Earth right now.
I only wish to help them, so that they do not cause any harm to the natives of this planet.
If I don't succeed-
Hang on a second! Why are you telling me all this now?!
Because, it looks like the Metal Breath chose you, sir.
What? Metal Breath?
The Metal Breath can only be possessed by the chosen one.
The one who holds the Metal Breath will become the king, the ruler, of all Metal Cardbots.
K-king?
Uh! Pardon my mistake. I mean... the boss? The master?
So, you mean... someone important?
Yes sir! That's correct.
No way! I've never been hall monitor or anything!
Excuse me. Would you please lend me your powers, sir?
Hmm... alright!
On one condition, though!
Yes, sir?
My name is Jun Grant! Call me Jun, not sir!
Yes, Jun!
And one more thing!
My BMX that your friend crashed! I'll need to be compensated for that!