Let's go find the cards to the end of this road / Dallyeogaja kadeureul chajaseo
Together we'll go find them all / heomhan i gil kkeutkkaji
Shout out / Oechyeo!
"Go Metal Cardbot, go!" (Let's go!)
That Metal Breath will help us do it all / himeul moa urin hal su isseo
You and I, let's join forces / neowa na himeul hapchyeo
Battle! Let's move ahead / ssawo nagaja
No one can stop us if we stick together / amudo uril mageul su eopseo (eopseo)
With our courage and our strength / meotjin yonggiwa himeuro
With Metal Breath we'll go / metal beureseuro
Collect all the cards / kadeureul moa
From here till the end / i gil kkeutkkaji
Let's go find the cards to the end of this road / Dallyeogaja kadeureul chajaseo
Together we can find them all / heomhan i gil kkeutkkaji
Shout out / oechyeo!
"Go Metal Cardbot, go!" (Let's go!)
That Metal Breath will help us do it all / himeul moa urin hal su isseo
Let's go! / Chuldong!
Metal Cardbot, go / Metal Cardbot