The Vagabond in the Sky
W-What is going on now?!
Have you also been sealed by the Metal Breath?
No.
I see you want freedom too, just like me.
Nice to meet y-
I am nothing like you! Make no mistake!
I will soon be the king of the Metal Cardbots!
I see no reason to fight with an unsealed Metal Cardbot.
I will be back for the Metal Breath.
So be prepared!
Wait up!
This is all your fault!
You are too weak to be the owner of the Metal Breath!
That's why Blue Cop was beaten!
I think you've gone too far, Wild Guardy.
Crest?
Jun. You said the Metal Breath was a token of friendship.
Yes. It is!
If you are truly united in your friendship, you'll be able to seal Fleta Z.
Then, you can prove what you said was true.
Wait up, Crest! I still have questions for you!
What is the matter with him...
Anyway... what should we do with her...?
...Ha, everyone, get in line... I'll sign autographs...
So you're saying... you sent Vera home safe?
Yeah. She didn't see that much, so I think we could make up an excuse.
What about Crest?
We still can't reach him.
We went to his house, but it seems like he's not home yet.
However... Crest knew all about the Metal Cardbots.
What?
He knew everything about them but didn't tell!
He was mocking us all this time!
We did act like we didn't know too...
I'm sure in time we'll get a chance to talk it through properly...
Jun. The emergency treatments are done.
Everyone was attacked where their defense was the weakest.
Does that mean he's that skilled at the bow?
Or maybe that it knows all of our weaknesses?!
But hey! We've never even met the guy!
Yeah. I didn't recognize his face...
Neither did I. But I think... I've heard rumors.
What rumors?
Fleta Z. A roaming vagabond, living as free as the wind.
Also known as the Hunter in the Wilderness.
I heard he does not like to show himself to others, and lives alone,
enjoying the freedom.
You're told to be careful if you hear a flute playing out of the blue.
It means Fleta Z is aiming at you from afar.
Edo! You startled us!
I-I'm sorry. I was wondering if it would sound like this, haha...
C-Could it... still be lurking somewhere nearby?!
He's probably looking for Jun, since he wants to take the Metal Breath.
But he probably doesn't know I'm here!
If so, he'll surely try to find Jun through Vera.
Try calling Vera.
I don't even know her number!
I'll call her right now!
Hello?
Vera? Are you free to talk?
Where are you right now?
Why? Why do you need to know? Ugh.
Anyway, get this, Anna!
I'm going to meet the person who sent me the email!
They want to hear my full story where we'll not be disturbed.
I think she's meeting with Fleta Z!
What?
Vera! Where are you?!
Jun?
Uh, yeah... the park near 7th Avenue. They wanted to meet here.
No, I don't know why they want to meet here.
They just told me to wait here, so I'm here!
Aah! L-Look at that!
You want me to run away? Why should I do that?
Aah!
W-What's that?!
Run!
W-what's-
Huh?
Sorry I'm late.
Aah! I remember you!
You're the robot that appeared at the bus stop earlier!
Alerting all pedestrians. This is an emergency.
Please evacuate immediately!
Officer, over here! This robot is-
H-Hey, we need to get out of here!
Get away from there!
Now that's enough, Fleta Z!
We will not let you carry on like this.
I was going to ask Ms. Vera some questions.
But I see you showed up before I had to.
Thank you for making this easier.
Not a chance!
You're not getting the Metal Breath ever, do you understand?!
Not even if it means your friends getting hurt?!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Phoenix Fire, setup!
Block the arrows with Water Splash!
What was that... it's a skill I've never seen before...
Fleta Z and the ground are all wet!
Mega Ambler, it's your turn!
Send the Forceps Shock towards the wet ground!
Got it!
Forceps Shock!
We did it!
I'll have to take a strategic retreat...
Come on! He's flying away again!
How strange.
What is it?
He was so cocky then. But so disorganized this time.
Theo? What's up? Is everything okay?
We found out Fleta Z's secret!
Fleta Z analyzed every single video that came up on the Internet.
And also wrote comments on all of them!
"Shadow X's weakness is its propeller.
When that is under attack, its mobility decreases."
"Mega Trucker is heavily reliant on his shield.
Aim for its blind spots for an easy win."
Hm. Fleta Z is a strategic type, huh?
First, analyzing the opponent, and only fighting when they are confident of winning.
Hm. I think I know how we can defeat Fleta Z, ha!
Jun!
I know where Fleta Z is!
Alright! Let's go right now!
Do you think Jun will pull it off?
We'll find out soon enough.
Hm?
So you managed to find me.
Fleta Z!
The Metal Breath is not some tool to take away the Metal Cardbots' freedom!
Please listen to me!
I don't need to listen. I will not change my mind.
I don't want to have to hurt anyone, either.
Just hand over the Metal Breath, now!
I won't let you take it so easily, you hear?!
Blue Cop, Burst Shot!
Burst Shot!
Beak Arrow!
Transform into a car and dodge!
Got it!
You can't keep running away!
Don't worry! The real fight begins now!
Blue Cop!
Again?!
Now! Shadow X!
What's this?!
What do you think?! A surprise attack!
Spinning Cutter!
Great job!
Mega Ambler! Forceps Shock!
Now you can't use your bow!
Not a chance!
Come back!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Mega Power Tackle!
You have underestimated me.
Vulture Wings!
Making my analysis useless with continued switchups.
And fighting in close proximity so I can't use my arrows.
Great strategy indeed.
However.
I am strong even without the analysis or my bow.
I just did all that because I have a type A personality.
I get it that you are strong!
But you will never take the Metal Breath away!
I see you have a stubborn personality.
I became friends with the Metal Cardbots through the Metal Breath!
This is where peaceful coexistence with the people of Earth begins!
It's all very nice to hear, but...
you are just controlling them as you please.
I don't control anyone!
We are just working together for a common goal!
If we work together, we can defeat any enemy, you understand?!
Now Dexter, it's your turn!
Spear Thrust!
A surprise attack from underground... not bad-
Blue Cop! Let's finish the battle now!
Infinity...
Force...
Break!!
Friendship...
working together...
I'll see if that's true...
Awesome!
Metal Cardbot, Chain Shot!
Fleta Z...
seal!
We did it, Jun!
Yeah! All thanks to you!
Hey guys...!
I'm fine over here! Don't worry about me!
Mega Trucker! Are you alright?!
Yeah... I'm okay!
Mega Trucker!!
Don't you think this is proof enough?
That Jun actually has the right to hold the Metal Breath?
I am not ready to accept him.
Haha... you're too strict.
Perhaps the time has come for the final showdown,
Jun...