Heavy Battle
Attention, citizens!
Landfill #30 is off limits!
Uhh... can we even have a look?! C'mon! Aww!
It looks like a giant piece of candy...
It could be a magma rock...?
I know what that is. That's Machinasium.
What?
What?! Machinasium?!
What is that?
It's a metal found only on Machina planet.
The core metal that is the heart of Metal Cardbots is also made of Machinasium.
What is now doing on Earth?
Shadow X! Please do a patrol!
Leave it to me!
A shining stone has filled the entire island!
There's a hole on top! I'll take a look!
Okay! Thank you!
Shadow X!
Jun! Let's hurry!
What was that just now?! There was something like a laser?!
We are... assessing the situation, so please calm down!
Emergency support vehicle passing through!
Please! Allow us!
Support? But we haven't heard anything-
There appears to be a crashed helicopter in that landfill!
We don't have time! Please, let us through!
[crowd murmurs]
Are you okay, Shadow X?!
Hey! What happened here!
I didn't see that coming at all...
What a surprise, right...?
Who did this to you?!
It was Heavy Iron...
What?!
Hahaha!
Do you find this funny, Black Hook?!
Just as I expected!
Heavy Iron is planning to use the Star Crown to reconstruct this planet!
What do you mean, "reconstruct"?
And what is the Star Crown?
Let me explain.
The Star Crown is one of the hidden treasures of Machina planet.
Using that, you can transform your planet into a copy of Machina planet.
I stole it and brought it here... but Heavy Iron took it from me!
So the huge mass of Machinasium that just appeared on Earth... was created by the Star Crown?
Yes. You can call it the Seed of Machinasium.
If you don't do anything, it will absorb all the heat on this planet to multiply itself.
And what will happen then?
I believe you can work that out yourself.
If all heat on planet Earth disappears... it might mean that its metal will disappear!
Its magnetic field disappears, allowing radiation from space to burn down on the Earth's surface!
Anna and Theo, you've worked it out!
So... you mean to say that...
That means all life on Earth... just as we know it... could go extinct?!
Oh no! Jun! You have to seal him up right away!
Shadow X!
You can't let Heavy Iron have it his way!
I like it here on Earth!
I have taken emergency measures.
Thank you. Shadow X!
Please come back!
Guys. I will go inside that dome!
Huh?! No way, it's dangerous!
You don't even know what it's like inside the dome!
I still have to go! It's my duty as the owner of the Metal Breath!
Hey, calm down, Jun! You don't have to carry everything on your shoulders!
You can leave these things to the grownups, you know?
I won't!
Calm down, Jun!
Heavy Iron is also a Metal Cardbot that escaped from Machina planet!
He's no different from our friends!
And you know I will not leave anyone behind!
But... I'm worried about you!
...fine. Have it your way.
Thank you, Mister Edo!
Why'd you stop calling me Uncle?!
Thank you, Edo. We promise to protect the planet.
I'll be waiting for you!
Take care of yourself, Jun!
Okay! I'll be off then!
But what is your plan now?
You would get struck down if you fly over there!
Well... there's one thing we can try!
Oh! Look there!
Oh! Seems like an ambulance is finally getting here!
Oh, wow! It looks like the ambulance that entered the landfill!
Huh? Anna and Theo?
And the owner of the car repair shop?
Over here!
What were you all doing over there?!
Huh?
Jun... please come back safe...
Here!
Yes!
Is this the inside of the dome?
It feels like we're back on Machina planet...
Welcome, kiddo.
How's the brat who recieved my welcome back there?
Heavy Iron!
The Star Crown!
Oh... you mean, this?
You can take it if you want it.
Dexter! Spiral Ray!
Spiral...
Too slow.
Dexter!
Be careful! It's the super beam that hit me!
But he barely lifted a finger!
Of course. He needed the power of using the Star Crown!
I'll wait while you choose your next fighter.
We have more than enough time.
Okay, guys! Let's attack all at once!
Alright!
Heh.
Buster Gallon, setup!
Twin Vulcan!
Fleta Z! Setup!
Beak Arrow!
Our attacks aren't working!
Then we have to try something strong!
Fleta Z!
Vulture Wings!
Hahaha.
Not even a scratch-
Augh!
It's a throne!
Mega Ambler?!
The throne that the Star Crown has made is releasing Machinasium energy.
It's making long range attacks useless.
Then we have to go up close!
Jun! I think it's my turn!
Phoenix Fire!
What about me?!
Sorry. Hang in there!
Water Splash!
Buffalo Crush! Setup!
Buffalo Moonsault!
Buffalo...
Moonsault!
Buffalo Crush!
It's your turn, Blue Cop!
Megavolt...
Punch!
It's no use!
Do it now, Phoenix Fire!
I told you, it's no use!
I don't care!
Go for it, Phoenix Fire!
Burning...
Hammer!
Well done!
Heh. My goal was to destroy the throne!
Look out, Phoenix Fire!
Heh. You've always been pretty annoying.
Nothing's changed.
You can't even leave a scratch on me!
Wild Guardy!
Wild...
Slash!
I see.
Look here, Earthling child- I mean, Jun!
Send me!
Black Hook!
I have a score to settle with him. Now's my chance!
Alright, then!
Black Hook, setup!
Hey!
Hey, bookie boy!
Wild Guardy! Come back!
Black Hook. You've become enslaved to this kiddo, I see.
He only means that anyone can turn from an enemy into a friend!
Black Hook! Captain's Cannon!
Captain's...
Do it.
Cannon!
Is he done?!
Don't say that, you'll jinx it!
I see. As powerful as ever.
I told you!
He's too stubborn!
So. Shall I finish it off now?
That doesn't look good.
Send me out there!
Mega Trucker, Shoulder Shield!
Heh! Not a chance, Heavy Iron!
Do not push yourself.
We'll be helping you again this time!
Yes. Don't worry.
We'll help you this time!
Me too!
Oh, my! What a beautiful sight!
I will give it all I've got!
Okay! Let's join forces!
Stop. I think you should stay behind.
You have to protect Jun in case something happens!
Don't worry! We won't lose this time!
We'll always...
...be with you!
...okay.
Hey, guys!
Energy Full Charge!
Ultra... Mega Power... Shield!!
Heavy...
Buster...
Cannon!!
OMG, what's that?!
Jun!!
Jun? What do you mean?!
We did it...?
I told you... we were going to win...
Haha... I guess I'm done now...
Hey, guys...?
So, do you understand...
the difference in power between me and you brats?!
Soon... this will become our second home planet.
The Earth will generate an endless supply of core metal.
And I will save our people of steel from the threat of extinction!