Metal Breath Gets Stolen
The Metal Breath?
The Metal Breath is the legendary treasure from Machina planet.
Now it's on the minor planet...
I know what I saw!
I'm sure that child's bracelet is the very one Deus Machina left behind.
I saw with my own eyes, Buster Gallon!
The child from this planet was commanding the Star Guardian like a minion!
Black Hook, what I want to know is-
Call me Captain.
Yeah, uh, whatever... Captain.
What is it, Buster Gallon?
Ahem. What I want to know is... what do you plan to do once you have taken the Metal Breath?
Hmm. What do you think you would do?
Well, the one who has the Metal Breath can rule all Metal Cardbots.
I'd use that power to conquer the universe!
Then we can divide it among us three, of course.
That sounds fun.
Yes. That is how it should be!
But the child has Blue Cop, a Star Guardian by his side!
It will not be easy.
Is there a way around it?
Of course there is. You can leave it to me.
Mom! Where are the towels?!
I told you to take them when you were going up!
I'm busy cleaning! You take them yourself!
Augh, Mom!
Ugh. Fine.
Ugh. Don't get into the habit of doing this.
I'll leave the towel here!
I love you, Mom!
Ugh. Save it.
Hmph.
Aaaiyah!
Aah! What are those animals?!
What, Mom?! What is it?!
There are some strange mice!
Huh?
Here-
Uh... Dearie, look out for the mice!
I'll check downstairs!
What? Did you say mice, darling?
Ah, feeling fresh!
Oh, my Metal Breath!
...uh... Heavy Iron...
...sealing... I'm gonna seal it...
Wha... where did it...
When did it drop there?
Aaah!
Stop right there!
W-what just happened?!
Waugh!
The Mini Gallons have succeeded in stealing the Metal Breath.
Although... it did take them some time.
Well done, Buster Gallon!
Heheh. Bring it over quickly!
Hm? Good morning, Jun-
Give it back!
Where did they go?
Uh, what's all the racket this morning?
Where are you going?!
Oh!
Sorry, Mom!
Hey! What's going on?!
Gotcha!
Uh... Jun, what are you doing here?
Did you forget that we were doing our homework together?
That's not important right now! The Metal Breath has been st-
Oh? Where did they go?!
The Metal Breath...
Stop right there!
...The Metal Breath got stolen?!
How did it happen? Did it get stolen really-
It's those mini things over there! They took Black Hook's friend!
Juuuuun!!
I said stop!
Just a little more!
Just a little more, Jun!
Stop!
I got them!
Anna, you're the best!
I, wait! Stay still!
I... can't hold them... any longer! Do something!
Anna, are you alright?!
Ow... I'm really sorry, Jun...
It's okay, I think... we've driven them to right direction!
Luckily they are going to Mr. Edo's car repair shop!
Huh? They are hiding in here?
Yes! So please help me look for them too!
Come on guys, I need your help!
Those pesky things... even if they came in here, it will take some time to find them...
They're just going round and round in the same spot.
Are they broken?
That's impossible!
Where is this?
A... car repair shop in the outskirts of Mowtown.
I'll go take a look.
Where are you going?!
I'll come with you!
Hm. Got a bad feeling about this.
You rats!
Great job!
Those tiny things have some guts!
I got an idea. Listen carefully!
Aha! I got it!
Metal Cardbot, setup!
Trying to steal us? You have some guts.
Yeah. They sure do.
Let's give them some attention.
I agree. Shall we get them to spill the whereabouts of Black Hook's lair?
They are leaving again!
No more chasing for me...
Hand over the little ones!
Wha...?
Buffalo Crush! Just barging in like that won't solve anything!
Huh?
Aah! My little mini-mes!
What's happened here...
Huh... uh, uh... I don't know...
Hey! What are you here for anyway?
Buffalo Crush! Let's retreat for now!
No retreat! I'm taking both Jun and the Metal Breath!
Yaaah!!
Buffalo Crush!
It's revenge for the little ones!
You did that to them!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Dexter, setup!
Dexter, Helix Sword!
Helix Sword!
We have to make a hole in that axe! Spear Thrust!
What? Hole?
Spear Thrust!
Buffalo Crush, step aside please!
Chest Cannon!
You better get going, Buffalo Crush!
I can still fight!
Now is not the time!
You need to know when to stop, Buffalo Crush!
Black Hook!
I'll admit, today was a defeat for the Black Crew!
The Black Crew?
B... Black Crew?
I'm not your underling! I reject that name!
And you're not black, by the way! You're blue!
Silence!
I told you to call me Captain!
I better stay put. Things are getting messy.
Ahem. Anyways! The legacy of Deus Machina will be mine!
The legacy of Deus Machina?
If you mean the Metal Breath, that's a misunderstanding!
Why should I believe you?
Ah! All done.
Hey Wild Guardy, your sword is as good as-
Uhh.... that's great...!
Right, yeah...!
Hey, kids...
Mister Edo...
I hope you can explain this.
Uh, well...