The Final Battle
The Earth will generate an endless supply of core metal.
And I will save our people of steel from the threat of extinction!
Is that your goal?
Yes. It is my dream to reconstruct Machina planet!
And you don't care if the people and creatures of this planet disappear for that dream?!
You know there has to be a little sacrifice for a bigger goal!
A little sacrifice...?!
Huh?
We're all doing our best with our lives!
No one should be allowed to put that to an end!
Jun!
No! I will never give up!!
I will make sure to protect my people...
and the Metal Cardbots!
It's happening again...
Jun! Unleash the forbidden power!
That is the only way to defeat him!
Wait!
A power sealed in the Metal Breath could be dangerous for him!
Haha! What do you mean?
Jun!
We have faced together countless ventures... and beat them all!
There is no danger I can't overcome when I'm with you!
Okay.
We haven't given up either!
Woah, guys!
There's one last card you can use.
You must not forget us!
We're always together!
Yes. The battle starts now!
Let's show the warmth in Jun's heart...
to that big oaf over there!
Jun... Blue Cop... let's use everyone's power!
Oh, wow... look at that!
Jun's spirit and determination to never give up has combined the spirit of the Metal Cardbots to awaken the forbidden power!
Coming together...
...as one spirit!
Ultimate Armour... setup! (FX-ua)
All the power of Machina planet...
was coursing through our veins...
Jun... are you alright?
Mhm!
Let's show everyone!
Edge Acceleration!
That's nothing for us!
Mega Power Shield! (FX-megaTrucker shake bold)
Spear Thrust! (FX-dexter shake bold)
Captain's Cannon! (FX-blackHook shake bold)
Continue to push ahead!
Wild Raid! (FX-wildGuardy shake bold)
Not too bad!
Twin Vulcan! (FX-busterGallon shake bold)
Spinning Cutter! (FX-shadowX shake bold)
Forceps Crush! (FX-megaAmbler shake bold)
Buffalo Moonsault! (FX-buffaloCrush shake bold)
Hammer Blaze! (FX-phoenixFire shake bold)
Vulture Wings! (FX-fletaZ shake bold)
Aagh! Not a chance this will work!
We are not done yet!
Lightning... (FX-shake bold)
Over... (FX-shakexl bold)
Strike!! (FX-shakexxl bold ua)
How dare you...
Incredible! This is the forbidden force-
A-aagh! (FX-shake phoenixFire)
Jun! Are you okay?!
I-I'm okay!
Aah! Blue Cop!
Agh!
What is it, Jun?!
The Metal Breath! It's starting to burn me up...!
Is the forbidden power going rogue?! Take off the Metal Breath!
No! We strike back!
Please, Jun!
No, Blue Cop!
I can't!
Not until I have him sealed!
But...
If we stop now, everything we did will go to waste!
The way we all met!
The way we became friends!
You know me well!
I will never give up!
For a world where humans and Metal Cardbots will live together!
Let's do it, Blue Cop!
Do you think this planet will accept you?!
You're wrong!!
This planet will be remade in our image!
You humans will not survive!
No!
Humans will survive no matter what!
Because they have been kind and wise!
And they have accepted us!
Shut up!!
Infinite... (FX-ua shake)
Punish!! (FX-ua shakexxl)
Huh?! Jun!
Hey, guys!
Don't get any closer, please!
Ugh... the Star Crown is still alive...
As long as I have it... my dream will...
Huh...?!
Blue Cop!
Setup!
Seems like... you still haven't learned your lesson.
Heh. Looks like you didn't hear me.
I will never give up!
Infinity...
Force...
Megavolt... (FX-shake)
Punch!! (FX-shakexl blueCop)
Iron Cannon!!
Metal Cardbot...
Change Up!
My dream was to bring back to life my home planet...
Why do you want to stop me...?
Because it is my dream to live together with my friends!
I always wanted to protect my dream too!
I see...
I've been defeated...
Heavy Iron...
Seal up!
Oh no!
Oh no! What happened to Jun?! And the Metal Cardbots?!
It's all my fault! I should have stopped him!
...can you tell me what happened to Jun?
Jun...
I just can't believe it...
What's wrong, guys?
Well, you see... the thing is that-
What?! Jun?!
You're alright?!
All thanks to my good friends!
Blue Cop!
Oh you little- I was so so worried about you!
I thought we lost you over there! Jun!
I'm sorry... but...
Here, take this! I'm back safe and sound.
Oh, thank you...
Here you go...
Eugh...
I'm so glad you're okay!
Jun!
What are you doing...?
It seems like a brave police officer managed to go inside and rescue the boy.
Please, can I have an interview?
That evening... we were given a huge scolding.
Don't you ever do that again!
Huh?
Jun?
Uh, uh... Mom... so... uh-
It didn't hurt too bad, Mom!
I'm sure the scar will be gone in a week!
Listen to me!
I'll never forgive you if you put yourself in danger again!
and I won't let you play with your friends ever again!
What?! That hurt!
That's a little too much!
Hey, Yuri! Please forgive Jun!
Quiet!
...okay...
I'm really sorry.
I know you just wanted to help your friends.
But do you know how worried I was?
I'll never do that again, Mom...
We also took care of the aftermath in secret.
According to Buster Gallon, most of the Machinasium turned into ordinary rock when the Star Crown was destroyed.
However... it seemed like small and dense pieces are still alive.
Ugh. We'll never find all of them!
Shut up! Let's see who can collect the most!
I'm sure I'll win this!
No, you won't!
Vera, who saw what happened that day, seems to believe that the dome was a base for an alien invasion.
Well... she's kinda right!
Ha! I saw it on TV!
It was just a swelling of different underground elements together with methane!
Vance, you're too smart!
You fool! They-
Hello, Vera!
We'll be off then!
Jun! You saw it, didn't you?
Aliens?
They probably exist! Space is huge, right?
According to the Drake equation, there are 25,000 planets in this galaxy with alien lifeforms!
Jun! We have a situation!
Huh?! I know that voice!
See you later!
Hey, wait!
And now... we are cleaning up the warehouse together!
Since we have some huge guys joining us, we have to get on Edo's good side!
Although... this big guy doesn't seem to have opened up.
This stain's just not getting off...
Disappointing, Blue Cop. I'll get that out!
Why the long face over there?!
Cleaning up after humans? That's a shame.
I can't believe you're doing this.
This is how we clean up on Earth. Why not give it a try?
Do you really think I'll ever stoop that low?
Haha! I think he's just bad at it!
Say what?
What a tough stain-
I'll show you that I'm not just good, I'm better than all of you!
Using that much force is not gonna work!
Why don't you use this-
Woah, woah!
Fire is the best when it comes to stains! Haha!
Phoenix Fire! We need you here!
Huh?!
No, you troublemakers! What are you up to?!
Ugh...
Jun! We have an emergency!
Let's go, everyone!
You won't get away this time!!
Phew! So we had to run all the way here...
Yeah... and even I've run away with you.
Isn't that proof that you've become our friend?
Look at the sky, Heavy Iron!
Hmm?
Machina planet doesn't exist anymore! So...
you have to live here on Earth with us!
Jun?
You know that's a painful thought for him.
But...
Huh?
You never know how many Metal Cardbots are still out there in the stars...
Lost in the vast universe...
Let's make it our role to give them a warm welcome when they arrive here on Earth!
Heavy Iron! Let's create a world where Metal Cardbots and humans can coexist and be friends!
What do you say?
I think... I'm starting to understand you.
Let's work together. For the future of Metal Cardbots.
Thank you, Heavy Iron!
Well done.
So we've made yet another incredible friend.
Can you quit that look in your eyes now?
Hmph.
Woah! Now you look more reasonable!
Right?!
Deus Machina...
Was this the reason...
That you chose him?