0 Seconds to Destruction
According to the Center of Astronomy and Space,
a meteor at about 300 ft in size is approaching the Earth.
In today's press conference, Mowtown Mayor Mr. Jack
said that no damage is expected as the meteor will burn up in the atmosphere.
Anna, is that why your dad called you?
Yeah... he said it will be a rare sight in the sky,
so we should try not to miss it!
Good. It wasn't anything big.
I was so scared we had been discovered!
This is footage of the meteorite captured by the Lunar Reconnaissance Orbiter.
That's...
What's wrong, Blue Cop?
That's not a meteorite.
It's an escape pod from Machina planet.
Huh??
What? No... you're right!
I wonder who's on it?
Hope it's not a troublemaker like you!
What did you say?!
Now is not the time to squabble.
If that's not a meteorite...
It means a giant piece of metal 300 ft wide will fall on us since metal doesn't burn up in the atmosphere!
The town will be blown away without a trace!
What?!
So, if there's someone inside, can you make it stop or change direction before it hits?
Based on the news,
it will soon enter the Earth's orbit.
But there's no sign of it slowing down.
Oh no! Is it broken?
Is the guy in there asleep or something?
Oh, so you guys sleep too?
These guys even talk in their sleep and snore!
Look at this.
This is the drop point of the meteorite according to an amateur astronomer.
It's in the middle of Mowtown!
The estimated time of impact is 2:51 PM.
Not even two hours left!
I'll ask my dad to issue an evacuation order right away!
But wait, Anna! What are you going to tell your dad?
That's not a meteorite, but a Metal Cardbot spaceship,
and it will fall on us soon!
Even so... revealing this will be a problem.
Yeah! Who would even believe you?
They'll just say it's a tall tale and ignore it.
Should we think of a more effective plan?
What do you think we should do, then?
Just sit and watch everyone in Mowtown disappear without a trace?
There's one thing that comes to my mind.
Do you think he'll believe us?
We don't have time! Let's hurry!
Anna and Theo have gone into the city hall, Jun.
Alright, Blue Cop! Come home!
Got it.
How's it going?
All done.
It's ready now.
Great. We're connected to the satellite. We can communicate with the pod.
Wow, Uncle Edo! You're the best!
Rgh... don't call me Uncle!
Ahem.
Notice to the escape pod! Decelerate immediately and prepare for landing!
I repeat! Decelerate immediately! Prepare for landing right away!
An evacuation order?
That's not a meteorite! It's a spaceship from Machina planet-
No, Anna, no...
You said you were an amateur astronomer, right?
Could you explain exactly what my daughter is saying?
My analysis showed that the meteorite consists of Hafnium and Zirconium materials with char used in the outer shell of the space vehicle,
so there is the concern that it will not burn up in the atmosphere, crashing into the Earth as it falls!
Are you sure?
I heard it from Blue Cop! It must be true!
Blue Cop?
It's... the name of my friend's horse!
I don't get it. A horse told you?
No no no! It's the name of a kind robot called Metal Cardbot.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Daddy!
This meteorite is being observed by the space institutes around the world,
so don't worry! We don't want to cause widespread panic, right?
Hey, Anna!
Uh... have a nice day!
How could he... he didn't even want to listen to a word I said!
Theo here. Mission failed.
We just have an hour left! You hide in the basement with Anna!
And the escape pod?
No word from it!
Hey, are they hearing what you are saying?
It's a code used by all Metal Cardbots.
If they can't hear it...
I think... their communicator might be broken!
Then the pod will crash, and it will be over for all of us.
No way!
Isn't there something else we can try?
Let's try sending a control protocol.
What's that?
It's a program that allows us to remotely control the escape pod.
We're connected.
I will change its course now.
That's great!
The meteorite changed its course...
The space center reported it seems to be accelerating, but the cause could not be confirmed.
Where is it going to fall?
That's the escape pod.
The drop point will be about 500 km southwest of Mowtown.
That is... above the ocean.
Then...
It's a success, Uncle Edo!
We did it, Jun!
Mayor Jack held an emergency conference to announce that the meteorite approaching Earth
is falling into the sea about 3 miles southwest of Mowtown.
Haha, they did it Anna! The meteorite changed its course-
Anna?
What? Anna?
Is that...
It's getting closer and closer!
Hang on, I can't hear-
What's... that...?
Did they separate the escape pod?
Separate, you said?
I think they took off a part of the pod to change its course?
B-b-what?!
Where is that falling?!
What?! A residential area in Mowtown?!
Anybody home?
Oh! So it was here!
It will land in about 10 more minutes.
Anna...
There is no time to lose!
Please, somebody help me!
But where's Anna...
Found her!
Mega Trucker, please help!
Leave it to me!
Anna!
Jun!
What are you doing here?
I left your birthday gift!
Birthday gift?!
There's no time for all that chatter!
10 minutes to impact.
We have to think of a way to stop it!
I think I could make your shield even stronger with a little tricking.
Really? Then let's do it right away!
It's not that easy. The stronger the shield, the more energy it consumes, you know?
Your shield!
What about my shield?
Now it's time to put everyone's strength together!
This will sync your power generators.
Then, you can use Mega Trucker's shield to create a barrier shield!
Great! Send me all your energy right now!
Phoenix Fire, do you think you can handle all of the energy?
I wonder... what if it fails?
You must not think that way! I believe in you guys!
I know you will keep our town safe by working all together!
Don't worry, we'll do it!
Y-Yes! Let's do our best!
I believe in you too.
Jun. You are our friend.
I believe in you too!
Thank you.
Let's prove them right for having faith in us.
Alright. Everyone, get ready!
Okay!
We are ready!
Energy full charge!
Blue Cop?!
It's okay, Mega Trucker! I got your back!
I'll help, too!
Me too!
Guys! You're doing great!
Everyone, give it all the energy you've got!
Ultra... Mega...
Power Shield!!
You did it...
Are you alright, Mega Trucker?
This is nothing! I'm fine!
Jun...
Anna...
I want you to know, I'll promise I will keep the Metal Cardbots a secret.
Thank you, Anna... and...
Sorry I lied all this time.
No, no! I'm sure I would have done the same if I were you.