The Great Showdown! Giant VS Giant!
Right turn at the next intersection, please.
Okay...
Crest! Don't you think you can tell us now?
Yeah! Where are we going?
I told you this is a mystery tour to a surprise location.
So we'll find out when we get there.
Oh well... Crest is all about the secrets, I see.
He's just serious, intelligent, and can keep his mouth shut.
Yeah, yeah! The opposite of someone we know!
Really? Who's that, now?
Don't let that get to you, Jun.
And what do you mean by that, Blue Cop?!
Here we are.
Our destination was Mowtown's landfill...
I've never been here before...
Now... tell us why you've brought us here.
Sure. It's this.
Here in the map?
Yeah.
What's the blinking thing?
The signal from a GPS transmitter attached to Heavy Iron.
Heavy Iron?!
Do you know what you're doing?! Heavy Iron isn't to be messed with!
Mhm. I heard from Wild Guardy.
You knew, and you still brought us here?!
So you mean... Heavy Iron is here right now?!
Yeah. Over there.
Waah!
That's too close!
What if we get caught!
Don't worry! He hasn't moved an inch since I started tracking him.
Oh... so he can't move due to the injuries from the last battle...
So... you mean Heavy Iron is deep asleep because he's recovering?
Yes. Us Metal Cardbots have a self recovering function powered by nanomachines.
But... it's not enough to just stay still like that.
It takes a lot of energy to heal a single wound.
Energy?
Metal Cardbots are like humans too. We get hungry even if we've been lying still.
I wonder... what do you guys eat?
We eat all kinds of fuel! Gasoline, electricity, methane...
A landfill like this is full of methane gas.
Really? You eat methane?
Sure.
It's a simple pleasure, but it tastes so good.
He can't do much while in recovery, so now is the best chance to seal him.
Okay, Blue Cop. We gotta seal him before he makes a move.
Metal Breath, pickup!
What's... that?!
Isn't that a ship with sails?!
Is that...
Black Hook!
You know him?
Yes.
He was a famous pirate in Machina planet.
Many Star Guardians have gone after him, but were beaten instead.
Aah! Stop it! You'll wake Heavy Iron!
Hahaha!
You've been hiding in this trash heap! You fit right in, Heavy Iron!
Ah...
Where is the Star Crown? My stolen treasure!
Hmph.
It's been a while, Black Hook.
The Star Crown is safe with me.
Glad to hear!
Nothing a pirate likes more than to loot and plunder!
You're just to come at me! (FIX_THIS)
One was bad enough, but now there are two of them?!
Jun, what do we do?
Don't worry. It might be a good thing.
Jun's right, guys.
We watch them fight it out and seal the one who loses. I wonder who will it be...
Like fishing in troubled waters.
Everyone, run!
Jun!
And who are you?!
Hey. You're the kid that was controlling Blue Cop.
That kid?!
You mean that Earthling child is a master of a Star Guardian?!
Don't be ridiculous.
I-Is that...
The Metal Breath?! Legendary treasure of Deus Machina?!
Give it to me!!
Not a chance! Don't even think about it!
Blue Cop, setup!
Yaah!
Jun. Are you alright?
I'm okay...
Here you are, Blue Cop.
So you are the surviving Star Guardian...
Yes. Even if my home planet no longer exists,
the will of Deus Machina is engraved in my memory circuit.
What a joke!
Black Hook. Let's settle our score some other day.
You want a truce, huh?
Guys, let's get out of here!
Come on, let's go!
I'll take up the offer, however...
The treasure is all mine! Raah!
He can't fight them both...
Jun! I'm okay!
Blue Cop, we'll confuse them! Run!
Got it!
You won't get away so easily.
I'm okay. You gotta go now!
Be careful, Jun!
I'll admit you have guts, kiddo!
Now, hand over the Metal Breath!
What if I don't do it?!
Shadow X, setup!
Yeah! Haha!
Shadow X, Spinning Cutter from the sky!
Spinning Cutter!
It hurts!
Huh?
Heli-Tornado!
Where is the kiddo?!
Hey Captain, I'm not over there!
You annoying little fruit fly!
Please, hang in there Shadow X!
Don't worry, I got it!
Blue Cop, we are on our way too!
We have to seal Heavy Iron as soon as possible!
Got it!
Enough with the games!
Blue Cop!
Not looking so smart, are you kiddo?
Wild Guardy, we need to hurry!
Got it!
I'll end you once and for all!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Wild Guardy, setup!
I'll take you on!
You'll pay for this wound a hundred times over!
Not interested!
Start playing fair and show yourself!
I'd hadn't won perfect? What a joke! (FIX_THIS)
There you are!
Where have you gone, Earthling child?!
Where is that pirate going next?
Listen, Edo! We need to follow them!
Uh-oh, alright! Guys, hang on tight!
Nice one! Wild Slash!
Wild...
Slash!
I would like to stay and play, but this ends now.
I still need to get some rest.
Both of you, run!
He's not gonna try that...
Hey, Heavy Iron!
If you fire that, the Metal Breath will also end up in smithereens!
That's not my problem.
What?
That was not our deal!
I never made a deal with you!
Captain's Cannon!
Iron Cannon!
Over there!
Could they be...
Jun...
Wild Guardy!
Jun is okay.
I thought I was done for this time...
That brought back some bad memories...
What a relief.
Do you think either one of them is down?
I don't think so...
Ugh... No way...
I only came for my Star Crown, and what a mess!
Earthling child! That will be all for today.
I'll be back for your Metal Breath soon,
so hang on to it until I return!
Hahaha!
Jun, what about Heavy Iron?
I don't think that was enough to get him.
There's no use staying here any longer. Let's get out of here, guys!
Aah!
Hey, take it easy, man!
Ugh. Stop moving.
Wild Guardy is fine.
Just a little tear in the fuel hose. I replaced it.
That's good to hear.
Those two were really scary...
Heavy Iron and Black Hook. Two of the most powerful Cardbots showed up at once!
We have to become stronger ourselves to be able to seal those two.
Yes, Jun!
I'll leave it to you guys from now on.
What do you mean, Crest?
The thing is, I realize how foolish I've been.
In the future, I'll try to help you in different ways.
Crest!
Please take care of Wild Guardy, Jun.
Of course!