The Mysterious Transfer Student
This is Blue Cop.
We have not yet found Heavy Iron's vehicle.
Resuming patrol from here.
No sign of a large trailer here either, over.
Ugh...
How can such a big guy be so hard to find?
Maybe he has the power to disappear, like someone we know.
You two!
Now is not time for a break, is it?!
Hey, you startled me!
Hear hear! Let's go back to the mission! One-two, one-two! Hurry up!
Alright, alright...
Ugh... that nagging little brat...
No complaining!
Everyone, please continue the search, will you?
Okay!
Ugh...
I heard that sighing chases away good fortune.
Four dollars.
But I thought it was for free?!
It was a joke. C'mon.
I know how you must feel.
We can't find Heavy Iron, who defeated Blue Cop...
We don't know who the Metal Cardbot who helped us was...
So, you're telling me to be patient?
That he will turn up in time?
No, I think we should hurry.
Looks like it's going to rain.
I must be going then!
Tell them to get inside the garage when they come back.
Alright. Take care!
Goodbye!
Is it really going to be raining like this?
Hey!
Watch where you're driving, will ya?!
Hey, guys, quiet down! We have a new student today!
Come on in.
Please introduce yourself.
My name's Crest.
Nice to meet you all.
Ah!
Ah! He's so handsome!
He'll make my channel blow up!
What are they squealing about, huh?!
What do you see in that guy, am I right, Jun?!
It doesn't matter how you look! What's important is in the heart!
Right, Anna?
Aw... ...but look at that handsome face...
Everyone settle down! Let me see...
You can go sit behind Vance there.
Thank you very much.
You have something cool on your wrist.
...y-yeah...
Let's start the class then. Page 48 of the textbook please...
Crest, where did you use to live?
In Eastpolis.
We had to move here because of my parents.
I don't know my way around here yet. Could you show me around sometime?
Of course! Any time!
Awesome.
Hmph! He's already making moves! I so hate that guy!
Watch this!
Watch out!
Huh?!
You better be careful, Vance.
How do you know my name?!
I memorized the name list. Of each and every student at this school.
C'mon, that's a lie!
I'm not lying, Lavi.
And Theo behind you.
And Anna...
Vera...
Kate...
Elaine...
Naomi.
Wow, that's amazing!
Just give me back my ball!
Take it from me, then.
Mine now!
It went in!
Such a good shot!
Just a little trick I learned.
Hey Vance, wait up!
Did I overdo it?
Not even Vance could do a thing...
So his name is Crest?
You find the new kid suspicious?
There's something about him that doesn't seem right, you know?
It's just not normal...
Hehe! Aren't you just jealous that Anna is obsessed, too?
Argh, it's not that! He took an interest in my Metal Breath too!
Something does seem a little off...
What are you talking about?
Aaah!
C-Crest, what are you doing here?
I'm sorry, did we disturb you guys?
Anna, did you bring him here?
Well, of course!
Crest has something he must talk to you about.
You should have said something before coming!
Why? You'd just be riding on your bike or something anyway.
This isn't a playground for kids. Get yourselves home now.
But Jun can stay?!
I never gave him permission either. He just barges in regardless!
N-No, Uncle Edo! You told me I could come hang out any time-
T-That's for sale! You shouldn't touch it!
I'm sorry, I haven't seen a car like this before-
Haha, no way, are you serious?! There are so many of these c-cars around here!
Y-yeah...
Crest only moved here not long ago, so it must be new to him...
It looks a lot like the R48 used in highway patrol,
but the shape of the bonnet is so different...
Woah, Crest! You're an expert in cars too?!
Well, this is a custom vehicle. It's been modified according to the owner's requirements...
Hmm... I see, that's why...
Haha, y-yeah! That's why!
But what did you want to talk about?
Yeah, I'm sorry this is sudden, but... could you do me a favor?
Just say the word! Crest can have any favor he wants!
That's not up to you to say!
Aah! Guys!
What's wrong, Anna?!
W-what is it?!
That's...
It's the Metal Cardbot from the last time!
The views will be out of this world!
Bring me Blue Cop right now! I know he's here somewhere!
W-what? Let's just see what it looks like.
Stop. We'll be discovered if we make a move now.
Show yourself right now, you coward!
I'm back. I didn't find any leads either.
Isn't that...!
Phoenix Fire, what's going on?
H-Hello, rescuers! Over here!
Ah! O-oh, yes!
Get in!
But I'm not even hurt!
Uh... just get in for now!
Jun? Aren't you coming?!
W-well.. uhh... there's no space for me in there!
I have my bike, so I'll go by myself, o-okay? Haha...
Theo, take care of them, okay?
Okay. You take care too.
It's our turn, Blue Cop!
What do we have here? Who are you?
My name is Wild Guardy. I'm here to be king of the Metal Cardbots!
Ha! King of us? What a joke.
Hang on! Wild Guardy. Weren't you on our side?
Yeah! You helped us in the battle against Heavy Iron, remember?
Hmph. Don't be stupid. I just wanted to show the riffraff that I'm the one in charge.
What?
You will submit to the one and only
Wild Guardy!
Jun!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Blue Cop, setup!
Blue Cop! Burst Shot!
Burst Shot!
Well done!
It is nothing compared to my shield!
I suppose that's not all you've got?
Of course not!
Blue Cop! Thunderbolt Smash!
Thunderbolt...
Smash!!
The Thunderbolt Smash did nothing...
My shield is an invincible shield trained over thousands of years on Machina planet.
Your puny attacks have no effect!
Wild... Slash!
Blue Cop!
Hey! You alright?
Jun! Hand it to me!
It's no use.
None of you are any match for me.
Huh? What did you say?
Haaaaaaaa haa!
Ha... ha!
Blue Cop? Are you alright?!
Since when have you guys been on first name terms?!
Hmph. Another pest intruder.
Blue Cop. We'll have our showdown next time.
Stop r-right there...!
Blue Cop!
B-Blue Cop, are you alright?!
Say something, Blue Cop!