Pure White Wings, Sky Gallop
That was refreshing! Huh?
Wh-where is it? It's not here!
What's going on?
It's gone! I bought a limited edition caramel pudding flavored ice cream, and it's...
HEY!!
Sorry.
You jerk!! Get out!!
What's going on?!
This is my house!
SHUT UP!!
So... that's why you two have been fighting since last night?
I told you I'll buy you one after I get my allowance!
That's not the point! I wanted to eat that ice cream right after my bath!
You were in the wrong, Jun.
Yeah. I'd be just as mad.
You think I'm the bad guy here?!
I also think it was wrong.
I fourth that too.
And I fifth that.
Limited edition ice cream? That's something you can't get, even if you have the money.
Glober!
What are you doing here?!
What a cold welcome. And here I thought I'd share some hot info, fresh outta the oven.
Gigantrex?!
Dad!!
This photo was taken a week ago in a jungle, 8000 kilometers away from Mowtown.
8000 kilometers?
That's far across the ocean.
How did he get all the way over there?!
What, you haven't heard? There's a rumor about a specialized Metal Cardbot transporter.
A specialized transporter?
Yeah, a professional transporter who can take you anywhere in the world with a single call.
You mean that transporter transported the captain to that jungle?
Could... they be a huge transport plane?
So that's why we couldn't find Dad anywhere!
Professional transporter...
What's your deal?!
You tell me!
Fighting is prohibited in my car center.
Providing a transportation service must mean there are more Metal Cardbots out there asking for that service.
Yeah. There are quite a few Hidden Cardbots living in hiding like me.
Hidden Cardbots?
Hidden Cardbots...
Why are you copying me?!
You're the one who's copying me, 'cause you have nothing original to say!
You wanna be kicked out?
Glober, I'd like to ask this transporter some questions. Can you help us?
No problem, but... This one's a bit sensitive, so be careful.
My name is Sky Gallop, the pure white wings that fly amongst the heavens.
Is't thou whom bid me?
I was just asked to call ya.
We're the ones who have business with you! We'd like to ask you something-
WAAAHHHH!!
WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU DOING?!
How dare a savage human speak to me... I have no intention of conversing with humans.
Wait! Why won't you talk to humans?
It would be against my chivalry...
...to shun a lady's question.
To the question of why I shan't speak to humans...
I shall answer that for you... my fair little lady.
What a weirdo...
I'm reminded of Fleta Z a little bit...
The answer is simple. I hate humans.
You hate humans?
I would normally never continue this conversation, yet it would be against my chivalry to ignore a lady's que-
Ah- okay, okay, I get it...!
Very well. So, it befell me when I had only just arrived on this planet.
To the aircraft of unknown nationality: identify yourself immediately, or we will engage!
How impertinent!
Wh-what the?!
Such savagery!
This is the scar from that incident. I kept it so as not to forget.
So that's why...
I'm sorry, Sky Gallop. I want to apologize on behalf of all humans.
What is thy name?
I'm Peruru.
Oh, Peruru! My heart is being swept away by thy kindness!
So Cardbots can shed tears too? Oh! My handkerchief!
What are you doing?!
Uh-oh! Sorry!
You totally did that on purpose!
Don't be like that. And you can always wash it, you know.
You definitely did that on purpose, Jun.
You basically trampled on her heart.
You guys are making me out to be the bad guy again!
Jun. Argue later.
Right. Do you know anything about this guy?
I am a professional. It is my duty to maintain complete client confidentiality.
You said client. Wouldn't that mean you transported him?
Let the cat out of the bag on that one.
Goodness, forbear with thy irritating noises...
Th-that is the treasure of Deus Machina. Why does a mere human have it?
Sky Gallop, I challenge you!
Huh?!
Pardon?
It's a duel! If I win, you'll tell me everything you know!
Ah. He intends to ask not only for information about Gigantrex, but about all the Hidden Cardbots they've been moving around as well.
He's really taking on a lot.
I decline.
Huh? W-Why?
A duel with a mere human being. The utterance alone hurts my pride.
Hah. It's obvious you're just backing out because you're afraid of losing.
What?!
If it's a challenge of the sky, it's my time to shine. Jun!
You've been acting all pompous, so I thought we should put those words to the test.
Hmph! 'Tis not chivalrous to dodge a challenge when thou hast been issued one.
I shall accept this duel!
You got this, Cielo!
Can I ride with you?
Eh??
May I bid thee why?
Duels are meant to be fought on equal terms. And...
I want revenge for my ice cream!
Oh, Peruru...
A bit excessive...
You sure about this, Peruru? You've never flown before.
You've only flown once!
Th-three times!
Jun! If we win, you're buying me 10 cartons of ice cream!
What?! Ten?! That'll cost all of my allowance!
And there's no point in us being here if you win!
I'm done arguing with you! Let's go, Sky Gallop!
Sky Gallop is lightning fast for a transport aircraft!
They've been through many battlefields to get here.
The nickname "Pure White Wings" is proof that they've never been shot down.
Pure white? But those wings are black and white...
Now, Cielo!
Missiles incoming!
This is nothing.
They blocked it?!
Looks like Jun doesn't even care that I'm inside here...
Sky Gallop! Let's repay him in kind with missiles!
It shall be done!
Shoot.
Cielo! Use Skyjet Shot!
You serious? But that'll mean-
Just do it!
Skyjet Shot!
What the-? Is he out of his mind?!
Counterattack! Homing Magnum!
Homing Magnum!
It seems those bullets are guided.
Use your flares again!
I can't use them right now.
Sky Gallop! Raise your altitude!
Sky Gallop, do you have any weapons left?
I do, however using them could put thee in danger.
I'll be fine. Attack them!
Very well!
Looks like they're plotting their next move. Cielo, be careful!
Don't worry about me!
Saber Arrow!
Wait here!
Thou art persistent. I shall end this now. Peruru?
Pardon me.
Now, allow us to settle the score!
You think that'll work on me again?
I shall reveal to thee...
the true form of the pure white wings!
All I see is a bigger target!
Then just try to hit me!
Cielo! They still can't outmaneuver your speed!
You're the champion of the sky, after all!
You got that right!
Cielo!
You're not getting away this time!
Proxima... Break!!
Victory shall be mine!
Saber Arrow Alpha!!
Cielo!!
Sorry, Jun.
Cielo! Are you alright?!
Because of me, you'll have to spend all your allowance.
I don't care about my allowance!
We won. Don't forget about my 10 cartons of ice cream.
I lost...
I had such an enjoyable flight with thee, my fair lady Peruru.
Yeah! Because of you, I was able to get my revenge. Thank you!
And you can just call me Peruru.
Very well, Peruru. I look forward to seeing thee again in the near future.
Ah, and you, filthy adventurer.
F-filthy?
Thou art forever banned from my transportation services.
Drat-!
Sky Gallop... They weren't bluffing. They really are strong.
We had no luck this time...
I wouldn't say that.
Word of you guys will surely spread among the Hidden Cardbots through Sky Gallop.
I wonder what the other bots on Earth will think of you?