Metal Cardbot Awakens from the Stone Tablet?!
Wow, it's a police car! Police car!
Ambulance!
Firetruck!
Giraffe!
No, elephant!
Wow, it's super bouncy!
Hey kid, we don't want you to get hurt. Just look at it with your eyes, okay?
I'm terribly sorry, they've been pestering me because they really wanted to see the cars.
Thank you.
It's nothing! Sightseeing is free after all!
Ms. Mona!
Ahh! Kids, how did you get up there?!
Your big brother Edo will carry you, so let's get down, okay?
My precious wings...
Fleta Z...
Hey hey, just hang in there...
I guess you repair airplanes too, hahaha.
Well, only sometimes.
Hey! Here's a giant ship!
Oh my, Kent!
This little runt..!
Stay calm, Black Hook.
Otherwise the kid could get hurt...
Ms. Mona! Did you see that?
Are you injured?
Perfect spot for a landing! You're lucky, buddy. Haha. Ahahaha...
Thank you so much for today!
Goodbye. See you again!
Yeah! Don't ever come back, you little troublemakers...
Uncle Edo!
Huh? Guys! You're here!
Who were those kids?
Ah, they're-
And why are these guys out here?
Jun!!
You're all welcoming me back? Aww, guys!
Those children came on a field trip from a nearby kindergarten.
It was a real mess.
Look! I'm covered in footprints.
I was worried that the kids would get hurt.
Even if they got hurt, I'd fix them.
What doesn't kill you, makes you stronger!
Get down from there!
They were more energetic than human adults.
Their mobility surpasses that of my Mini Gallons!
I would've recruited them all back in the old days!
Me tired... Hungry...
Good grief, all you're thinking about is eating...
Unidentified dome in Landfill Site 30. Is underground methane gas the cause?
You idiot! who do you think will read this kind of trash article?
Uh...
Mowtown Times is not a scientific journal!
I'm sorry, sir.
You know our newspaper sales are falling, right?
Bring me something more provocative and sensational!
I will.
Hi, Mr. Hawkins.
Hello.
Looks like you're ill-tempered again today, Dad.
Oh, Vera! My sweet daughter!
Dad, I'm a grown woman!
You know dad, I have that.
Hm? Have what?
A provocative and sensational news story!
Sensational news he says... Who reads news from soon-to-be-extinct newspapers these days, anyway?
Oof. Oh, sorry.
Uh- what's up with them?
Hey, do we have to wait much longer?!
Hurry, hurry!
I need more...
The battery is dead.
What'd you say?!
There's nothing left for us?
More will arrive tomorrow, so just wait until then.
Boooo!!!
You need what, exactly?
Parts! I need to invent more support items to maintain functionality.
I was also thinking it would be good to have my own medical equipment.
Right?
Oh, okay. I'll look into it...
Thank you, Edo.
Dexter, can you please stop bringing more cats in here?
Cute!
Don't worry, this one will be the last!
Please, let it be. I'll leave their food and snacks here...
Thanks, Edo.
Don't mention it...
Jun! You gotta' do something about your friends! If this keeps up, I'll go completely bankrupt!
Well, our numbers did increase a lot...
No matter how many times I repair them, they just keep coming up with something new...
I know how you feel, but it's not like we can kick them out...
Hey, watch it!
I barely grazed you and you're making a fuss over it? Heh.
What's that? I couldn't hear you. Say it to my face!
I'll let the doctor know you need your ears checked!
Do I have patients?
Everyone move!
Stop it, you two!
Ah, Uncle Ed-... Brother?
Listen well, Jun. If there's no incident happening, these guys are to stay sealed!
No way!
But I'd really prefer living outside!
From now on, when you're at this car center, I'm going to charge you for parking!
What? You'll take money from us?
You already know we don't even have a dime!
Charge us for parking? But we're not automobiles! ...are we?
I'm an airplane.
But I was well behaved.
Me too, me too.
Eheheh... It can't be helped. Just hang in there.
Alright...
Guess I'll take a nap, then.
Sorry everyone. Hm?
Wild Guardy!
Hi guys!
Anna!
Long time no see.
Crest!
It has been a while. Greetings to you all.
Thanks for bringing us here, Wild Guardy.
Don't mention it.
I picked him up at the airport, like you asked.
Thanks, Anna. Crest, have you been well?
...did something happen here?
Ahaha... Let's talk someplace else.
Hang out as long as you want, kids.
Thank you!
So what is it you wanted to show me?
Sebastian?
Yes, sir.
What's this?
Woah!
A stone tablet?
It was found in the ruins of Porcaca in the Andean mountain range.
This symbol... It's similar to the one on Metal Cards.
What?
That's not all. Porcaca ruins feature murals of giants and cars.
No way...
But that doesn't make sense. Cars were invented 300 years ago, but the ruins of Porcaca were built more than 4,000 years before that!
Or, maybe other Metal Cardbots came to earth earlier than we thought...
This can't be!
What's happening?
Master Crest, it's dangerous!
Wh-What?
Nnnngh! That hurt!
WHERE THE HECK AM I?!?!!
A Metal Cardbot? Jun!
You! Bright red guy!
Huh?
Who are you?
Huh! No one ever taught you to say your name before asking someone else's?
I'm Jun Gra-
Hold up! I hate going second!
What?
I'm known as the crimson flash, Red Blitz!
What an unruly runt he is.
Red Blitz? I've never heard that name before.
Is that a Metal Breath?
You! You're not Mukara! Where did you steal that Metal Breath?!
Mukara?
What do you mean I "stole" it? It was given to me.
Blue Cop!
Metal Breath, pick up!
Blue Cop, set up!
Behave and surrender!
No way, a Star Guardian?!
You know Blue Cop?
If you were trapped in that stone tablet all this time, then how do you-
Shut up!
Stop right there!
Dang.
Blue Cop!
Right!
Let's cut him off! Crest, take Wild Guardy and follow me!
Got it!
Please be careful, Master Crest!
Kids! Something happened to the window!
Jun, we'll take another route.
Got it!
Let's go, Wild Guardy!
Wuh- B-Blue Cop!
Heh, not bad!
Jun, hang on tight!
Stop right there!
You're too persistent!
We'll have to pay for that later!
Pay for that?!
Heheh!
I got you!
Oh, bolts!
Jun, we got him!
Stay down.
Surrender obediently.
Wild Guardy!
Who are you?
You're the one who stole the stone tablet!
Are you okay?
This is nothing...
Come back, Wild Guardy!
Huh? How did he get a Metal Breath?
Huh?
What?
Hey!
Did you forget that I'm here?!
Scarlet Hurricane!
Everyone, stay back!
Blue Cop!
Dang. Gotta' remember what the Captain said about controlling my temper.
I dunno who the heck you are, but the Metal Breath doesn't suit you.
What are you doing?
Ooh, you captured a lot.
My Metal Breath...
Don't make me laugh. It wasn't yours to begin with!
No!
Guys!!
Now, the best punishment for a bad kid who steals...
is a GOOD BEATING!
Blue Cop!
Jun is my dearest friend. I won't forgive anyone who hurts him!
Shut up!
If you say so... then, I'll start with you!
Blue Cop...!
You just said you're friends, right? Then prove it!
Now!
Okay...
What the?!
W-what is this?!
This power...?
I don't get it, but this is amazing!
Just who are you...?