Wild Cardbot's Roar
Blue Cop! What happened to your arm...?!
Tch! Those noisy jerks are back!
Get back here!
Are you okay, Blue Cop?
Wha- Blue Cop!
That's... it can't be!
Everyone... Get away from me!
Blue Cop! Take Ba-
Blue Cop! Can't you recognize us?!
I do! But...!!
He started acting like that after he was attacked by that helicopter bot!
This must be the "Beast Virus"!
Beast Virus?!
It's a terrifying disease that turns infected Metal Cardbots into vicious beasts.
If left untreated, Blue Cop's life will be in danger!
What?!
Wake up, Blue Cop!
Phoenix Fire! Set Up!
Mega Ambler!
Please stop it, Blue Cop! We're your friends!
Shut up.
I don't have any...
FRIENDS!!
Blue Cop!
Who...
Shh.
It's okay. You can relax.
Don't worry. No one is going to hurt you.
Sealing complete.
Wait! He's my dearest-
...dearest friend. Right?
Y-yeah.
Huh?!
Hey, kid! Wake up!
Do not lay a single finger on Soleil.
Soleil?
Is that the name of this child?
And just who are you?!
I am... Blaion.
Blaion...
Uncle Edo, how's Blue Cop holding up?
His appearance changed a bit, but he seems to be fine.
Jun!
Why am I in the car center?
What happened?!
Huh? You don't remember anything?
Looks like he completely forgot what happened last night.
He might be better off not knowing.
Hey...
Do you at least remember that I lent you money so that you could buy a book?
Wait, really? H-how much was it?
Just kidding!
What??
Falling for such an obvious trick? You're still so gullible.
Do you think this is funny?!
Mr. Mayor!
I had accepted you all because I believed that humans and Metal Cardbots could coexist!
What do you think will happen to my reputation when you cause a disturbance in the streets, like you did yesterday?!
I'm sorry.
Both of the troublemakers were bots we've never seen before.
Perhaps they're acting like that because
they haven't been on Earth very long and don't know the rules yet.
I do not care. There will be a mayoral election next year!
If my approval ratings drop any further because of you, I will be in-
DAD.
A-ahem! Excuse me.
Anyways, find that helicopter and fire engine as soon as possible.
Sorry. My dad is being so...
Don't worry about it, Anna.
Creating a society where everyone can live together is our goal and responsibility.
About that. I want to speak to all of you about last night.
Is that... a Weapon Card?
Yes. Blue Cop's Weapon Card. It wasn't just him whose appearance has changed.
My analysis shows that the Beast Virus that corrupted Blue Cop has been contained inside it.
By the way, what is the Beast Virus?
It's a pathogen that Wild Cardbots carry from creation.
"Wild Cardbots"?
First I've heard of them.
Since ancient times, there has been a force on planet Machina...
that's been hostile towards the Metal Cardbots.
They are called the Wild Cardbots, wielding the power of the beasts.
They were a fearsome species that raided our cities and wreaked all manner of destruction.
To counter the threat of the Wild Cardbots' uprising,
Deus Machina formed an elite unit of Metal Cardbots.
Wait. You must mean...
That's right.
They were the Star Guardians.
Though, with the destruction of planet Machina, all that fighting has become meaningless.
As I suspected, Wild Cardbots, too, somehow survived and came to Earth.
The helicopter and that Blaion guy must be one of them, right?
The way they summoned their Weapon Cards, and those eyes...
There's no doubting it.
The Beast Virus is a pathogen that infects the electronic neural circuits of Metal Cardbots.
To prevent infection, we must eradicate the Wild Cardbots as soon as possible.
Eradicate?!
Not sealing?!
Hey hey hey, you're taking this too far!
I'm being serious. This is a warning from a doctor.
An unlicensed doctor.
They are a dangerous species!
Or are they?
What are you thinking?
There was this girl named Soleil who stopped you from going berserk yesterday.
And she had a Metal Breath too.
WHAT?!
That can't be! Are you sure, Jun?
Yep! But it looked different from Peruru's and mine.
Only the chosen ones can wield the Metal Breath, right?
The treasures of Deus Machina should not appear so often, one after another.
This is hard to wrap my head around...
That's why we need to hear her side of the story!
That may be true, but how do we find her?
The population of Motown is about 7 million, ya know.
It'll be like looking for a needle in a desert.
Hey, hold up! What are we going to do about the helicopter spreading the virus?!
Heh heh... Don't you worry about that, Anna.
I'm always three steps ahead!
...But first I need to call the Mayor.
So you're awake, Soleil.
Goodness... Why did you do something so reckless?
My mother told me that because I am a strong girl, I should be helping those in need.
Still, you didn't have to put yourself in danger like that.
You and I just have a difference in mindset.
Ahh, ahhhh...
Is this thing on now? Ah, okay, okay.
Ah, this is a summons.
Ms. Soleil, who is with Blaion, please come to warehouse 003 at the port of Mowtown immediately.
I have something to deliver to you.
Who the heck would summon-
It's Jun. Probably.
Is he stupid? This channel is for Mowtown's disaster prevention announcements!
You're the stupid one. You're the one who called me by name in front of them.
Uh, ahem...
Since they're calling for us, why don't we go see what they want?
Are you being serious?
Or would you like me to go there alone again?
Ugh... Fine, fine.
Hmm...
I think I understood the plan, but do you really think they'd come all the way out here just because you called for them?
Of course they will.
Guys! When Blaion appears, proceed as planned!
Roger!
You can count on us.
And here I am again, going along with Jun's reckless plans every time...
Uhhh...
Hey! They really came!
You must be Blaion?
Welcome! I knew you would come.
This is quite the audience for a simple handover.
What's the real reason you called us out here?
Haha! You'll find out soon enough.
Now!
Bzzzt!!
Too loud!!
Phantom Hornet?!
Bingo!
Tch. I thought I'd finally found a place to settle down!
I'm sorry, but we need you to come with us!
I'll fix that awful temper for you!
What are they doing here?!
Hehehe! You wanna know?
There are CCTV cameras for monitoring traffic throughout Mowtown's roads,
so we used them to roughly track them down.
They must've noticed the cameras and flown through the canal instead of on the road...
...But unfortunately for them, there were witnesses.
Bzzt! Those pesky little things!
You're not getting away this time!
Where are you going? The diagnosis hasn't even started yet!
Are doctors really that scary?
Why did you call us here?
Why do you think?
Because we trust you.
You trust us?
Yes. You helped us in our moment of need, even though we were strangers.
That means you're not our enemies.
Bzzt! I would've spared you if you just left me alone!
Watch out!
Looks like we were right.
Hmph! Just catch them already.
I'll make you regret chasing after me!
Let's do this!
The Metal Breath...!
Don't worry.
It's simply taken a form that suits your friend's new wild powers.
Alright! Blue Cop! Are you ready?
I always am!
Blue Cop Wild! Set up!
Huh? Wait!
I thought I struck you with my poisonous stinger!
I don't know much about that so-called Beast Virus...
But we'll show you that we're no pushovers!
Bzzt! You should've just accepted the change! Phantom Legion!!
These are advanced holographic clones!
No problem! Blue Cop! Burst Gun!
Found them! Go!
Venospear!
Watch your five!
Alpha Bolt Cannon!
Infernal Stinger!
Now!
Thunder Howl! Smaaash!!
Thunder Howl... Smash!!
Way to go!
Wild Cardbot! Change Up!
Step aside.
Eh?
Phantom Hornet, sealed.
Soleil...?
I'll be taking them with me.