[The Revival of Flame Nova]
It is time for me to return... to my true form!
You have my thanks, Gigantrex. I've got my body back thanks to you.
Is that... Flame Nova?!
Wait, you know this guy?
Is that his...
...true form?
Give Peruru back!
Are you talking about this child? If you want it back, then you'll have to take it by force!
Hey!
Red Blitz!
No! You can't fight him like this!
Red Blitz! Set-!
Peruru!!!
Everyone, get out of here!
This way!
Rock Crush, keep our friends safe.
O-okay!
Oh, looks like you still have the strength to fight.
I can see why Deus Machina entrusted you with the Speranza. However!
It's time for you to retire!
Flame... Impact!
Huh? It's back on!
Where the heck is my daughter?!
I-I think it's... Oh! Editor-in-chief!
I'm sorry!
Are we sure this is the port where Jun is?
We can't just sit around! Hurry!
H-hey! Honey! Look!
I'm sorry to have to do this to my savior, Gigantrex.
But thanks to you...
I now possess an army of two billion Metal Cardbots, sleeping in the depths of the ocean along with the Speranza!
T-two billion?!
Tch... That son of a-!
What are you going to do with them?!
You ask such an obvious question.
I'm going to have them wipe out the human population of this planet, and then I will build my kingdom of Metal Cardbots!
What?!
A kingdom of...
Metal Cardbots?!
What?!
Stop talking nonsense, will you?!
I've heard enough about conquering Earth and all that!
As long as we're here...
...we won't let you do whatever you want!
Heh! Those guys barely got out alive...
...and yet they still have some nerve.
And what about you two?
I'll follow you! I like a strong guy.
Not to mention, you have the treasure of Deus Machina now.
I too shall follow.
Hahaha... It's reassuring to know you'll be joining me.
I merely wish to see how this all ends.
Very well. So long, for now.
Wait!
Ugh. You're a total mess.
- The device is tattered and the spindle is warped.
- Just what is going on?! Jun! Are you hurt? Let me have a look!-
- Can we fix him?
- Daaaaaad!
- Of course we can.
No one can use the Metal Breath except for it's chosen owner.
But I never considered the Metal Breath and its owner being stolen at the same time.
Will Peruru be alright?
His name was Flame Nova, right? Who exactly is he?
I don't know!
He wasn't part of our crew.
So he was with Sky Gallop and those brothers all along?!
Flame Nova was... my superior on planet Machina.
What?!
That would mean he was a Star Guardian too!
He was a valiant Metal Cardbot who was a three-time recipient of the Machina Cross.
But one day, he suddenly rebelled against Deus Machina.
He broke into the sanctuary of planet Machina in an attempt to steal the memory core of Deus Machina.
ENTERING THE SANCTUARY IS A CAPITAL OFFENSE. (FX-italic)
THEREFORE, I WILL SEPARATE YOUR BODY AND SEAL IT SO IT CAN NEVER BE RECOMBINED. (FX-italic)
He was sealed AND got his body separated?!
That goes to show how serious the crime he committed was.
But I thought he died when planet Machina collapsed.
I cannot believe that such a felon survived and came all the way to this planet to hijack our ship.
Inside the Speranza, two billion of our people sleep in the form of Metal Cards.
- If those Cards fall into the hands of Flame Nova...
- H-how much is 2 billion...?
- It's only a matter of time before the Earth is conquered by them!
- Is there any way to stop him?
- Excuse me, Mr. Theo? A moment, please.
- There is one way.
Really?!
Please tell us, Gigantrex.
By retrieving the Speranza before they get it in the air.
But they stole the Organizer too!
Don't worry! I can fly to Porcaca in no time!
Cielo, we can't fly like you.
Ah...
You're too impatient.
Speak for yourself...
I believe we may have a solution to this problem!
A solution??
Wait, this is...
We can just put them all on here and go!
Hehe, that's right!
Once we connect these vehicle transport containers, we can fly all the way to Porcaca together.
How did you get all of these, anyway?
Ahem. I am how! I bought some old, unused containers.
Uncle, is your wallet okay these days?
Master Crest paid for them.
I'm just glad I can help like this.
Can we really cross the ocean with these?
Do not worry! My interdimensional rails can take us anywhere.
Are you sure about that?
O-of course!
He is a dependable fellow.
Then, let's go now!
Dibs on front seat!
Hey! You can just fly!
I've never flown in the sky before!
I guess it'll be a bit like swimming in the ocean.
Good, good. It's great to have a bunch of big behemoths for this job.
Let's get started! First we move these over- Hey-hey-hey, you! Last behemoth! Come here and help us! Chop chop!
W-what's that? Are you talking about me?
...Guys, wait a minute.
I don't have the Metal Breath anymore. You don't have to follow my orders now. So...
That doesn't sound like you.
Gigantrex...
What are you saying all of a sudden, Jun?
We've been fighting side by side all along. I don't want to just sit back and watch from the sidelines!
Heh, heh! Well said, kid!
And you said that the Speranza is at the bottom of the sea. That means you'll need my help.
We do not want them to steal the Speranza away. And most of all...
We need to save Peruru.
If we don't, Mukara will never forgive us.
We'll go with you, too.
Yeah! Let's go save Peruru!
And we've got to pick up the kids who can't get home.
Even without the Metal Breath, you and I are connected by the bonds of friendship.
Let's go, guys. Let's put a stop to Flame Nova's plans!
Let's go!!
Haha, Blue Cop! You're really excited aren't ya- Huh?
Alright, line up!
Dad?
So this is the Speranza that Gigantrex and his crew traveled in.
The heck? This place is boring! It just smells like a whole bunch of mold.
'Tis only natural as the ship has been left unattended to for 4,000 years.
We need to find the engine room first. Our first priority is to power this ship.
Peruru. Peruru! Wake up!
Huh?! Wh... Where am I?
We're in the Speranza. Well, we're in the body of that fire truck guy, to be exact.
Glober?! When did you get in here?
Well, my back hurts a little, so I'm letting myself rest up a bit in here.
But that's not important. We'll be in big trouble if we stay in here. We gotta get away!
How? You said we're in Flame Nova's body.
Hehehe. And we'll use that to our advantage!
Is this the engine room?
They used whole, high-purity Machinasium as a battery to power the ship...
Such ignorance.
The power is off. We need to check the circuit-
Glober! Set Up!
What's going on?
The kid used the Metal Breath!
Get m'lady out! Now!!
You rat!
Cutter Whip!
The Metal Breath!
We gotta run away first!
Heh! You think you can get away?
Wait. That girl is no longer useful to us.
The recent suspicious events in this city...
You were at the heart of it, Jun!
Dad, We're doing this for both the Metal Cardbots and humanity-
Stay out of this, Anna!
I know you only want to protect them.
However, I also have a duty to protect my citizens!
We'll take care of the Metal Cardbots now!
Mr. Mayor!!
Nooo!!!
Metal Cardbots are our friends!
That's right!!
They've all been good friends to us!
Mr. Mayor, please listen to these kids! Violence solves nothing!
Anna's father. If you're going to threaten Jun and his friends, then I won't step aside even one inch!
I will not hear this any longer! Get out of the way!
Heeey, I've got a really nice picture!
The title is... Lemme think... "Police units and the mayor subdue children!"
You!
You might think that the Metal Cardbots are a threat if you only watch the news.
But... While there's one bot that likes to cause trouble, they have a lot of passion. There's a cowardly bot that is kinder than anyone else.
Metal Cardbots are just like us. They're all different, and there are more good guys than bad!
So, don't you dare hurt my friends!
Friends? Those Metal Cardbots are your friends?
Dad. You taught me to be nice to everyone.
And you also taught me to reach out to help a friend in need.
Metal Cardbots are our friends in need!
And we don't have much time! We need to go save our other friends! Right now!
Go? Where are you going?
The train to Porcaca will be departing soon. If you wish to board, please hurry.
Mr. Mayor. We will come back no matter what.
And when we come back, please tell us whether humanity can trust us or not.
Very well. Please take care of Anna. And please come back safely.
We will!
That should do it.
Tie me tighter! I don't want him to put a hole in my butt!
That's why I asked if you wanted to change seats...
Never!
Captain, tell me if you start to have a headache again, alright?
I will.
Jun!
Mom! What's all this?
Some food for the trip. I can't let you go empty-handed when you're out doing something great, right?
Be careful out there.
Mom...
Tell Peruru that I'll make some for her when she comes back.
Okay!
Excuse me!!
Lemme- Lemme go with you!!
Mr. Jim?
It's not that I'm greedy for a scoop...!
...well, maybe a little bit, but as a journalist, I want to tell the world the truth about Metal Cardbots!
Alright. Welcome aboard!
Speaking of which, I don't see Vera anywhere...
Ah, the editor-in-chief... uh, I mean Vera's dad told her to stay out of trouble.
Ah.
Now then, time to put my skills to work!
The train to Porcaca is now departing!
Have a nice trip!
Take care of yourself!
Come back safe!