Runaway Locomotive Blastrain
Wh-why did you only take me?
Because I made a promise. I promised to take you to Oatland station.
What?
Mr. Conductor...?
Are you okay, ma'am?
You're...
I'm Peruru! I came to rescue you, but...
The train suddenly got faster!
Midnight Express... Was a robot!
And there were other robots too!
I took pictures but none of them are clear!
My camera!!
Now, now. Calm down, everyone. Calm down.
You know something! Tell me everything you know right now!
Why can't you tell me what that was?!
I don't know anything either...
Are we sure we can just leave them there?
We can't take them with us. Anna said to count on her.
We called their parents, so they'll take care of them.
Jun! Blastrain is starting to speed up!
He might get derailed if he keeps on running like that!
Derailed?! Then what will happen to Ms. Mona?!
Peruru is with her too, you know.
AND PERURU!!
Cielo, I need to speak with Blastrain! Can you get close to him?
No problem!
Blastrain! Slow down! It's dangerous to continue at this speed!
Drat!
It's rude to ignore someone when they're speaking to you!
Jun!
Blue Cop? How are you holding up?
I'm feeling better now that I'm in the Metal Breath.
But, I think it's obvious that something is wrong with Blastrain.
As expected...
I kept thinking about what Blastrain said.
I had never seen railroad tracks before coming to Earth.
On this planet, I could just keep running on the rails.
Ah! Mowtown's railroad is a third rail system that draws power from the tracks!
It's likely that the residual electricity was flowing into him and is causing him to malfunction!
So that's why he lost consciousness...
He ate something that's bad for him...
So all we have to do is help him regain his consciousness, then?
You can do that?
Did you forget how many Metal Cardbots I've fixed?!
But to do that, I have to get on a train running at a terrifying speed...
Don't you wanna... save Ms. Mona?!
I'LL SAVE HER FOR SURE, JUN!!!
FULL SPEED AHEAD!!!
You're the best, big bro Edo!
Alright! Let's do this!
Ms. Monaaaaaa!!
Uncle Edo! Are you sure about thi-
I'm coming for you! Sit tight!
Mr. Edo! Be careful!
Leave it all to this genius mechanic! Let's go, Red Blitz!
You got it!
I'll be coming for you!!
Alright. Slowly now, keep on like this and-
AAAHHHH!!
Uncle!!
Mr. Edo!!
I'm okay!
AGAIN.
Huh? O-okay...
The power of love is scary...
Just wait and I'll-
WOOOAAAHHH!!
Mr. Edo!
I got him!
Thank goodness.
Thank goodness for what?! Onto the next plan!
What?
MS. MONAAAA!!
Ma'am!
Watch out for the cold!
Mr. Edo! It's dangerous!
Jun. Don't imitate him.
Okay! A little closer!
I got it! Alright, stay close, Cielo!
Hurry up, uncle! Tunnel up ahead!
A-a-almost got it!
It's not gonna work! Hang on tight!
W-w-wait-
AAAHHHHHHHH!!
Another failure...
Oh! The sun is rising!
Jun, the first train from Oatland Station is about to depart.
The track Blastrain is traveling on is a single track, and if it continues like this,
it will collide head-on with the train from the opposite direction!
THEN WHAT ABOUT MS. MONA?!
And Peruru!
- We don't have time to get Uncle Edo onto Blastrain!
- DO SOMETHING!! MS. MONA!!! AAAAAAARGH!!!
I'll do it!
Huh? You? But how?
Of course, I don't know anything about machines. But we have a genius mechanic on our side!
Yes! I'm here!!
Uncle, we're in the control room.
Alright, take good care of Ms. Mona, Peruru!
I'd appreciate if you worried about me too...
Alright, first things first...
...and next...
...no, that's not it! ...
...yeah. The third one! ...
...almost done!
Take care!
Like this?
Now, grab that wire from earlier and-
Hurry, uncle! We're closing in on Oatland station! We're out of time!
I know! Peruru, this is the last part! Press that switch on the right!
Blastrain, can you hear me? Blastrain, you need to stop now! Blastrain!!
He's not responding!
Was it too late?
It can't be!
What a peaceful start to the... day?!
NOOOO!!!
What was I doing...?
You've regained consciousness...
Mr. Conductor! Could you please take me to Oatland station?
I have to... take you to...
He-hey!! What are you doing?!
To... Where, exactly...?
I'm glad we didn't have a major accident, but Peruru and Ms. Mona are in danger! Let's hurry!
Okay!
Jun, let me face him.
Blue Cop! But you're hurt!
Blastrain is also injured.
We need to seal him as soon as possible so he can recover in the Metal Breath.
I want to save Blastrain too. And I'm the only one who can do it!
Okay.
I'll make an opening for you, then.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Jun!
Blastrain! This is your last stop! Blue Cop! Superior Docking!
Are you ready?
Yes!
Blastrain, let them go and come with us!
The train will soon be arriving at Oatland Station-
They'll get hurt if he fires that!
Blue Cop!
Peruru! Ms. Mona! Hang on tight!
Peruru! Ms. Mona!
Jump here, you two!
Ma'am!
Okay!
Looks like they've started without us!
Hurry up!
Get yourself together, Blastrain!
You've already arrived at your destination! You don't have to run anymore!
A-Attention all passengers, please remain...
Behind you, Blue Cop!
...seated!
Please refrain from verbally abusing or... Assaulting car attendants!
Mr. Conductor!
Blue Cop Trinity! Set up!
The train will soon be arriving at our last stop, Star Guardian station!
Please, be prepared!
Get ready, Blue Cop! Let's finish this!
Wait! Don't hurt Mr. Blastrain! He's brought me all this way!
Don't worry. We're just trying to let him rest.
That's right, Ms. Mona.
Wh-when did you get here?
He's just sick, so I'll fix him right up once they get the job done!
We can trust uncle Edo's skills.
He's fixed so many Metal Cardbots before!
Like my tooth!
And my butt!
You can trust in us.
Alright. I'm counting on you.
Alright!
Last... Destination!!
Galaxies...
Punisher!!
Thank you... for.. riding with us...
Metal Cardbot, change up!
Blastrain, sealed!
Is Mr. Blastrain okay?!
He's fine. We'll let him rest up in here for a while.
We'll have him repaired soon.
Thank goodness!
Have a safe trip!
Thank you again!
All of our secrets have been revealed to her.
I'm sure they'll be safe with Ms. Mona. Right, Uncle Edo?
Please let Mao be okay, please let Mao be okay, please let Mao be okay...
So that conductor robot is like a...
Another side of me that moves by my will.
Woah, you guys can do that!?
It's a little bit strange to see a human sized Metal Cardbot.
Inspection all done.
Jun, Thank you very much.
Don't mention it. You should thank Peruru and Blue Cop instead of me.
Aren't you forgetting someone?
Excuse me!
Ah, Ms. Mona!
Thanks for what you did back then. Here.
Aw, you didn't have to! I'm just doing my job-
Is Mr. Blastrain okay now?
Eh? Oh yeah, he is. I took good care of him!
Ah, Ms. Mona?
Yes!
I heard about what happened. I am terribly sorry for putting you in danger.
Don't worry yourself over that.
Anyway, Ms. Mona, is your brother okay?
My brother?
Was it... Mao, right?
Ah, Mao is... My pet dog living at my parent's house!
He's all better thanks to you. He's made a full recovery!
Aww, so cute!
Mr. Blastrain?
Ma'am?
Thank you very much.
He's malfunctioning again.
Uncle Edo! Why didn't you fix him properly?!