Exclusive! Steel Reporter
What's with this weather? Right when we're in the middle of carrying some valuable treasure.
Be careful. 'Cause when we deliver this thing, we'll be millionaires!
Heh. Don't worry 'bout it!
You're making a mess back there! Fly gently!
Stop yelling at me! You're the one who picked this scrapheap of an airplane!
What did you say?!
It's all getting knocked over!
Dang it!
The- the tablet!
Mmm... Delicious!
One milkshake coming up!
Uncle Johan! Your homemade pickles are the best!
You want mine too?
Hey, wait. Don't dump your pickles on Peruru because you don't like them!
I got busted...
How can you not like these delicious pickles?
Last night, a transport plane over Mowtown crashed in the mountains. There were no casualties, but the cause of the crash is unclear.
Oh, goodness...
There is some suspicion that the incident may be related to the last flying object seen over Mowtown city center, but...
It's Crest. Hi, Crest!
Jun! I found out where the third Metal Card tablet is!
Where is it?
It's in that transport plane that crashed last night!
He couldn't have gone too far yet.
Just where am I? Ow!
I'm certain this is not the mountain in Porcaca.
What happened while I was asleep?
Huh? That noise...
Phew. I'm saved. I thought I was all alone. Hi there!
Uh, h-hi...
M-m-m-monster!!!!
H-hey! Wait a minute!
What's up with him?
Hey there. Can you tell me where I am?
Are you shy or something? In that case...
Tickletickletickletickletickletickletickle!
Why are you ignoring me? Unless... You're not a Metal Cardbot?!
You're early.
Where's the crash site?
Over this way.
Heeeelp!!
A m-m-monster just showed up!
What? Sir, are you okay?
Excuse meeeeee!
Can you tell me more about that monster in detail?
It's him again.
Who is that?
He's a photojournalist for Mowtown Times. The one Vera's dad manages, or something.
Ah...
Excuse me. Here's my business card.
Mowtown Times?
Was that monster a giant robot?
Uhh, come to think of it, it kind of looked like one....
Where did you see it?!
Just around the corner, on this road here.
Do you think by "monster" he means...?
Yeah. I don't feel good about this.
Let's hurry.
Ahem! This is reporter Musclehyde from Cardian's Post. Would you care for an interview?
I've never seen a machine like that. Since when did humanity build those things that look exactly like us?
Where is this place? It doesn't look like Porcaca.
Why am I here? Where are my colleagues?
Of course you wouldn't know any of that.
Is someone coming?
This must be the site where he saw that monster, right?
Why are you following us?!
Huh? Wait, You're that friend of Vera's!
Now you recognize me?
Great! Do you want to help me look for that robot?
R-robot?
The monster that the truck driver saw!
Is there any evidence that it is a robot?
You're right, there's no proof. I took pictures with my camera, but for some reason all the data has been wiped out.
Thanks to that, I got scolded by the editor-in-chief, and Vera looked down on me.
Have we been too hard on him?
Just you wait, editor-in-chief! I'll take you down a peg or two for sure!!
Why is he like this?!
I'll reveal the secret of that monster!!!
A monster, huh? As I expected, the people here don't seem too friendly towards our species.
BOO!!!
Go away, or I'll eat you right up!
Heeeeelp!!!
Phew. Huh? Why aren't you guys running away?
You're a Metal Cardbot, right?
Huh? Wait! You know about us?!
Yeah, we know.
That voice...
It's been a long time, Musclehyde.
Cielo!!
Put me down!
It's been so long!
What's going on? Where is this place?
Calm down. Meet my new friends first.
This is reporter Musclehyde from Cardian's Post. Would you care for an interview?
An interview?
You haven't changed at all. His old reporter habits still come out.
There's newspaper on planet Machina?
Yes. But it is very different from the newspaper on Earth.
That's Mukara's Metal Breath.
Why do you have it? And why is there a Star Guardian sealed insi-
Well, that's because...
Where's Mukara?
He's no longer with us. He passed away a long time ago.
Passed a-- what?!
While we were sleeping, 4,000 years in Earth time have passed.
4,000 years?!
We still don't know where Captain Gigantrex went, either.
This can't be happening! It's worse than I thought!
Don't worry! I'll help you find all your scattered friends.
Ah... Who are you?
I'm Jun! Nice to meet ya!
Jun...
Don't fall for it, Musclehyde!
Red Blitz!
Red Blitz! You're okay too!
Don't be fooled by that little brat!
He's trying to use Mukara's Metal Breath to rule over us!
What?
That's not true! Jun has no intention to do that! If you'd just listen to him, you'd know that!
What's going on...?
Cielo, you fell for that kid's lies?! If that's how it is, then you're my enemy too!
Cut it out, Red Blitz!
Cielo!!
Jun! Cielo won't be able to stand up to Red Blitz like this!
Metal Breath, pick up!
Blue Cop S, Set up!
Blue Cop! Star Rising Shot!
Star Rising Shot!
You think that'll work on me again?! Scarlet Typhoon!
Block it, Blue Cop!
Stay back!
Be careful!
I'll take that Metal Breath back today for sure!
You're one to talk! Give me back my Metal Breath!
I know you stole that one too!
Jun!
Cielo!
Don't butt in, Cielo!
Sorry, Red Blitz. This is who I choose to stand beside.
You...!!
You need to try cooling your head!!
Red Blitz!
Jun!
Alright!
Cielo! Set up!
Crimson Shoot!
Skyjet Shot!
Musclehyde! Help me!
Homing Magnum!
Blue Cop! Star Rising Shot!
Musclehyde!!
Let's settle this now!
Blue Cop! Meteor Bolt Punch!!
Meteor Bolt...!
Punch!!
What?!
That form is...!
Such strength...
Those I had interviewed gave me this title. The strongest reporter who can take anyone down... The Arms of Steel, Musclehyde!
All those arms are holding down Blue Cop. One, two, three... Ah!
Look out!
Blue Cop! Hurry and get out of there!
Bronto Strike!!!
You still got that Herculean strength too, Musclehyde.
What's the matter? Get over here so we can continue the interview!
I met with Musclehyde today, so I'm done here.
Let's go, Musclehyde.
Ah! Red Blitz! Wait up!
Musclehyde! There's still more I need to say--
Cielo. You don't have to go after them.
What?
I'm sure we'll see them again soon.
Alright.