Era of Change
C'mon, bus driver! Do something!!
I've lost control of the engine!
Everyone! Please hold on tight!
- Thank you!
- You saved us, Blue Cop!
Four thousand years ago, from the farthest reaches of the vast universe...
metal-bodied mechanical lifeforms came to Earth. They are... the Metal Cardbots!
They no longer have a place to return to,
because their home planet, Machina, was destroyed a long time ago.
Mowtown's mayor Jacques once said...
So long as they learn about Earth's customs and uphold our laws,
humans and Metal Cardbots will be able to live alongside one another!
The Metal Cardbots have lived up to these expectations.
They spread out and got to work to prove that Metal Cardbots and humans can help one another.
Now Metal Cardbots and us humans are joining forces, working hard to keep Earth safe.
And, uh... that concludes our presentation. Thank you!
I'm deeply moved, Jun!
I had no idea you were the link connecting Metal Cardbots with humans!
I'm so proud of you, as one of your best friends!
I'm also proud of you, Jun!
Right...
Does anyone have any questions?
How long have you been hiding this...?
Uh... Hiding what?
Don't play dumb with me! I know you've been lying this whole time!
Uh, that's because...
I admit, I'm also proud of you as a friend too.
But I absolutely cannot forgive anyone for being more popular than me at this school!
Hey, by the way... what's it like to be inside of a Metal Cardbot?
Give me a ride in one of them next time too!
Me too! Me too!
This makes no sense! How can he be more popular than me?!
Ugh. I never wanted to become famous...
But in a way, you did practically save the world.
There's no denying that you're doing great as a mediator between humans and Metal Cardbots.
I agree.
Blue Cop!
Are you on duty?
My shift is over. After all, we promised to meet with everyone today.
Wild Guardy!
Hello everyone.
Crest!
You're here early.
We can't be late on a day like today.
Whaaat?! You're working on a farm now?!
Yes. Plowing the fields, tending to the horses and cattle...
It's indescribably satisfying to see the vast land managed all according to plan.
You are pretty meticulous, I'll give you that.
What on earth happened while we were away?
Everything's changed.
It end of the world.
Change means we’re making progress.
Jun's hairstyle has progressed quite nicely, too.
It still feels kinda weird. My mom forced me to get a haircut.
You're going to be on TV a lot, so cut your hair! (FX-italic)
Hahaha. Well, I like your progress.
To hell with progress!
What has Uncle Edo so upset?
It's because...
WHAT?! HE GOT DUMPED BY MS. MO-?!
Shhh!
- There could've been some misunderstanding...?
- What did I do wrong? Maybe I should just...
- There is no shame in accepting defeat.
- ...call her and ask her what I did wrong. Or maybe..
Here, use this.
Oh... thanks.
Eugh! You can keep it.
By the way, I don't see Rock Crush, Glober, or Blastrain around.
Ah, they went to visit Porcaca.
Are you still keeping in touch with Peruru?
How are those Speranza guys doing?
They seem like they're all doing well and in good spirits.
Don't cry when I win, Red Blitz!
Heh! You think you can beat me when it comes to speed, Spark Bit?
Ugh. They're at it again, even when we have guests from Mowtown.
Right? They never get tired of competing.
I don't even know how many times it's been now.
Why can't they just get along?
Haha! It looks like they're getting along quite nicely to me.
NO.
Whatever the case may be.
Since we're here, how about we make a bet on who'll win?
A bet?
Oh, that sounds interesting.
Red Blitz will win, obviously!
I second that. He seems like he's in a better condition than the other one.
How foolish. My little brother will win no matter what.
I... I can't choose!
Peruru, how abou-
No! You don't have to buy me flowers anymore, Sky Gallop!
O-okay. Just this once. Keep up the good work!
Still cherished by her love.
Sigh... huh? Ah, Jun!
Peruru! Are you getting along with the guys who came to visit you?
Yeah! Everyone welcomed them.
They've been asking why you didn't come too.
Haha! I promise I'll visit you soon.
It feels like it was only yesterday when I was staying at your place.
I really miss those days...
- I win!!
No way, idiot! I came in first!
What? You got any proof?!
Boys, stop it!
Mukara's reputation will be ruined if people see the Giants from the Sea of Stars acting so shamefully!
Peruru's Mother speaks the truth!
Stop with your nonsense!!
The Speranza will not be able to leave Earth if you persist with this behavior.
Or, I can always leave you behind!
Don't say something like that, Dad!
Mom!
So what, is it a draw?
How disappointing.
Which means...
Rock Crush, looks like you won the bet.
Yahoo!
Heh. Just look at these guys.
Ahaha! They all look like they're doing well.
As noisy as ever, right? How about you guys?
Everyone around here has been busy.
What about Flame Nova?
Blue Cop... I saw it... (FX-italic)
At the lowest level of planet Machina... (FX-italic)
There lies Metal Cardbot's very... first... (FX-italic)
Metal Cardbot! Change Up!
Flame Nova, sealed!
Ugh!
Are you okay, Jun?
What happened?
It stung my hand. It felt like he's rejecting me.
I don’t feel anything.
Augh!
Here.
How strange...
I've called out to him several times since then, but he's never answered.
I'm starting to think he may never wake up again...
No way. He'll wake up when he sees that humans and Metal Cardbots are getting along.
I hope he can open up his heart even a little bit, just like Heavy Iron did.
Yeah, right. Must be why he doesn't bother to show his face.
All he wants to do is work! Such an unsociable fella, that one.
Now, now, that's all for today!
You guys should go and meet up with the new friends you've made!
What? Already?
Get a move on.
We finally get together and this guy gets so heartless...
We're no longer a family under one roof to you, huh?
Don't take it out on us just because you got dumped.
SHUT UP!!
Well, we can always see each other next time.
See ya later!
What a bummer!
Wild Guardy, let's head out.
See you next week!
Phew! Let's go back home, too.
Mhm!
How's work going?
I'm enforcing parking and speeding violations these days.
It's certainly a lot easier than fighting Metal Cardbots.
Hehehe. There's no job harder than that.
About what Peruru was saying earlier...
Hm?
Let's wait until Flame Nova opens up his heart like she said.
Blue Cop! That's...!
Could that be...
Let's go after them!
Roger!
This is Blue Cop. Warning to all who hear this alert.
A suspicious helicopter and a fire truck were spotted in pursuit across the residential area toward the city center.
Report immediately upon sighting.
Could they be Metal Cardbots?
We were just getting back, and now we have to head out again!
Here you go. Thank you for your service as always.
Thank you.
Please come again!
What is that?!
Bzzt! How many times do I have to tell you to stop following me?!
I told you to stay out of trouble, Phantom Hornet!
Goodness... Go fight somewhere else!
I've never seen them before.
Are you sure they haven't met Jun already?
They haven't. I've never seen them before, either.
What?
Our police officers make an effort to memorize every single Metal Cardbot in this city.
This is Vold! Two unidentified Metal Cardbots are facing off on the road in front of the Milky Way diner!
Aaugh! Why does it always have to be at my family's diner?!
If we rush in without thinking, the restaurant could be in trouble!
Mega Ambler here.
Phoenix Fire and I will be arriving at the scene shortly!
Nngh, noisy! The heck!
We'll try to break up the fight. Set me up, please!
Alright! Mega Ambler, set up!
Forceps Crush!
Now, now! Calm down, you're going to startle people with all this commotion!
Bzzt! Calm down?! Why don't YOU calm down!
...you incorrigible idiots!
Can't you see it's not me you should be chasing,
but that guy over there?!
Tch!
Mega Ambler, are you okay?
You saw it too, right?
Those eyes... and their Weapon Cards...!
Wait, are you saying they're--?!
Ambly! Fifi! Are you okay?
Unidentified Metal Cardbots are fleeing eastward!
Block the coastal road now!
Blue Cop, set up!
Bzzt-! Augh!!
Freeze!
If you continue to disrupt the peace between Metal Cardbots and humans, we will arrest you!
Be quiet! Eat this and beat it!
Blue Cop!
Star Rising Shot!
Veno-Spear!
Jun!
Blue Cop!
What's going on, Blue Cop?!
I don't know... It... burns...!!
What?!
Blue Cop!
Wh... what happened to your arm...?!