Catch Me! Outlaw of the Sea!
Aaah!!
Jun! What's wrong?!
He just has a cavity.
A cavity?
When you eat and don't brush your teeth, cavity bacteria multiply and cause your teeth to rot.
Your teeth can rot?
Hah! Whaddya know, you humans are so fragile!
Our bodies are made of Machinasium and cannot be dissolved by any acidic substances.
But... we don't have teeth in the first place.
Why not just go to the dentist and get it fixed?
Easy for you to say! The dentist is so scary!
Really? I wouldn't know, because I've never been to the dentist.
Peruru, can you say "Ahhh"?
Ahhh...
Ooh! They're so sparkling white!
Jun, you should take notes from her.
Hey, Crest. Huh?
What?
A strange car was found sunken off the cliffside of Mowtown's beach.
Glober?!
Glober? What's wrong with Glober?!
Crest, stay there and keep an eye on him.
I will.
Let's call uncle Edo.
Okay. We should ask him to check on Glober.
Have you come to your senses?
You almost drowned out there.
What happened to you?
Well, it's a long story, but...
Have you guys heard about the recent series of unusual accidents in the waters of Mowtown?
Unusual accidents?
Leisure boats capsized,
fishing boats sunk,
large cruise ships went missing...
All within the last month.
I went to investigate 'cause it seemed fishy.
And when I got there, he showed up.
Known and feared by all as the Outlaw of the Sea back on planet Machina...
Deep Bite!
Is he like Jaws or something?
Now that you mention it, didn't you say you saw a Metal Cardbot that looks like a shark, Crest?
Yes. I saw him clearly when we were looking for the fourth Metal Card tablet.
That guy's biting everything in sight. I'd be done for if I didn't have a helmet on.
Wait! This looks just like the wound on Gigantrex's head!
Don't tell me, the reason why the captain was acting strange...
Perhaps it's because he was bitten by Deep Bite and his thinking circuits went haywire?
That can of tuna is gonna pay!
We need to seal Deep Bite before he causes any more trouble!
How can we lure him out here when he's in the ocean?
Don't worry! I've got a plan.
A long time ago, the beautiful Princess Andromeda was sacrificed to a sea monster for the good of the kingdom.
But! The hero Perseus bravely defeated the monster and rescued her.
The king was so pleased that he rewarded Perseus with a great riches, and the people remembered his heroism for a long, long time.
Which inspired me...
To lure the sea monster out with beautiful bait! "Operation Andromeda!"
NO!
Eh? Why not?
Why? Why should we be shark food?!
But you and Crest are...
GAAH!! I'm not doing this!!
Why would a Metal Cardbot chase after pretty people in the first place?
Jun, you're only doing this because you want to be the hero, aren't you?
Thank you, Jun!
You're the best!
Is that it, Jun?
Wha- No! I'm being framed! Let's move on to the next plan!
First, you all dive into the ocean.
Then you're going to make a lot of noise together.
This will drive Deep Bite into shallow water.
Then, pow! You all swoop in and defeat him!
Do we really have to do this?
Of course!
But if we get soaked with salt water, our bodies will rust!
Ehhh?? Whaddya know, you Metal Cardbots are so fragile!
I can't swim.
You don't need to worry about that. All you have to do is walk along the sea floor.
But this plan has one fatal flaw.
A flaw?
Yeah. A flaw.~
What are you doing?
Can you speak normally, please...?
Didn't you hear me earlier? Deep Bite is chomping down on everything in sight.
If you get caught in his path, you'll end up like this...
One by one.
NOOO!!
Can't we use your submarine?
Deep Bite is faster than that. We'll get chewed up right away.
How about floating a propane tank in the water and using it as a bomb?
You wanna blow him up or something?!
We're not trying to kill any sharks.
I asked my dad to make this area off-limits to ships for the time being.
Good job, Anna! You're always one step ahead.
That's all you got? Think more! This has been going on for hours!
What are you doing over here?
We should be thinking up a way to catch Deep Bite together.
Well, about that...
What? Friends?! You're friends with that Outlaw of the Sea?!
Shhh! He was rough around the edges, sure. But he wasn't the kind of guy who would just bite people for no reason.
I don't know what's made him so violent...
Alright! The new plan is done!
First, we'll use Musclehyde's Crane Bhuh as a fishing rod.
Hook the bait, and cast it out to sea. When Deep Bite takes the bait, we'll reel him in!
I call it Operation: Hook, Line, and Sinker!
Musclehyde! Set up!
What?
W-wait, when you said bait, you didn't mean-
Let's do this, Musclehyde!
WHY MEEEEE?!
The trick to bait fishing is to push and pull.
It's all about bobbing your bait so that it looks tasty enough to entice the fish.
Ah, like this?
I got a bite!
Great! Reel him in!
I can't! He's too heavy!
Then let us work together!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
The wire snapped!
Th-then what about Red Blitz?!
Red Blitz, we'll never forget you...
You can't get rid of me that easily!
You little scamp!
You're okay!
"Okay" my butt! I thought I was gonna die when he bit me!
That's...
A shark tooth.
Alright, let's try the Hook, Line, and Sinker one more ti-
Here's an idea. Why don't you go this time?
Jun!
JUN!!
Musclehyde!
JUN!! Let me go!
But you can't swim either!
I said I'm sorry...
JUUUUUUN!!!
That oversized guppy! Hey, you!
Wait, Red Blitz!
Now let go of Jun.
Jun!!
Where am I?
Thank goodness you're okay!
Deep Bite? Can you recognize me?
Glober! You were on this planet too?
Well now, quite the gentleman for a sea outlaw.
It's all because of this.
This tooth?
He had the same problem as someone else here.
Deep Bite must've been suffering from tooth decay, too.
Thinking about tooth decay makes it hurt even more...
Want me to pull it out?
Aah! N-n-n-no thanks!
It's done!
It feels like I'm born anew. Thank you so much.
You're very much welcome!
I want to return the favor. You can ask anything of me.
Anything?
Yeah. I'll do whatever I can for you.
Then... how about joining us?
Sure.
Huh?
Deep Bite, are you sure about this?
I won't go back on my word.
You did it!
Good for you, Jun!
Alrighty!
Metal Cardbot! Change Up!
WAIIIIT!! (FX-changeFail)
Red Blitz?
I'm not gonna accept him as our ally!
Red Blitz...