The Second Metal Card!
Wuh- W-what is this?!
This power...?
I don't really get it... But this is awesome!
Blue Cop's Metal Card!
Tch. I dunno what kind of trick you're trying to pull, but I'll turn you into a heap of scrap right away!
Blue Cop!
Blue Cop S! Set up!
Crimson Shoot!
Blow it away!
He parried my Crimson Shoot so easily...!
In that case, I'll just have to kick him myself!
Blue Cop! Take him down!
Blue Cop!
Blue Cop! Star Rising Shot!
Star Rising Shot!
Is this the power of a Star Guardian? Fine! I'm done playing nice too!
He's about to use another skill.
Not gonna happen!
Mega Crimson-
Blue Cop! Meteor Bolt Punch!
Kic--huh?!
Meteor Bolt... Punch!!
Wh-waiwaiwaiwaiwait-Argh!!
So, how is it when you use it?
Oh, well, it's almost the same as the one I was using.
Time to finish the job!
Metal Cardbot, Change Up-
You think you can seal me?!
See ya' later, Blue Hair! Bye-bye!
He got away.
Darn it!
Shall we talk about this?
Alright. But let's go somewhere else first.
This is exclusive!
My name is Peruru. A caretaker of the Porcaca ruins.
A caretaker?
In my village, it is said it's where the souls of giants from the sea of stars are asleep.
Giants from the sea of stars?
Ah! Giants must mean Metal Cardbots, and the souls are the Metal Cards. Which means...
She's talking about that stone tablet I brought here?
I knew it! So it was you!
Wait, calm down!
And put that down first, please!
Let's calm down and talk about this, shall we?
There was nothing left in the ruins when Master Crest paid a visit! Everything was already stolen!
Then what about that stone tablet, the Metal Card of Red Blitz?
We bought it from a local tour guide! He said it's a valuable item that is very hard to come by...
What was his name?
Araclahn.
Ugh. That guy's a famous black market dealer! You've been deceived!
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize. But first, I'd like you guys to help me.
A total of four Metal Cards were stolen from the Porcaca ruins, and this is one of them.
Ooh. It looks just like the one we saw yesterday.
Oh no, please don't do that!
What will you do if it wakes up?
We should take it out of here before that happens.
But how?
How about setting off a smoke bomb to cause a commotion?
(Fire!!)
You're trying to sneak the tablet away in the midst of confusion, right?
I already asked uncle Edo to bring a smoke bomb here!
This museum has a total of 188 video surveillance cameras. It's impossible to sneak away unseen.
Then we'll have to take it by force!
(Stick em' up! Gimme' everything you got!!)
I'm against it.
Think about this more seriously!
Anna?
Huh? Dad! What are you doing here?
I came to talk with the museum director about a new exhibit. What about you, Anna?
Ah well... We're trying to find a way to steal that stone tablet behind u-
Why are you telling him that?!
I can't lie to my dad!
Are you in charge here?
Hmm. This is a municipal museum, so you could say that.
This relic belongs to Porcaca village! Give it back!
You can't just demand him like that...
If we don't explain it properly, he's going to misunderstand.
Jun. Something is coming.
What?
What is that?
That's-
We need to clear out!
I found it! A Metal Card! Hehe.
Anna, are you alright?
Red Blitz!
Why does he look unscathed?!
We cannot let him take it!
Huh?
Sebastian!
Huh? What was that?
Good job!
Now let's get out of here!
Argh, that dang tin can!
You're unharmed, right?
Yes, dad.
Why did he suddenly ask me to bring a smoke bomb anyway? Huh?
Ah, Jun! What about-
We're bringing the slate outside! Get ready to flee!
Sebastian! Pass it here! Over here!
That tablet is property of Mowtown. Give it back!
M-m-m-m-Mr. Mayor, it's not like that!
Hand that over!
Red Blitz! Behave and be sealed!
Seal me if you can!
Dad!
Blue Cop, let's chase him down!
Okay!
I'm coming too!
You should stay and watch the museum in place of your father.
Excuse me?!
Again?!
Why is everybody driving at me?!
Because you're driving in the wrong lane!
This road is right-hand traffic! Right-hand!
So that's why!
Just a little faster!
This speed is the best I can do.
Jun!
Anna- Ah!
We're busy right now!
Why do you decide that?!
What does she have against me?!
Ahaha... sorry, Anna.
Jun, please save my dad!
Of course.
Jun! We have a visual on Red Blitz.
All right!
Hang on tight, you two!
You're persistent today, too!
L-l-l-l-l-look out!
Huh?
Commencing emergency ejection!
He caught up again! He's really starting to cramp my style- Ow!
Mr. Mayor, are you okay?
Red Blitz, give up and come with us!
Huh? Look!
The tablet awakened!
That's... the champion of the sky...
Cielo!
Hnnngh. That was a nice nap.
Red Blitz!
Where are we? What happened while I was asleep?
Let's talk after we teach that little runt a lesson.
Runt?
He stole our Metal Breath!
OK, situation understood!
Go hide somewhere safe, quickly!
And what about you?
Now, now, let's be quick, Mr. Mayor!
Be careful!
Don't worry about me!
B-but...
Blue Cop! Star Rising Shot!
Too fast...
Now it's my turn.
Skyjet Shot!
Look out!
Where are you looking?
Having trouble paying attention?
Blue Cop!
Both of you, cut it out! Have you forgotten your promise to Mukara?!
What did you say?! How the heck does someone like you know Mukara?!
Leave the kid alone.
Hey, Blue Hair. If you wanna save her, how 'bout making a trade for that Metal Breath?
What?
Throw the Metal Breath in there. Now!
No! I won't forgive you if you do that!
Shut up!
Agh!
I said leave her out of this!
Do it!
Okay, fine! I'll give you what you want, so just let Peruru go!
Don't be an idiot!
Heh, should have tried this in the first place.
Trade on three!
Alright!
One!
Two!
Three!
What is this?
When did he-?!
Why did he suddenly ask me to bring a smoke bomb anyway? Huh?
Be careful!
Don't worry about me!
Huh?! No! Don't touch that!
Nooo!!
Jun. Are you alright?
Ah... thanks...
Guys...