Fair and Square! Vector and Bit Brothers
A steel giant came from an alien planet to challenge humanity....
Good grief. What a troublesome pair.
Alien robot, it says! An alien robot!
You mean those monsters that seem to appear out of nowhere these days?
Yeah! Metal Cardbots, I think?
It says they came to Earth because their planet Machina exploded.
You actually believe that kind of news? That setting is so cliché!
Wow, it feels strange to read newspapers in this era.
Today's Mowtown Times, please.
Here you go.
Hahahaha! We're about to make ten times our usual sales thanks to this article!
Tomorrow's front page will also be about Metal Cardbots! Schedule the next interview!
Well, actually...
Eh?
You never asked for the robot's contact information?!
I didn't have time for that!
Then find a way to contact him! Don't bother showing your face in this office until you reach him!
It's no use.
There's no way we can just browse the internet for a way to contact Hidden Cardbots.
Speaking of which, what's your plan after we contact them?
Of course we'll-
Of course we're going to have a revenge battle!!
Okay! We'll beat them up for sure this time!
We're not going to do that.
Those guys were strong enough to beat you before. What if you end up losing again?
Argh, I wasn't in peak performance!
Alright, let's just calm down...
Then why are you trying to contact them?
We have to teach them that they shouldn't be seen in public, don't you think?
He's right. If we leave the Hidden Cardbots alone, something even worse could happen.
But if someone gets hurt during that time, the coexistence of humans and Metal Cardbots could be-
Let me handle that.
Glober! How long have you been eavesdropping?
I'm always by your side.
Hi, Glober!
Answer me, bro! What were you thinking when you did that?!
(Sparking Force...!)
Don't tell me you did it...
(Knuckle!!)
...because you thought I'd somehow lose!
It's not like that. I won't interrupt you any longer.
You better keep your word!
Man. You always interrupt me and it makes my stomach turn, right when I'm having some real fun and-
(Do you have any idea how terrified I was that you might lose, you foolish little brother?!) (FX-italic)
Huh?
Hm?
Hm? What?
Ugh, nothing...
Woah! I almost tripped over myself.
(That's exactly why I can't leave you alone!) (FX-italic)
What a peculiar brotherhood.
Flying to thy heart. Many thanks for bidding Pure White Wings Sky Gallop Transportation Service. How may I help thou?
Hey. It's me, Glober.
Eh? What the- They hung up!
Again! Again!
Flying to thy heart. Many thanks for bidding Pure White Wings Sky Gallop Transportation Servi-
It's me again.
Did I not compose it clearly enough that thou art permanently banned? Never bid me aga-
Oi, wait wait wait!
I'm trying to introduce you to your new client! You'll be transporting a very interesting client to a very interesting place!
Interesting client? Who, to where?
A Star Guardian, to the place where the Flash Vector and Spark Bit brothers are!
Hmmm... A Star Guardian...
Yeah. He wants a duel with those two brothers.
Wait, we're not going to fight them!
Shhh!
Very well. Allow me to contemplate this.
Will they really show up?
Don't worry.
Not only does Sky Gallop enjoy partaking in a good duel, but they also like to watch others duel.
I don't want to fight them...
Guys! Over there!
They're here.
Oh, my lady Peruru. I brought some purple pansies for thee. In the language of flowers, pansies symbolize eternal promise-
Th-Thank you...
There's no time for that!
It smells so good!
You want it?
- N-no thanks...
- Thanks for coming.
I assume thou art Blue Cop, The sole survivor amongst the Star Guardians.
Formerly a Star Guardian, yes.
Okay, now take us to them!
Thou art a short-tempered one. There is a condition for thy transportation.
A condition?
Young sir, master of the Star Guardian,
thou shall leave all thy Metal Breath-sealed servants hither. That is the condition.
S-servants?!
We're not servants!
Wait, are we?
Of course not.
You think Jun will accept that kind of condition?!
That wasn't part of the deal, Sky Gallop!
The original summons was for transporting the Star Guardian.
Above all, a duel should be fair and square. To have someone else step in and interfere with the duel is...
Absolutely! Unacceptable!
But I can come along too, right?
Thou art a paying customer, so thou may join us.
But this shall be the last time.
O-okay...
Looks like we have no choice.
We'll take care of them.
Yeah!
Come back soon.
Then it is decided.
Bon voyage!
Kick their butts!
The airplane shall be landing soon.
Lady Peruru and other passengers, prepare to disembark.
One million thirty-two, one million thirty-four, one million-
They always leave and come back without telling me. Take me with you sometime!
This is it. The Hidden Cardbot's hideout...!
It's the Star Guardian!
So he was the one you said you were bringing along...
They said that?
You heard it while right beside me!
Ah, heheheh...
I saw your interview, Spark Bit. I came here because I wanted to talk to you.
Talk to me? Ha! I want to beat up the Star Guardian, which is you!
If you wanna talk to me, do it after you beat me!
If it's what you truly want, so be it.
But, if I win, you'll get sealed by Jun.
That's a ridiculous condition. You don't have to listen to-
Fine! But if I win, leave me alone so I can live freely!
Agreed.
Hm. And thus the match has been set.
Is this why you brought them here?
Let us watch this broil, to observe if the Star Guardian's power is still intact here on Earth.
Don't you dare lose.
I always win!
Now then, Lady Peruru, please take this seat. The rest of thou, sit wherever thy want.
Let's do this fair and square.
Fair and square, huh?! That's one of my favorite sayings! Heheh!
Alright! Let's do this!
Blue Cop, I'm counting on you!
I'm counting on you too, Jun.
Blue Cop S! Set Up!
Let's attack first! Blue Cop! Star Rising Shot!
He's so fast!
Don't just use that pea shooter like a coward! Use your fists!
Like this!
One more time!
Heheh! It should've been this way from the start!
Blue Cop! Blast him up and away!
Now!
Supernova Smash!!
Now it's my turn! Sparking Force... Knuckle!!
(Sparking Force Knuckle is an inescapable technique that unleashes six, no, sixty, no, six hundred fists in a single second! You're doing great, my little brother!) (FX-italic)
That Star Guardian... He's blocking every hit!
Don't underestimate Blue Cop's Palm Protection!
So far, so good... but I might need to lend Blue Cop a hand.
If I leave these guys be, they're going to become a nuisance to me-
What the-?!
This is a fair and square duel. I won't forgive you if you interfere.
Okay, okay!
(Did you see me, little brother? I caught a cowardly saboteur for you...) (FX-italic)
(Huh? Ah... You didn't see me... That's okay, I won't let anyone interfere with you, so you can fight fair and square!) (FX-italic)
...can you let me go now?
Sky Gallop Transportation Service is closed today. Call again another time.
Hm?
You may continue.
Tch! This keeps getting more and more exciting!
(No. No way! It's the same situation... As before!) (FX-italic)
Just stay down already!
I told you, I'll strike you down with all my heart and soul!
With all your heart and soul, eh? That's one of my favorite sayings!
Tch. This keeps getting more and more exciting!
The feeling is mutual!
It's been a while since I burnt myself out like this.
For me, this is the first time.
Okay, I've decided!
Flash Vector is now my big brother, and I'm his little brother!
I'm... Your big brother?
Of course! 'Cause I fell down first.
Hmph. I only held myself up a second longer than you.
(He's enjoying this fight as much as the other time! This is really bad! If it continues like this, he'll make that Star Guardian his brother too!) (FX-italic)
(And if that happens, I'm-) (FX-italic)
(No.) (FX-italic)
(NO.) (FX-italic)
(NO!) (FX-italic xl)
(NOOOO!!!) (FX-italic xxl)
Uh?
Blue Cop!
You coward! You said to keep this fight fair and square!
I-it wasn't me! Bro! What the heck was that all about?!
It's... It's not what you think, Spark Bit.
(I-I un-unintentionally threw it! It's-It's not what you think!) (FX-italic)
(H-hey. What's with... that look in your eyes?!) (FX-italic)
(D-DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT!!) (FX-italic bold)
Blue Cop!
Capture Whip!
Sky Gallop! Hurry!!
We shall meet later.
Allow me to handle this, my Lady Peruru!
Thou would cheat in front of lady Peruru, let alone myself.
A duel that goes against the spirit of chivalry is invalid!
Channel three?
Ah, Mr. Mayor! How may I help you?
I ask that you refrain from making a fuss over a single article of questionable authenticity.
Excuse me? What are you- It's on the evening paper?!
Eh?!
Apparently, yesterday's press conference and shark scare were all for promoting a movie.
W-w-wait! Hello?! Mr. Mayor?! Hey!!
Chief editor!
What?!
We're terribly sorry. We didn't know it was a movie promotion...
I-i-i-it was all just... To promote a movie?!?!
Metal Cardbot VS Sharknado...
Is it really okay to make up a fake advertisement like this?
This is probably the only way to resolve all the commotion from yesterday.
This movie isn't actually coming out, right?
It's not uncommon for a movie to be cancelled in the middle of production.
But, that doesn't solve the Hidden Cardbot problem. What do you plan to do about them?
What should I do...
Bro! You told me you wouldn't do that again!
What was that for, huh?! Answer me, now!
We have a guest. It seems he would care to form an alliance with us.
So you wish to defeat the Star Guardian? Allow me to help you.