The Great Cave Escape!
Vance!!
Did you see how good my performance was? You get all that?
Yeah! Perfect! It came out great.
Hehehe! That bounty is as good as-
-ours now!
Hey, stop making weird noises.
It wasn't me.
You're lying! You were like "Roarrr"--
See? I told you it wasn't me-
So in summary, Jun lost his own Metal Breath to Red Blitz, so he had to borrow Mukara's Metal Breath from Peruru.
Yeah. I can't go back to Porcaca village either, until I retrieve all the stolen Metal Card tablets.
Musclehyde, do you have any idea where my Metal Breath might be?
Speranza.
Spera... what?
Speranza. It's the giant spaceship we arrived on.
"We"?
So none of you arrived here on the one-bot escape pods?
Right. The Speranza is much larger than those.
The four of us arrived here on that ship, but now it lies sunken under the sea after an accident. Red Blitz has a transportation device that leads there.
A transportation device?
Think of it as a convenient door that connects to the inside and outside of the Speranza.
Ah, that!
That means Jun's Metal Breath is in that spaceship.
If we seal Red Blitz, we'll have the transporter too!
And if we have that transportation device, we can get to the Speranza.
Then retrieving my Metal Breath will be a piece of cake!
Not to ruin the mood, but that transportation device is broken.
What?!
Is that true, Cielo?!
Why would I lie to you? I heard it from Red Blitz himself.
How did it break anyway?!
Because you were too rough with it that one time.
Don't be too discouraged. Maybe Captain Gigantrex has a spare.
Who was Gigantrex again?
The leader of the giants I told you about before.
JUN!!!
Vance? Lavi?
We've been looking all over for you!
D-d-d-don't get freaked out. But we saw a monster!
You guys told this story before.
It's true this time!
We even got footage of it. Look!
(What are you doing, Lavi?! Come on!)
(We need to get proof! Proof!)
I don't see anything.
But you heard it, right? The monster's noise that goes "Roar!!"
I don't hear anything.
Ugh! You too?! We brought it to the newspaper company, but nobody believed us either!
Should we give up on that bounty?
Excuse me, where did you see the monster you're talking about?
Mowtown landfill No. 30.
I see... then it'll be best to stay away from there for a while.
Eeeh?
You believe us?!
Thank you! But, who are you?
I'm Peruru.
Peruru!!
I'm Vance!
Lavi is my name!
Peruru...
What are you thinking?
Musclehyde woke up while being carried on a plane. What if Gigantrex suddenly woke up like him?
That makes sense.
Alright boys? No more going to that landfill. Here, it's a pinky promise with Peruru.
Yes ma'am!!
Is this the place where they saw the monster?
Maybe it's already gone somewhere else?
Oh, over there!
Someone's here!
Huh?
Excuse me, it's dangerous to go camping in a place like this.
Dangerous?
Some people saw a monster nearby here.
Heheheh, a monster, you say...
It's true!
AAAAAAAAIIIEEEEE!!!
What happened?!
Jun!!
Th-th-th-th-th-th-the heaaaaddd...!!
It's a mannequin.
Is this some kind of prank?
What?!
Does the monster you're talking about... look something like this?
A Metal Cardbot!
Is that Gigantrex?!
No.
We've never seen him before!
Who are you?
Well, well, seems like my introduction is overdue. The name's Glober. An adventurer who travels across the six continents, so to speak!
An adventurer?
That's right. I'm on an adventure in search of landscapes I have yet to see. Although, I'm always one step ahead of the pitch-black darkness...
Go home, kiddos, before you get hurt!
He's messing with us!
Cielo! Blow this smoke away!
Got it.
He's gone!
Jun! Over there!
Let's follow the trail.
Hm? Is that...?
An underground tunnel?
Ew, it smells awful.
Yeah, it smells like a trap.
Cielo, Take Back.
Do we have to go in there?
He may not be Gigantrex, but we can't just leave him like this.
I'll lead the way.
Okay, thanks.
What's all this?
It says "Keep out."
Yeah, right! Let's ignore it and keep going!
Roger!
Run for it, Blue Cop!
Again?!
What does it say this time?
"Danger inside: Turn back."
We won't turn back because of this! Everyone! Keep going and watch out for the ceiling!
Come on, Look out for the--?!?!
Wait, don't touch anything!!
Let's carefully go around these.
I'll go first.
Sorry!
Turn back!!
Good grief.
Capture Whip!
Glober!
Like I was saying, you should go home before you hurt yourselves.
I don't wanna' hear that coming from you!
You're the one who set all these traps here, aren't you?!
Isn't it your own fault for walking right into my traps?
What did you say?!
That noise...
It's the monster Vance was talking about!
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't call him that.
Hm?
You wouldn't like it if someone called your friend a monster, would you?
I'm... I'm sorry.
So you're saying there's another Metal Cardbot in this cave besides you?
Yeah. It's my buddy who's become sick and tired of the city life.
You're kidding?
There's holes all over the place.
Ay, Rock Crush! Some friends are here to meet you. Can you poke your head out for us?
No...
He responded!
I want to be left alone where it's quiet! I told you to leave me alone!
Man, what a coward.
Jun, I think we can be summoned in this place.
H-hey!
Mr. Rock Crush! Would you care for an interview?
Come out and fight already!
You got the wrong idea!
Don't provoke him!
I said...
I want to be left alone!
Look out!
Blue Cop!
Cielo, set up!
It didn't work.
Now we know that drill is super solid.
Stop it. He doesn't wanna fight you!
It doesn't look that way.
Why can't you just leave me alone?!
All of you! Get out of here already!
Metal Breath! Pick up!
Musclehyde! Set up!
Stop him before he attacks again!
Right!
Blizzard Age!
Oh boy. Follow me!
Musclehyde! Get out of there now!
What a troublesome kid...
Glober, didn't you say you're his friend?
Tell me. Why is he hiding underground like this?
Rock Crush and I have been friends since the days of planet Machina.
We each took an escape pod on the day Machina collapsed. After a long while, we arrived on Earth.
But an accident separated us before we could land together.
When I first laid my eyes on planet Earth, it was beautiful. I wanted to take in all of the new scenery.
But in that time, Rock Crush experienced pain.
Pain?
I hate it! I hate this planet!
Someone help me! Glober!!
By the time I found him, he had already become a recluse.
Then the tent and the mannequin are for...
For me to watch over him, and prevent anyone from getting near until he got back on his feet. And then, you guys showed up.
So you built all those traps just to protect Rock Crush?
Rock Crush!
Where is he?
Here's Rock Crush!!
Run!
Can't you at least give us a ride?!
Cielo!
Why do you keep chasing us when you want to be left alone?!
Oh no, the tunnel is narrowing down!
An exit! Cielo, let us down!
You two, take back!
Run for your life!!
I think we're safe...
He's not coming after us anymore...
You got off lucky, fellas. He doesn't come above ground after the sun rises.
You got your little butts kicked, so don't come around here anymore.
Adios!
What's with this guy...
He reminds me of my uncle...
I wanna go home...