Midnight Ghost Train
A sleepover? You mean you'll all study together? At Edo's car center?
Yeah! Theo and Anna will be there too, so it'll be fine.
I'm also coming along.
But you're already getting good grades, Peruru.
Besides, you don't even go to school here, and yet you want to study too?
You flatter me, ma'am! I still have a lot to learn.
Besides, my mother called me recently and asked, "Are you studying enough?" So I still have to study hard!
Okay, I understand.
I'll call Edo for the details, so stay out of trouble.
Blue Cop, please watch after them.
Of course, ma'am. You can count on me.
I deceived her... I actually lied to her...
- Don't be like that, Blue Cop!
- How could I let this happen?
- In this world, there is such a thing as a necessary lie.
- I've never lied to anybody in my life, except-
You got me into trouble too! How am I supposed to explain this to Yuri if we get caught?!
Ah, just make up a good story!
Ahem! "Midnight Express".
That's the name of a jet-black express train that appears out of thin air on the Mowtown Railroad, late at night.
No one knows where it's headed, so there's rumors that if you get on, you'll be taken straight to hell.
But! If my instincts are correct, that train must be a Metal Cardbot-
Jun. Who are you talking to?
Good thing Rock Crush is at the car center, 'cause that story would freak him out.
I'm sure Musclehyde will take good care of him for us.
Yeah. They said they were going to watch cartoons together.
Shh! It's here!
The Midnight Express!
I've never seen a train that looks like this! Who knows what makes this train run?
What is he babbling about?
Theo really loves trains.
Let's go!
Guys, are you sure this is safe? If we get on this train-!
What the- is that you, Jun?
Vance? Lavi?!
Huh? Wait, don't tell me. You're here to reveal the secret of this train as well-
P-Peruru!
Why is she with Jun?
Hey, what's your relationship with this punk?
Punk? He has a name, you know.
Huh? Is that...
Ms. Mona?!
Ms. Mona? I can't just sit here like this! Ms. Monaaaa!!
Wait, Uncle Edo!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Ms. Mona!
My, Mr. Edo!
You shouldn't be here. It's dangerou- agh!
I thought I missed the last train. Thank goodness.
What are you talking about? This isn't the last train.
What?
Don't butt in!
This train won't stop at Oatland station?
Why are you going to Oatland station at midnight?
It's because my Mao is in critical condition.
Wait, what?!
He's a spirited boy who loves to run around. He's been with me since he was a baby...
and now he's waiting for me to be there.
Oh no...
Wh-wh-what was that?
Was it a ghost?
Th-th-that's unscientific!
Let me have a look!
I'll go with you!
Unce Ed-
I-I-I'll open it.
- AAAAAAAAAHHHHHH!!!
- IT'S A GHOOOOOOOOST!!!
Jun?
Wait, that voice... Vera! Are you here to-
Solve the mystery of the Midnight Express, of course!
This time I'm gonna get the scoop!
So you were the ones who have been making all that noise.
Who is it this time?
Mr. Conductor...
A robot?!
Please, be quiet on the train.
A Sc-scoop...
Please adhere to passenger etiquette.
Aah! Hot!!
Jun! It's dangerous!
Who the heck was that?
Let's get out of here!
M-Ms. Mona?!
Mr. Conductor! Could you please take me to Oatland station?
Oatland station, you say...?
I'm begging you!
Y-y-yeah! Pretty please!
Her precious family member Mao is very sick right now! He's waiting for her!
How unfortunate...
Leave it to me. I'll make sure you get to Oatland station.
Thank you so much!!
Now I'll check everyone else's tickets.
Tickets?
A-ah, did we need tickets?
We don't have them!
Ah, so you all rode for free?
Please get off the train immediately.
Jun, guys, retreat!
Fare evasion is an unforgivable offense. (FX-glitch)
What the heck is with that robot?!
I can tell something's wrong just by looking at it!
It is useless to resist, fare dodgers, so please stop resisting. (FX-glitch)
Peruru!
Jun... Your idea better work...
Disconnecting the passenger cars from the locomotive! Great idea!
Vance and Vera are here, so we should be careful about what we say.
We can't let them know about the Metal Cardbots, right?
This is why I didn't wanna come with you guys- Huh?
Do not think you can hold out... forever!
Riding for free is strictly prohibited.
Hm? I don't see the other two-
Here!
You came in through the roof of the train. May I ask what you are doing here?
M-Mr. Conductor! I-I just wanted to get some fresh air...
Please step aside!
Keep up the hard work!~
What are you doing?!
What the-?!
WAAAAAAAH!!!
Blue Cop!!
Jun, are you hurt?
I'm fine... thanks, Blue Cop.
An emergency stop without a good reason... is prohibited.
I knew it. You're a Metal Cardbot.
I go by the name of Blastrain.
Blastrain! I have something to ask you. Are you a Hidden Cardbot?
Hidden Cardbot? What do you mean?
Wait, he doesn't know anything?
I know some things.
One of them is that you are my enemy!
Wait!
He looks sick.
Sick?
Deep Bite is right. He's got symptoms similar to that of Captain Gigantrex.
But he doesn't seem to be injured anywhere...
Oi. Easy now, Mr. Conductor. I've been watching you and it looks like you've lost your true self.
Excuse me? What are you-
Your mental state is like a runaway train right now. You remind me of my past self... I can't just stand by and watch.
I'm... I'm fine!
Hey, put that dangerous thing down. We have a competent friend named Edo. He can fix you right up, so come with u-
I knew my words wouldn't work on him!
Deep Bite is angry...
Jun. I guess we'll have to convince him by force!
Looks like we have no choice.
Metal Breath! Pick up!
Deep Bite! Set up!
Deep Bite! Beam Trident Gatling!
Go for his gun, Deep Bite!
Trident! Cannon!!
Great job! Now grab hold of him!
I didn't ask you to bite him...
Just let me run on the railroad tracks!
Blastrain! Why are you so obsessed with running on a railroad track when you have no passengers on board?!
Because I have never seen railroad tracks before coming to Earth.
There were no railroad tracks on planet Machina?
No, there weren't.
On Planet Machina, I had to create a rail of light myself to in order to move.
So if I took my eyes off of the road or thought about something else for even one second, I'd have a big accident.
But on this planet...
I could just keep running on the rails.
To be able to run without thinking... Can you imagine how wonderful that is?
That's one reason why I only run in the middle of the night, so as not to inconvenience humans!
That's why...
So I'm asking for your cooperation... In getting me back on the rails!
Reconnection sequence!
My camera...
Gosh, stop crying!
I still have 20 monthly installments to pay it off!
I heard the sound of a horn over there.
Just use the company camera!
But the company cameras are old and outdated!
Huh?! The passenger cars are moving on their own!
Where are you going without us?! Mr. Jim, Let's chase that train!
Let's go, Ms. Mona.
Deep Bite! Take Back!
We need to stop Blastrain now!
Attention, all passengers.
The train will be connecting with the cars shortly. We apologize for the inconvenience.
He's trying to combine!
Blue Cop! Set up!
Thank you kindly for your patience.
We will resume operation...
Now!!
Jun! Get out of here!
An explosion?!
Hurry!
Blue Cop...?
Jun! Time to fight back!
Alright!
Supernova Smash!
Supernova! Smash!!
You are no longer a Star Guardian. You have no right to stop me.
Wow! It's a real giant robot!
It really is a scoop! Mr. Jim! Take a shot! Now!
The bounty is mine!
It's so dark, I can't get a good pic!
Children! It's dangerous! Please stop!
You...! (FX-glitch)
I'm begging you! Would you please take me to Oatland station?
That's right... I need to take you to Oatland station...
I will- take you- to- Oatland-... (FX-glitch)
MS. MONA!!!
WAIIIIT!!!
Peruru!
MS. MONAAAAAAA!!!