Reunion with Gigantrex!
Abyss... This must be it.
This is the freighter that was carrying the 4th Metal Card tablet.
Master Crest, is this...?
So you woke up too, Gigantrex...!
Angry face, not angry face, angry face...
...not angry face, angry face, not angry face...
This is how you brew a tasty cup of coffee.
Cielo, I'm working on my notes.
Okay, keep going~
Gigantrex?!
The freighter that went missing three days ago off the coast of Mowtown may have sunk from an attack by Gigantrex.
That's not possible!
"Get along with the humans." The Captain always said that.
Could it have been in an accident, like with Musclehyde?
Perhaps. That's why I'm not jumping to conclusions just yet. There's another thing that bothers me.
What do you mean?
While we were investigating the freighter, we were ambushed by another Metal Cardbot.
What's going on?
Master Crest, look over there!
Can we shake it off?
Absolutely! Ejecting drones!
A submarine that looks like a shark?
Does that ring any bells?
No.
We don't have any colleagues like that.
What's a shark?
You should have given way earlier. Why would you even...
Wh-w-w-w-what are they doing?!
This is Edo Motors- Oh, it's you, Uncle Edo. What?
Jun! I'm in trouble!! Big trouble!! A Metal Cardbot showed up!!
A Metal Cardbot?!
Is it a submarine?
I told you I was on the road! It was a gigantic semi-trailer truck!
Trailer truck?
Could it be?
The Captain!
Uncle, where are you now?
The Route 4 Rest Area. I'm on a mountain road with no cell service, so I called from a pay pho-
Uncle Edo!
We'd better go look for him.
If we're facing the Captain, you can count us in!
Alright, let's hurry!
Hey! I just fixed this car!
Ah... I should have asked her to go out with me.
WAAAAAAAHHHHH!!!
You alright, Edo?
Th... thank you... Cielo...
WAAAAHHH!! It's so good to see you, Jun!!
G-Glad you're okay...
T-t-t-that's the semi-truck!
That appearance... it must be him!
It's the Captain!
That's Gigantrex?
He's huge!
His size is on par with Heavy Iron...
Captain! I missed you!
Wait! Cielo!
Captain... why...?
Something must be wrong with him.
This isn't the Captain we knew!
Mukara?
No. I'm Jun!
Why are you wearing the Metal Breath that I gave to Mukara?
It's a long story, but I'm keeping it for now!
The Metal Breath is a sign of trust between humans and Metal Cardbots.
But humans have trampled on that trust.
I believed that someday, surely, there would come a day when we could live together...
But, you humans have broke that tru-
Wait! Do you even realize that it's been 4,000 years since you all went to sleep?
Who are you?
I am the one who inherited the lineage of Mukara!
A descendant of Mukara? If that's so, I must not forgive you!
What?!
I entrusted humans with my dream.
A dream?
You mean a world where humans and Metal Cardbots can coexist?
No, progress!
I wanted human civilization to advance through the power of science.
But! You humans monopolized the fruits of your budding civilization!
Wait, wait! We never monopolized anythi-
I do not need your excuses!
Why are you doing this, Captain? You've told us over and over to get along with humans!
It won't be easy, but I'll need all of your help to persuade Gigantrex.
We're counting on you, everyone!
Sigh... okay.
S-sure!
Cielo...
Don't worry.
Let's do it with a series of attacks!
Roger!
Cielo! Set up!
Cielo! Skyjet Shot!
Cielo!
Musclehyde! Set up!
Dreadnought Storm!
Dreadnought Storm!!
That's our Captain.
That old man is still strong, even after all these years!
Do you think now is the time for compliments?!
Are you next?
M-me?! Waaahhh!!
Hmph. What a weakling.
Say that again!
What?
He's good!
Now!
Rock Crush! Set up!
Blizzard Age!
I-I-I'm sorry!!
Let's finish this, Blue Cop!
Blue Cop! Meteor Bolt Punch!
Meteor Bolt...!
Punch!!
Death Grip.
Blue Cop! Rock Crush!
This is the end for you.
Jun!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
You're right. Even after 4,000 years, we have yet to see a world where humans and Metal Cardbots can live together.
But maybe next year, by the 4,001st year, it'll be possible!
What Jun said! Believe in us!
Silence!
Captain! Stop!!
This light... I've seen this before..!
Does this mean... I am wrong...?!
Captain!
He left.
What just happened?
Well well, a pretty bothersome fellow has shown up...
I don't wanna see that scary guy ever again!
I've never seen him act like this. Such aggression... That's not my Captain.
Maybe something happened on that cargo ship.
What do you mean?
I saw a wound on his head.
That was on my mind too.
That could be why he occasionally touched his head...
Maybe that's the cause for his recent actions.