Fly up higher and higher / Deo nopi nopi naraolla
We ride for tomorrow / naeireul wihae dallyeoga
Searching for the giants from the sea of stars / byeolbada geoineul chaja
Shouting out with all our might / himchage oechyeobwa
Metal Cardbot S!
When I walk this road with you / Neowa gireul geotgo
Time becomes meaningless / siganeun huimihaejyeo
In this changed world / byeonhan sesang soge
We open our eyes again / dasi nuneul tteo
Set Up! Let's start again today / Set Up! oneuldo sijakae
Change Up! For us and our future / Change Up! naeirui uril wihae
I'll ride once again until I find you / neol chajeul ttaekkaji hanbeon deo dallyeoga
Fly up higher and higher / Deo nopi nopi naraolla
We ride for you / Neoreul wihae dallyeoga
Gather our friendship made of steel / gangcheol ujeongeul moa
Let's ride with all our might / himchage dallyeo
Metal Cardbot!