Facing endless conflict and division / gyesokdoeneun galdeunggwa bunyeol
It feels like we'll lose the light inside / bicheul modu ileul geot gata
But as long as we / geuraedo jeoldae
never give up and / pogihaji ma
Put trust in one another / seororeul mideo bwa
Together today, let's drive away / uri hamkke eoduumeul
the darkness using our light! / bicheuro moranaeja
Our hearts / tteuge-
shine passionately / -pge pureuge
hot and azure / bunnaneun maeum
May they forever blaze bright / ujuui byeolcheoreom
like all the stars in the sky / yeongwonhi taoreugil
Even through darkness and hardship / eodumi siryeoni
I'll be there to protect you / dakchyeodo jikyeonaelge
Shout out! Metal Cardbot / oechyeo! Metal Cardbot
Wild!