Glober's Last Stand
Oh! There's Mr. Crest! Mr. Crest!
Where is this movie being produced? Is the production of this movie even real? Or is it fake?
Would you please desist? Where did you even hear such nonsense?!
From an anonymous tip-off! Ah, w-well, that doesn't matter.
Are you perhaps trying to hide the truth?
You know... about the mechanical lifeforms hiding among us in this city?!
Let us depart, master Crest.
So that's how it went.
Who could have found out and reported something like that?
I don't know. But one thing is for sure.
Someone is trying to let the world know about the secrets of the Metal Cardbots.
Hahaha! He got you good, Bro!
(I've never even heard of a Metal Cardbot as ginormous as he is!) (FX-italic)
You're pitiful to have lost to Blastrain.
Blue Cop Trinity, who has the power of Deus Machina, is several times stronger than he is.
Stop adding insult to injury!
Flash Vector. This is our new colleague, Gigantrex.
Sky Gallop brought him over while you were out.
The treasure of Deus Machina was, in essence, my entrustment to Mukara.
And now... I must take it back from that punk of a boy.
With all due respect, you lost to him.
How are you going to get the Metal Breath back...
...if you've already been defeated in a head-to-head match?
You better mind your own business!
Hey, hey! Not the floor!
And why are you staying in your vehicle mode?
I cannot trust someone who refuses to reveal their own true identity!
That is enough, Sir Rex.
Flame Nova is an excellent source of information. I do not see any harm in listening to him.
If you truly are certain... then I will listen.
Very well.
This shark movie was a fake advertisement. Who would put out a fake ad, and for what purpose? It's obvious!
Metal Cardbots are already hiding among us, trying to make us let down our guard!
I don't think the day of their Earthly invasion is far off.
This is Warren Williams, the Editor-in-chief from Mowtown Times, signing off.
Hmm, invaders?
My name is Fleta Z. I am a fan of yours. (FX-italic)
Are Metal Cardbots really invaders? It didn't seem that way...
"I'll tell you the secret of the Metal Cardbots. Meet me at the Mowtown Wharf."
What is this? Who sent this-? ...it's anonymous?!
This is my best shot to uncover the secrets of the Metal Cardbots! If I get the right shot, my views will skyrocket!
Hello?
Huh. Nobody's here. Did I get here before them?
I'm sure this is the right place...
If you are looking for me, I'm here.
Eh?!
You must be a Metal Cardbot! Then the one who called me here must be-
Yes. Me.
Oh, my! Is he also a fan of me? I must really be popular among these robots!
So what's that secret you wanted to-
Capture Whip!
A-Another Metal Cardbot?!
Who are you?
Just a wanderer who happened to be passing by.
Might I ask why you're attacking an innocent human?
The Star Guardian operates on justice.
If you make a big scene, he's sure to be there with that little runt named Jun.
What do you mean by a big scene?
It's simple.
Attack the humans.
Better yet, target their celebrities that can do livestreams.
I have my reasons.
I don't think an old man who has been asleep for 4,000 years knows how to send an e-mail.
Which means there's another guy who hides behind you, pulling the strings...
all to stir up a conflict between the humans living here and Metal Cardbots!
This has nothing to do with you!
Cutter Whip!
D-Did that dirty robot just save me?!
This is no time for gawking!
Guys! We have trouble!
Glober! And...
It's Dad!!
Why is the captain-
-Fighting with Glober?!
Where are you going all of a sudden?!
Thunder Whip!
This is not a dream, nor fake footage.
Metal Cardbots are actually fighting right now, right before my eyes!
Guys!! We have- Uh?
And there's more. That filthy Metal Cardbot just saved my life!
Who's broadcasting such a big scoop like this?
Why, I dunno. Maybe because I'm pretty? Duh?
Vera!!
Hey kid, what are you doing?! Run along!
What? And miss this scoop??
There!
You tiresome wretch.
Dang-!
Death Grip!
You're next.
W-w-w-wait. What d-d-d-did I do?!
Don't you look away... I ain't done yet!
Persistent fool.
REX INFERNO!!
H-hey! Ow! Are you okay?!
The instigator is gone now.
And you will follow right behind him!
You're finally here.
D-Dad!!
Glober!!
This time, I will finally take back my Metal Breath!
No. 'Tis all of ours!
"My" Metal Breath... Thou better not forget what was agreed upon for this operation, Sir Rex.
Hmph.
Now, young sir... It seems our time does call upon's the Metal Breath to change hands.
W-Why is my dad working with the Hidden Cardbots?!
Glober... Guys! Can I leave him to you?
Of course.
Don't worry. Go do your thing.
Stop procrastinating and give it up already!
Captain!!
Let go of me!!
Captain, come with us already!
We'll fix you up!
DAAAAAAAAAAD!!! (FX-sarcasm)
Wha-! He's getting away!
Where do you think you're going?!
Jun! Go!
You think you can stop us with those peashooters?!
Jun! It'll be hard For Blue Cop to do this alone. I'll help him!
I'll cover him too!
Alright!
Take care of Glober!
Open fire!
Cowards. Ranged attacks against us melee specialists?!
Thou should'st be ashamed of yourself for running away!
Jun! I'll fight too!
Rock Crush!
Blizzard Age!
Such disgrace...!
I'll stay on guard here. Please save Glober!
You can count on me!
There are so many Metal Cardbots!
H-Hey. Why did you save me?
I didn't actually mean to help you.
But... I knew if I looked away, that kiddo's gonna' get real sad.
That kiddo?
Glober! Glober!! Glo- Huh?
Hey kid, what's up? The weather's really bad, huh?
Glober, let me seal you.
I want to live freely. Leave me be.
How can you expect me to leave a friend to die?!
Friend...?
Hahaha... A friend... You're making me blush.
Staying in the Metal Breath will help you recover.
We can go to Uncle Edo's and get you fully repaired, and then you can live free again!
You're too stubborn for a little guy. Do whatever you want.
Metal Cardbot! Change Up!
Good grief. I don't like how the sky looks today...
Take it easy now, Glober.
What the heck was that?!
Uh... Are you still streaming right now?
Jun...
Rock Crush! Vera, stay here!
Blastrain! Combine and supress Sky Gallop!
Affirmative! I'll leave them to you!
You dare?!
Attention all passengers, please stand behind the yellow line!
Blastrain! Set up!
Finally, a worthy opponent has appeared!
Deep Bite! Go for Spark Bit!
Little brother!!
So Metal Cardbots were hiding among human society, disguised as vehicles.
Deep Bite!
Right now, a lot of people in the world consider Metal Cardbots to be invaders.
I used to think so, too.
But as you've already seen, there are some Metal Cardbots that aren't!
And there's a kid who calls them his friends!
Captain!
Dad!!
GIVE ME BACK MY METAL BREATH!!
Oh no! Jun!
Could that be the power of Deus Machina?
Please keep your eyes on the road!
Last time you got lucky. Don't count on it this time.
I'm going to win, to turn you back to who you were!