Help Me, Deep Bite!
I'm not gonna accept him as our ally!
Red Blitz...
Oi, fish! I don't like you.
What are you doing, Red Blitz?
What has Deep Bite ever done to you?
Do you really have to ask?! Look at this!
It was a mistake to use Red Blitz as bait...
At the least- no, the leastest, I can forgive him for this wound.
But! I can't forgive him for biting my dad's head!
Dad? What are you talking about?
Don't you dare play dumb!
I'm sorry... I had a bad tooth ache at the time, so my memory's a bit hazy.
Then maybe you'll remember if I knock the screws out of you! Come outside!
Cut it out, Red Blitz. You're making Deep Bite uncomforta-
Great idea!
I was starting to get fed up with your attitude!
- Oh no!
- He was such a gentleman before!
That explains why he was called an outlaw.
Shouldn't we stop them?
Stop it, you two! Don't fight!
Lemme go home already!
It's... not much of a fight.
Red Blitz is getting owned...
What's the matter? Is it your bedtime already, baby boy?
I'm gonna make you pay, fish!
The power gap between the two is overwhelming.
Poor Red Blitz...
Metal Breath! Pick up!
Red Blitz! Set up!
Now we're talkin'! I'm gonna make grilled fish outta you!
What are you doing, Jun?!
I can't just stand by and watch Red Blitz get owned!
Heheh! Bring it on!
You're letting this fight get out of hand!
How are you planning to sort this out?
Let's do this, Jun!
Yeah! Crimson Shoot!
Jun!!!
Crimson Shoot!
Beam Trident!!
Nice job!
There's nothing nice about this!!
Let's go, Red Blitz!
Cielo!
Surely this is for the best!
Huh?
They'll understand each other faster by talking with their fists!
You fought well back there!
Heh. Not so bad yourself!
I see, it must be an Earth custom!
I'd love to cover this in detail! Can you explain, please?
Is that how it goes in Mowtown?
Of course not...
I'm not afraid of any fish out of water!
Jun! Let's finish this already!
Sorry about this, Deep Bite. But... Scarlet Hurricane!
I don't want any part of this...
Scarlet...
Heh! You think I can only swim in the ocean?!
Hurricane!!
Trident! Submarine!!
Mist?
I can't see anything!
W-What the heck is this?
Show yourself already!
There!
Red Blitz?
Red Blitz!
This is getting serious...!
What have you done?!
This is too much, even for what he did!
Be thankful I didn't swallow him whole!
- What?! Hey!
- Rein it in, rein it in!
- Come here! I said, come here!!
- Deep Bite, the outlaw of the sea... it'll be hard to get along with him.
Jun! I'm not gonna fight alongside that guy!
Heh! Took the words right out of my mouth!
Instead of understanding each other, the fight only escalated...
How are you going to fix this?
I can't leave things like this.
I-I'll go with you!
We'll bring Deep Bite back! You guys take care of Red Blitz!
Uuwoooogh... My butt...
Anyone here...?
WAAAAAHHHHH!!
Relax, Jun. It's just Deep Bite.
Ah, sorry...
Don't bother. I'm used to that kind of reaction.
I thought so.
I don't think you're an outlaw or someone dangerous.
Me neither. You don't seem dangerous.
And that's coming from my intuition as a Star Guardian.
Ugh. It's all because of my face.
Huh?
This scary looking face. It's the reason why everyone is afraid of me.
So then I thought, "I'll become someone who's truly terrifying!"
That's how I became an outlaw.
Isn't it pitiful?
Deep Bite...
Terrifying?
You?
W-what? Look at my face! Don't you think it's scary?
You're not scary at all!
Of course, it was a bit scary when you guys started to fight, but that's Red Blitz's fault, so...
Wait! Look closer!
Look how big my mouth is, and how sharp my teeth are! Look!
You can say that, but I can't really see it.
You know the moles that live on this planet, right?
I'm like a mole. I only know where you are by using infrared and sound.
I didn't know that...
Hehahaha! Alright!
So you're really not scared of me? I've never heard those words until now!
I almost can't believe scaredy pants Rock Crush isn't scared of him at all.
Hey, why are you guys all laughing? All I said was that I'm not scared of him.
It would be nice if Red Blitz and the others could understand that you're not someone to fear.
Ah! Then how about this?
Remember to follow the script, guys. I'll be the director and the producer!
But I've never tried acting before in my life...
Just believe in me, the director!
Make sure to have your lines memorized by tomorrow!
Will this actually work...?
You're all done.
Ow! I told you to be gentle!
It's still tingling... I'll make him pay the next time I see him!
Count me in!
Let's go and knock the screws out of him right now!
Let's go!
Stop!
We're busy, Peruru!
Wouldn't it be better to make peace with Deep Bite, who can dive into the ocean and find the Speranza?
That is true...
She has a point...
But he bit the Captain's head! I can't forgive him for that!
Cool your temper and use your head!
I understand how much you cherish Gigantrex. But!
Think about how Deep Bite felt when you suddenly told him you don't like him.
I'm sure it was startling.
If I were him, I would be angry too!
WE'RE IN TROUBLE! BIIIIIIIG TROUBLE!!
Hey, hey, hey! What is he doing?!
He suddenly went berserk!!
I'm a big bad mole monster- I mean, a big bad Metal Cardbot!
The heck is all this?
Please stop! Rock Crush!!
Wha- You!
Not today, you evil Metal Cardbot! Deep Bite will not forget-
No, forego- Uh, foreign...
Ugh. I don't know what you're trying to do, but make them stop, Jun. It's dangerous.
M-me? I'm not doing anything!
I'll crush everything in my sight!
My used crane I haven't paid off yet!
Phew. It's sturdy enough...
Get back!
Waahhh!! A monster!!
Rock Crush is in danger!
Rock Crush! I'm he-
Musclehyde!
What is this?!
Cielo!
Go help them!
We'll continue fighting later!
Sounds good to me!
Let's do this!
Guys! Wake up!
Deep Bite! Thanks for helping us out.
It was nothing.
Tch. All that fuss over nothing.
Mission failed, I guess...
Good grief, just do it already!
You wanted to seal him. Do it before I change my mind!
That means-
Make no mistake! I just need him for his diving capabilities.
You just can't be honest, can you?
Well then. I'll happily join ya, Jun.
Okay!
Metal Cardbot! Change Up!
Deep Bite! Sealed!
I'll happily accept you too, Deep Bite.
Well done, Jun!
We have another friend on board!
Yeah!
That kid sure is something.
So... surely you have plans to clean this mess up.
Isn't that right, DI-REC-TOR?!
I TOLD YOU COUNTLESS TIMES TO STOP MAKING TROUBLE FOR ME!!!
I'M SORRY!!!