Attack of the Final Boss!
Sail, sail, sail... Sail your ship!
Let's go together down the ocea-
What is that?
Huh?
Aah!
Jun seems to be in high spirits today...
He got a new bike from his parents for his birthday...
And that's not all I can do!
Oh... so it seems like Anna gave him that scarf, and he's very fond of it.
That's right...
Question. What's a birthday?
It's the day he popped out from his mother's belly.
Popped out from where?
No, no...
It's the day you celebrate your birth into this world.
Ahh...
So... they were celebrating Jun?
Shouldn't we get something for him too?
A... gift?
But I don't have money...?
Hey, what if we save money on fuel...
But fuel prices have gone up!
Hey guys, I have something to discuss with you.
Huh?
This was inside the escape pod we stopped yesterday.
Is it a trailer?
Where's the tractor that transports it?
It will be in the pod that separated and fell into the sea.
So the owner of this trailer was inside the escape pod?
Jun.
Please look up the data in the trailer using the Metal Breath.
...like this?
Data access complete.
Code name: Heavy Iron.
Heavy Iron?!
So he's landed here, then...
Why? What is it?
He's just one scary Metal Cardbot.
The most powerful and evil outlaw that will use brute force to crush anyone he doesn't like!
He will come here looking for the trailer, since it's a part of his body.
We may already be too late then...
Anna!
Late? What do you mean with that?
Take a look here.
Let me see... an oil tanker explodes in the waters near Mowtown.
One survivor said they saw a huge shadowy form swimming in the ocean...
Did it collide into a whale?
No, this is...
Could it be...? Heavy Iron?
For real?!
This is the location where the escape pod landed.
The oil tanker sunk here.
You mean that... it's not headed towards Mowtown?
Let's move the trailer somewhere outside town!
We don't want anyone to get harmed!
Yes.
So... who's going to move it?
Hrgh! I knew this was going to happen! Ugh...
Stop complaining. I'll be sure to see if you are pulling it along, okay?
This trailer is super heavy!
Jun! Over there!
Look here.
Where are you taking my body?
Heavy Iron!
He caught up with us this fast!
Huh?
Ha!
There's an empty construction site there!
Let's go there!
Mega Ambler, Phoenix Fire! Try to keep Heavy Iron here!
Got it!
Come on then, you outlaw...
Yeah! We'll take you on!
Disrespectful runts!
Great job! No one will get harmed out here!
What do we do know? Heavy Iron will be here soon.
Let's hide the trailer in that tunnel first!
You have to enter in reverse mode!
Huh? What do you mean?
It could be hard for you to get out if you go in head first.
I'll watch out for you. Now, hurry!
Ugh, what a bother...
How pathetic.
Stop!
It's coming!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Shadow X, setup!
Shadow X, Spinning Cutter!
Spinning Cutter!
Why is it so hard?!
I see. Then, Heli-Tornado!
Got it!
Heli-Tornado!
Haha! How is it?!
Oh no, no way!
Jun!
Blue Cop, setup!
Blue Cop, Thunderbolt Smash!
Thunderbolt...
Smash!!
Blue Cop! Are you okay?!
Where's my body.
Here it is!
You want it? Come take it from us!
Ha.
Anna, let's hide!
Do it now!
Blue Cop! Blow the tunnel entrance with a Burst Shot!
Got it!
Jun, it worked!
What happened? What?
We did it! It's game over for the tractor!
W-what is that?
What's going on?!
You brats are starting to annoy me.
I mean it.
All you had to do was give me my trailer.
You will pay for this now.
That's Heavy Iron's true form!
It's larger than I expected.
Seems like... he's hopping mad!
Just because he's big doesn't mean he's strong!
Let's try attacking in turns!
Mega Ambler, setup!
Mega Ambler, use Forceps Crush to stop him from moving!
Yes!
Forceps Crush!
Phoenix Fire, setup!
Your turn, Phoenix Fire!
Burning Hammer!
Yaah! Burning Hammer!
How do you like my fire?!
Hahaha. That was barely a scratch to my Heavy Iron body.
I'll show you what true power is!
W-what's that?!
He's going to destroy everything!
Iron Cannon!!
No, Anna! Are you okay?!
Theo. Are you alright?
I think so... are we still alive...?
Now you understand, you brats...
I am the most powerful Metal Cardbot.
Heavy Iron!
Now... kneel before me.
Vow loyalty to me, and I will let you live.
You know well by now that resistance is futile.
What was that...
This is it, Blue Cop!
Megavolt Punch!
Megavolt...
Punch!!
I'll end it here today since I found my body.
But...
You will pay for this!
Thanks, you saved us all.
Huh?
It disappeared.
But... who could it have been?