Farewell, Blue Cop
You can summon Mega Trucker any time you want with that card,
and you can give him commands, too.
Huh? What's going on? What happened here?!
Huh???
Uh, hello Edo...
Stay away from Jun!
Uh, sir!
Edo, were you at the repair shop?!
I dozed off while working late... then I woke up when I heard loud noises outside!
It was you! You were the one who broke my fence!
And totally crushed Jun's bike!
Aah, Edo, that's not what happened!
It's a misunderstanding, I-
Don't come any closer!
What are you doing, sir?
I'm going to get you, you heap of scrap metal!
Please stop, sir, this is not safe!
What did you say?!
Please stop! Blue Cop is not a heap of scrap metal!
He's from some planet...
I am a Metal Cardbot. A mechanical lifeform from planet Machina.
Right, that one!
Why are you here? Are you trying to bait us or something?!
No no no, sir! We are...
Hey, who are you calling, Edo?
I'm calling the cops, why? Do you think the army should be handling this?
T-that's not a good idea, sir!
Please, stop him, Blue Cop!
Yes.
Uh, hello? Is this the army headquarters-
Waah!
Let me go! You're trying to get rid of me to shut me up, aren't you?!
We have to stop this misunderstanding somehow.
What should I do?
Just untie me already... my shoulders are killing me!
Blue Cop. Do something about his shoulders.
His shoulders?
Yes! Show him you're not a bad robot after all.
I heard on the radio that delivering a vibration of 3200 rotations per second helps blood circulation and relaxes the muscle.
Woah!
Ohh... that's good... that's the spot. Try to really get in there...
Ugh...
Are you alright?
No, I'm not... I'm hurting and I'm thirsty... make me a coffee, would you?
Yes, sir.
So you can make coffee!
It's a basic skill for surviving on planet Earth.
White sugar and no cream, okay?
Yes, sir!
Here you are.
Augh, why is it so sweet?!
By white sugar, did you mean... one cube?
You're trying to give me diabetes, huh?!
Where are you going, Edo?
To work. I have a meeting with a partner in the morning, actually.
And you! You better be sure to get this mess cleaned up while I am gone!
Hey, kiddo! You look like you need help. Want a hand?
This voice is from...
Mega Trucker?
Jun! Let's summon Mega Trucker!
Summon? You mean... bring him back here?
Yes. A Metal Cardbot that has been sealed must obey the master.
Don't worry about it.
Alright, I'll give it a shot.
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Hmm... such delicate work is my specialty.
Are you sure you can do it?
Leave it to me. Cue the music!
Mega Trucker, you're doing great!
Just getting started!
Woohoo!
Stop!
You're getting in my way! This is my favorite part!
Woohoo!
Aah! Both of you, stop! Stop fighting and start getting along!
...did you guys finish cleaning-
What is this?!
What in the world is this?
We... are very sorry.
Oh, that's right! My meeting is starting soon.
I can't waste any more time.
Don't get into any more trouble while I am gone.
Jun, don't you have to go to school too?
O-Oh, that's right!
Why is everything getting in my way!?
Looks like you need some help with that, Edo!
Blue Cop! Here's a job for you!
So you can transform into a car...
Yes.
Wait... are all these cars your bodies?
Huh?
There's a bad traffic jam.
Augh, but I'm in a hurry!
I'll try my best.
Hey, what are you going to do?
Woah, you're going too fast!
Oh my God!
Hang on, stop the car!
Come on, I said stop!
Police car sirens should only be used in serious situations!
This wasn't one! And you!
You aren't even a real police car!
...I'm sorry, sir.
Hmm... I have... something important to discuss.
Edo! I'm back!
Oh, Jun! What's up?
Were you able to make it to the meeting?
Uhh... sure.
What about Blue Cop?
Just... forget about that robot.
What do you mean?
I promise not to tell anyone about you. In return, you must leave.
I can't do that! As you know, Jun has the Metal Breath, sir. Without Jun-
That's not my problem at all! If something happens to Jun, how will I explain that to his parents?
So, you should leave. Go back to your planet!
Edo, how could you be so dumb?!
Huh? What do you mean?
Machina planet was blown up by an explosion! Blue Cop has no home to return to, Edo!
Huh... what?!
Why didn't he tell me he had no home to go back to?!
That truck seems to be a little wobbly, isn't it?
Coming through, sir!
Ugh...
That's the wobbling truck!
Oh dear... was the driver dozing off?
Oh no! We must alert the train, quick!
Blue Cop... where are you now...
You wouldn't mind me using the siren now, would you?
Blue Cop!
Yes! Give me a command, now!
Yes! We gotta push that truck away from the crossing!
Hey, stop there! Please stop! C'mon, please stop!
This won't do. I'm not strong enough on my own.
Hey, Jun!
Mega Trucker!
Looks like an emergency. Need my help?
I surely do!
Metal Breath, pickup!
Mega Trucker, setup!
Scoot over. I'll help you with that!
Just a little bit more!
Now!
So you spent thousands of years wandering through space until you finally landed on Earth?!
Okay... from now on, planet Earth will be your new home.
Really?
I'm sure we will need your help in the future.
Don't worry, I'll take care of you guys!
Planet Earth is...
...our new home?
Here, you can use these, Edo!
Eugh...