The Secret is Out!
Hey, Dad! Do you know what's up tomorrow?
Tell me what's happening tomorrow 🎵
Did you forget? I'll give you a hint, it's-
Was it your time to clean up?
No, I mean something more special-
Is it the spring clean? Your room is a bit of a mess, you know.
Why don't you also get to the garage and garden while you're at it, huh?
Ugh...
Hm? Vera!
What are you looking at?
At Jun!
Huh? Jun? Wait... Vera, do you have a crush on-
No!!
I'm just keep an eye on him. He's hiding something!
Hiding something?
Yes! It's a top secret thing that would make FBI agents go after him!
You'd better watch out!
A top secret thing...?
Metal Breath... pickup...
Mega Trucker... setup...
Now... come at me!
Very well!
I think I could make your shield even stronger with a little tricking.
Huh, really? Then let's do it right away!
It's not that easy. The stronger the shield, the more energy it consumes, you know?
What if it stops working when you need it?
Come back, Mega Trucker!
I'll be off now, Uncle Edo...
What? Leaving so soon?
It's my turn to clean up, ahaha...
Hey, why is he acting so weird?
Secret? With Jun?
Mhm. Do you know anything?
Oh, uh...
Attack!
Let's go!
You got it, Blue Cop!
Seal complete!
I might say... uh...
What is it, Theo?! Tell me!
Actually, actually...
Well Jun is...
Yeah?
It's his birthday today!
Oh-aha! That was it?
Y-Yeah, that's it...
Oh, Theo, you should have told me! I misunderstood!
Then... we should go celebrate!
...celebrate?
Yes! We should get a cake and go to Jun's right now!
S-shouldn't we call before we go-
But that's no fun! I'm sure Jun would like a surprise event too!
Oh no, this does not feel good...
It's my birthday and I'm mowing the lawn!!
Mom, Dad, everyone, I'm not feeling loved today...
Jun, what are you up to?
Can't you see? I'm mowing the lawn!
Looks fun! Can I try? Please, I wanna try!
Woohoo!
Is it fun?
Haha! It's the best!
Hey, Jun! Let me do something, Jun!
Haha! This is fun!
Woohoo!
I'm happy that you guys are happy...
Jun.
What if someone sees them? We agreed that Metal Cardbots should be a secret.
That's true...
Ah, Blue Cop! Come here and help me!
But don't let anyone see you!
Hey buddy, wasn't the food today the worst- huh?
This street has been closed. Please use the other street.
Let's just go play games.
Yeah, I agree... let's go.
...should we really be doing this?
Come on. Nothing is going to happen. Just relax.
Oh, excuse me!
I'm sorry, this area is out of bounds.
...huh?
Hi, I'm sorry, but we just need to get over there. Could you just let us through?
But, uh... well, uh...
Oh, it's you!
Perhaps... you could go ask the person... in charge?
Oh, haha, right. Hold on a minute!
Okay, let them through!
What's going on?
Theo has come over.
Waah!
Hello!
H-Hey Anna!
Hey, this is an emergency! Hurry, transform!
Oh no, this is bad!
Sorry for dropping in like this. Is this a bad time?
Nonono! Of course not! You guys are always welcome here!
That's good! What were you up to?
Uh... cleaning the garden?
Wow! Can I see?
B-b-b-but Anna! I-It's not done yet!
Why is there a truck in the garden?
Uh, someone just asked me to take care of it!
Aah! Hey! Anna!
Why don't we-
Aah!
Shadow X, stealth mode on!
What is it? Why are you doing that?
There was just a huge bug!
Theo, you hate bugs, right? I know!
So Anna, what brings you here?
Oh, that's right!
Now, you can open your eyes...
Happy birthday, Jun!
Thank you, Anna! I never imagined you'd come to celebrate my birthday!
Hey, time to blow out the candles!
Jun. Calling Jun.
What's that sound?
Yeah, what's that?
It must be the TV in the living room!
I think we have to open the street now. Will that be okay?
Jun?
Jun! I need a reply!
Jun! Jun! Jun!
Stop saying my name, please!
H-happy birthday, Jun!
Jun! Why isn't he replying?
What? What's the matter?
Maybe he has been taken hostage by robbers!
Jun! I'll be there soon!
Blue Cop!
What was that?
It sounded like an accident!
Anyway, let's blow out the candles!
Yes! Let's sing the birthday song!
1, 2, 3!
Happy birthday to me...
What's that?!
No... this looks really bad!
Don't stand there watching! Give them a hand!
What do we do? Jun! Hurry, give us a command!
Jun?!
You're hiding something from me, aren't you?!
But, I...
I'm done!
Ah, no! Anna!
Hello...
Aah!!
She just found out...
The secret is out...
So you guys are like...
refugees who came to Earth all the way from planet Machina at the end of the galaxy?
Oh...
She's smart.
So, Anna. Will you help us keep these guys a secret, please?
I'm afraid not.
Huh? Why not?
Because this is... the first encounter between humanity and aliens.
This is not something us kids can handle by ourselves.
But I'm a grown-up.
I'm sorry, Mister Edo.
Wait, please stop calling me Mister...
Anna. We just want to live quietly on planet Earth.
Please trust us.
It's not that I don't trust you. I just think...
that we won't be able to keep lying to the grown ups.
Hey, it's my dad!
Dad? The father of this child!
There are people who are grown-ups?
Anna's dad is the grown-up who is in charge of important things.
He's the mayor of Mowtown!
Shh...
Hello, daddy!
Anna, where are you?
...he's asking where I am!
Why is he asking?
Could it be... he found out that you're with us?
No, that's not possible!
He's not a mind reader. How would he know?
No, no! My dad really knows everything!
He knew when I skipped piano practice and when I broke a vase!
Yeah! Grown-ups know everything.
Yeah, you can't lie to them, you know.
Hang on! You mean, the mayor already knows?
About us Metal Cardbots on Earth?