Guardian of the Forest
Watch this explosion of art, haha!
Hahaha! Something exploded, alright!
What did you say?!
Oh, I said nothing...
Get out of here right now...
It wasn't me!
I said, get out!
W-what was that?!
V-Vance!
Aaah!
Hahaha! A monster?!
You expect us to believe that?!
We really saw it, guys!
It had a long neck, sharp teeth, and he said
"Get out of this forest! Do it now!"
The monster could even talk?
No, no way...
You better hurry home today so you don't see it again!
I swear it's true!
What do they mean by monsters?
I'd make up a more believable story if I were them...
You mean... like robots from space... right?
Crest?!
W-well, what do you mean "robots", Crest?
Y-yeah, w-what do you mean by that?
Seems there's so many strange things happening in this town.
There might be something to Vance's story, don't you agree with me?
There's been a series of accidents taking place in the new highway being constructed in the north of Mowtown.
All the workers on-site said the exact same thing.
That a giant monster appeared from behind the fog.
What?!
Don't you think it should be checked out?
Waaah!!
You mean... there are monsters like that on Earth?!
There weren't any monsters like that on Machina planet!
Don't worry... that's only a movie, guys.
Nah, come on. I knew it wasn't real.
Blue Cop!
Jun.
Let's go monster hunting!
What?! A monster?!
You're joking, right?!
Huh?
I'm not going near any monster!
What's wrong?
No idea.
So you think the monster behind the rumors could actually be a Metal Cardbot.
That seems to be the most likely story.
I wonder how much Crest knows about the Metal Cardbots...
Let's not worry about that.
We need to focus on finding the monster first.
Okay... we're here.
Crest!
Hey guys. I was waiting for you.
Yeah. Let's go.
That's... some bad art.
Looks like Vance.
Be careful, master.
Can we just stand here without permission?
Construction has been suspended since the accidents. All that remains is...
Waah!
Wildlife. Like that raccoon.
Lots of animals in this area...
There were many around the repair shop too.
They disappeared when development projects took place in the area.
Hey, look over there!
Is that a footprint?
It's huge!
Probably not an animal...
About 12 meters in height.
Bigger than the robot we saw last time.
You can't say for sure it was a robot...
Yeah! It could be a conspiracy trying to cover up what's going on!
Not a conspiracy theory now.
Watch out, Jun. It's close.
Get out right now!
What's that?
Where did it come from?!
Get out of this forest...
...right now!!
It's a monster!!
Who are you?!
An excavator?
Careful, Jun. That's a...
I said, get out! Didn't you hear me?!
Waah!!
Let's hide under there!
One, two! One, two!
Edo, hurry!
I can't get in!
That's what happens when you have all those muscles!
Over there!
I told you to get out... right now!
Take that!
No, Edo!
Uncle Edo!
The monster was indeed a Metal Cardbot...
...what do I do? I can't summon them with Crest around...
Let go of him!
Wait a moment, Crest!
Hey!
Why are you chasing people away?
I don't like humans.
What is the problem?
You really don't know?
They're all destroying the forest.
Every time the humans expand the roads, creatures of the forest lose their home.
That's the problem.
You threaten people pretending to be a monster and destroyed the construction site?
Yeah. Got a problem?
A true guardian this forest has, huh...
Using violence to oppress others?
Isn't it the same thing as what these humans you hate are doing?
Shut up!
Waah!
Uncle Edo!
You fools! You don't even know how many forest creatures have been sacrificed
because of humans!
Crest!
Don't worry about me. Just run!
You know I wouldn't do that!
Jun?! Are you going to show him?!
The secret of the Metal Cardbots?!
Metal Cardbot, pickup!
Is that...
Wild Guardy!
You all better run!
Guys! Please take care of Crest!
Got it!
Crest, are you okay?!
I-I think I can walk...
Hold on us tight!
How about me, guys...
Waah!
You?
You injured a human being?
You are a disgrace to the Metal Cardbots!
Oh!
Master Crest! How did this happen?!
Are you okay?
I tried to be careful, I swear...
Crest! Oh no!
Oh!
Master Crest, sir!
...I can't see anything!
Be prepared, Dexter.
Wild Guardy is here to take you down!
Hold on!
If he hates humans that much, he won't open up to us right now no matter what we do!
Please, leave it to us!
You said... us?
Metal Breath, pickup!
Blue Cop, setup!
Out of my way, Blue Cop! Dexter is mine to punish.
Wild Guardy, can't you see? That doesn't solve anything.
That's none of my business.
That pile of metal hurt my friend!
What?!
You can't run away from me!
Stop it!
Don't you dare try to command me!
Mega Ambler, it's your turn!
I'll leave it to you, Mega Ambler!
Got it!
You will have to settle things with me!
Out of my way!
W...where is this?
Huh?
Here! Blue Cop!
Dexter! Stop!
Hey! Don't follow me!
Blue Cop! Are you alright?
That was a powerful hit...
Blue Cop! Let's use the Infinity Force Break to end this right now!
Infinity... Force Break...
Infinity...
Force...
Break!!
But... if we use it here... the tunnel could collapse.
But... Blue Cop...
Dexter is gone!
Let's go after him!
Woah, careful!
What's this...